Chapter 11

Harry looked up from Potions Quarterly with an unimpressed sigh when Archie burst into her room and shut the door loudly behind him. He leaned against it, looking slightly out of breath, and she half-expected him to drag a piece of furniture across the frame. For a moment, a much-younger Archie transposed himself from memory over her fourteen-year-old cousin. A bittersweet smile twisted her lips. In four years, her cousin had both changed entirely and not changed at all.

"She won't take no for an answer," Archie panted. His eyes were wide in his head and bright like a cornered animal's.

"Lily?" she guessed, flipping a page unconcernedly. Her mother had been wheedling Archie about giving her a duel since they returned from school. She'd been polishing her skills with Remus since the World Cup, but after hearing how well the third task went, Lily wanted to test Archie's ability for herself.

He flopped dramatically down onto her bed, and she hastily rescued a cup of tea balanced near her foot from certain doom. "This is the fourth time this week she's asked. I told her I get enough of that in the tournament, but I think she can tell I don't really mean it."

"Just keep putting her off," Harry said after draining the tea. "There are only two more days until the end of break."

Archie's face scrunched in distress. "I hate this."

She closed the magazine slowly, sensing that he was referring to something more than her mother's persistent badgering. Archie's gaze was on the ceiling, but the pain in his eyes was for something else. Harry reached out to run a hand through Archie's hair, grown out to Rigel's length but not quite as unruly. "Today I realized…we're halfway through."

He turned his head on the covers to blink at her. "Halfway? Huh. That's—" He broke off, unable to articulate what, exactly, it was. After a long moment, he settled for another, "Huh."

"It's strange, I know. When we started this, even though the idea was to make it all seven years, I don't know if I really thought we'd ever get this far," she confessed.

"And now? Do you think we can last another three and a half years?" Archie asked.

"I don't know that we have another option," she said quietly. They'd have to make a dramatic change to get out of the ruse, now. It wouldn't be as simple as switching back. There were too many differences between their personas. A dozen people would realize in the first week that Archie wasn't Rigel and she wasn't Harry. It was a comical thought, almost; their original lives were all but closed to them until school was through. As Archie's face screwed up again, she offered hastily, "If you wanted to give it up, though, I would find a way, Arch."

A hollow-sounding laugh escaped him. "Yeah? What exactly could you do?"

She swallowed. Nothing great came to mind. Rigel was bound by the Unbreakable Vow to finish out the tournament. Until the end of the year, at least, nothing short of actual death would release her from the ruse. Archie could run away somewhere, if Harry faked an illness, a sabbatical of some kind, maybe. She didn't think he'd be happier somewhere other than AIM if he couldn't be himself, though.

"I could pretend to get pregnant," she suggested half-heartedly.

Archie snorted. "That would raise some eyebrows. It would give me an excuse to leave AIM, but I'd just end up back home. Eventually, it would become clear that I wasn't, in fact, pregnant. Or you."

"You could use your morphing to mimic it for a while, though," she said. At his flat look, she grimaced. "I know; it's a bad idea. You'd have to pretend until I got home for the summer."

He ran a hand over his face and nodded tiredly. "It's just as well," he said on a sigh. "Hermione is coming back to AIM now that her part in the tournament is over. I'd rather be where she is."

"How is Hermione?" she asked. She'd grown rather fond of the girl in the few months they'd interacted. Harry loved her Hogwarts friends, but none of them really understood or even bothered to notice the inequality and injustice beyond the world that cocooned them.

"She wanted me to tell you she hasn't given up on the Fade. You'll probably get letters every week. Also, she's hoping you or Delacour win the tournament," Archie told her.

Her head tilted. "Not Jacob Owens?"

Archie smirked. "She thinks he's a disgrace to muggleborns everywhere. I believe she called him a 'blood-narrative-swallowing, party-line-regurgitating collaborator.'" He sighed in admiration. "Hermione is so uncompromisingly principled."

Harry tried not to let the sympathy show too strongly on her face. Archie had it bad. The way he'd lost his good sense at the Yule Ball was proof enough that time away from the brilliant brown-eyed girl hadn't dimmed the torch he carried a whit. What would he do when they inevitably did have to switch back? Would he feel free to woo her as himself, or would it be too late by then? Given the way Hermione had felt comfortable confiding in Rigel about her conflicting feelings for Harry, she had to wonder if she hadn't inadvertently put Archie-as-himself firmly in the friend category before he'd even had a chance.

"I'll be fine at AIM," Archie eventually said into the silence between them. "Like you said, we're already halfway done. It doesn't make sense to quit now. How are you, though?"

She frowned. "I'll be better when this tournament is over. If I never see Riddle's face again, it'll be too soon." She hesitated before saying anything further, but Archie knew her too well to be fooled by the blank expression on her face.

"What is it?" he asked.

"I think there's something shady going on in the lower alleys."

"What else is new?"

She shook her head. "Not the usual stuff. The other day I heard the name…Voldemort."

Archie gaped at her, then sat up and rounded on her fully. "The diary construct? And you're just now telling me this?" His face closed in concerned worry and he chewed on his lip. "What are we going to do?"

She hitched her mouth in a weak grimace. The truth was, she didn't know whether there was anything they could do. "I sent an anonymous tip to Dad's office, but the vow I made to Riddle after second year prevents me from saying too much." Aside from Ginny, Archie was the only exception from the vow; she'd told him everything before the Malfoys' garden party, and hadn't considered it misleading since Riddle was under the impression that Arcturus Black knew in any case.

What Archie didn't know, what she wasn't certain how to explain, was that she was also bound by the thief's code. She couldn't betray anyone who pledged to the Court of Rogues to the Ministry; the trouble was, she didn't know all of the people that entailed. It seemed unlikely that Crouch, Jr. would be paying tithe in the Lower Alleys, but until she could catch Leo long enough to ask him, Harry couldn't be sure. "I wrote there was an aspiring Dark Lord gathering followers in the alleys. Maybe that'll be enough to catch one of the recruiters, and one could lead to more."

It might be wishful thinking. How could the Aurors find one shady bloke in a hub for shady blokes?

"You said before that it might come after you, if it survived," Archie reminded her.

She inclined her head grimly. "I haven't spent much time in the alleys since I heard that name. At Hogwarts, I'll be safe. Next summer, though, you'll have to start being very careful. After all, it's really Rigel Black the thing has a grudge against, not Harry Potter. Sorry," she added.

Archie waved her off. "You can't take responsibility for the actions of every psychopath in your life, Harry." After a moment of contemplation, he added, "It's kind of messed up that there are enough of those to warrant a blanket rule, actually." He sank back into the covers again and stared at the ceiling with furrowed brows. "Closest fire to the house is the tournament," he murmured. "Once you extinguish that one, we can worry about the next."

Harry tentatively agreed, though privately she suspected Riddle's ambitious amalgamation of warped magic and teenage angst would prove to be the larger firestorm in the long run. A tournament she could handle.

The train rattled comfortably along beneath her feet, its steady sprint across the countryside at once familiar and soothing. Students in her year group called her name in greeting as she walked down the central corridor. Younger ones waved or stared shyly and upperclassmen gave her friendly nods. Rigel tried to return the acknowledgements casually, but she knew her cheeks carried flags of color to announce her embarrassment to any who looked too closely.

She marveled at the difference between this train ride and the first, three and a half years before, which she'd spent with her chin tucked into her collar, convinced that anyone who glanced at her profile would immediately discover her secret.

Her friends chorused in pleasure when she slid the compartment door open, and Theo jumped up with Millicent to help her hoist her trunk into the overhead rack. Draco took the book out of the seat they'd saved between him and Pansy, and Rigel sank into a feeling of utter belonging so pure it could only have been distilled from years of true companionship.

"How was everyone's break?" she asked, unable to help the contented smile on her lips.

"We've already been through our holidays," Theo said, waving a hand dramatically. "Tell us about yours instead."

Rigel shrugged. "Mine was quiet. Spent time with the family and just relaxed."

"How is your cousin?" Pansy asked. She had a round of embroidery in her lap, and Rigel eyed it curiously before answering.

"Harry is fine. And Addy is as tall as my knee, if you meant her. She even talks a bit. What are you making, Pan?"

Pansy dropped her eyes to the burgeoning design. "I think it's a heart. Or an onion." She sighed. "Mother wants me to pursue a few feminine hobbies, to impress the suitors. I'm to charm it into a throw pillow after I finish, but I'm told the most gentleladies complete the actual embroidery by hand first."

"What a waste of time," Draco said, flicking his eyes sharply to the side in the way that indicated he was trying not to roll them completely.

"It was either this or knitting," Pansy said with a moue of displeasure.

Theo guffawed. "Does Lady Parkinson think suitors want women well-suited to grandmotherhood? Put it away—she won't know. I got a new set of Exploding Snap cards for Yule." He pulled out the shiny pack and tossed it invitingly up and down in his hand.

Clearly tempted, Pansy slipped her needle into the edges of the round and said, "Don't anyone tell her I neglected it."

"You should just bribe a younger student to do it for you," Millicent said. She pulled the fold-up table out of the side of the compartment and opened the flaps. "That Greengrass chit sews in the common room sometimes."

"Astoria?" Pansy gave up pretending to clutch the embroidery and propped it in the windowsill. "I think she needlepoints."

"Same thing," Millicent muttered.

Theo set up the first game. "Blaise, you playing?"

The quiet dark-skinned boy looked up for the first time from his notebook. "No, thank you. I'm working on a puzzle my mother set me over break."

Millicent glanced over at the notes he'd scribbled and said, "Runes? Don't you get enough of that at school?"

"This is more interesting than the problems Professor Sinistra assigns." To soften the subtle brag, Blaise added, "It's not tailored to whatever concept we're covering in the textbook, at least."

Pansy made a noise of interest. "I know what you mean, Blaise. Sometimes I wonder whether I'm learning anything beyond how to be a good student of magic. The practicality of real life rarely fits so neatly in a framework of concepts, does it?"

"Application is key," Blaise agreed distractedly.

Seeing that he was too invested in his puzzle to carry the conversation further, Pansy let him be. "Rigel, are you playing?"

She hadn't played in months. "Sure, deal me in," Rigel said, pulling out her wand.

The game began, and Rigel let herself relax into it. All five of them were fairly skilled, so it was several rounds of matches before any of the cards reached the danger zone. Theo shuffled faster, trying to get a match before Wendelin the Weird started smoking.

"Come on, come on," Draco muttered, chin propped in his hand and foot bouncing restlessly.

Millicent's wand darted forward, but it was for a different set of matches, and Wendelin begin to tremor. Pansy let out a nervous noise as she made an aborted forward movement—it was only Wronski, though, not a match.

The explosion was inevitable, and should have produced nothing but a harmless flinch from the lot of them. Something about the tense atmosphere had seeped into Rigel unconsciously without her realizing it, however. When the card swelled with power preparing to burst, her magic flooded it instinctually, instantly duding the impending explosion.

Anticipation whooshed out of the room like air from a punctured balloon as her friends stared at her incredulously. Theo poked the now dormant card and frowned. "You broke it. That's cheating, Rigel."

She looked down at her wand sitting innocently in her lap, as though she could blame the sensitive tool for her magic's actions. "My bad," she said.

They gathered the cards so Theo could deal again, but nervous energy had taken root in Rigel's blood. Every time a card flared with magic she had to tamp down on her own to keep it from lashing out and ruining the game. After the third time she wasn't fast enough to stop the unconscious reaction consciously, Theo put away the deck with a shake of his head. "Your reflexes are monstrous," he said, half admonishing and half admiring. "Don't tell me you're going to be this high-strung forever."

Rigel grimaced. She'd thought she was very relaxed. Perhaps she had forgotten what true relaxation even felt like, after so much time spent on near-constant alert. "Sorry," she said again.

"Don't apologize," Draco said quietly. "Those reflexes have saved you from a number of injuries this year. Keep them sharp. We can always play again when this is all over."

She smiled weakly, hoping he was right; she wanted to look forward to a normal that was possible to get back to.

"Cheer up, Rigel," Millicent said bracingly. "You look like a glum ghost."

She made a face, and Pansy said, "He looks more like a put-out poltergeist."

Sensing a challenge, the others were quick to join in. "A sad specter," Theo suggested.

"An abject apparition."

"A sorrowful spirit."

"A forlorn phantom," Draco tried.

"That isn't a true alliteration," Rigel pointed out.

"You come up with one for phantom, then." Her friend huffed.

"A…pitiful phantom?" she wrinkled her nose. "Well, that was a bad noun pick. How about 'gloomy ghoul'?"

"A miserable manifestation," Millicent said, a proud grin tucked into her cheek.

"A wretched wraith," Pansy countered.

"Ooh, good one," Theo said. He stuck his tongue between his teeth, then offered, "A sorry shade."

"A sour spook."

"A…something phantasm," Draco muttered, clicking his tongue in annoyance when he couldn't come up with anything.

"Why do you pick the hardest ones?" Pansy asked, laughing

The blond boy threw up his hands. "There's nothing else left!"

"Soul, presence, shadow—"

"Shut up, Blaise."

Blaise, who had evidently not been so wrapped up in his work as they assumed, smiled slyly. "It appears the long winter break has softened your mind, Draco."

"I'll soften your face," Draco threatened halfheartedly. Blaise had already turned back to his notebook.

Rigel just smiled, watching them all interact so freely. She'd missed her friends, despite wanting nothing more at the end of term than to get away from everything.

Millicent ruined the moment by asking, "What have you deduced about the fourth task so far?"

She blinked at the other girl. "I haven't thought about it at all. Bagman and Crouch said we won't find out until a few days beforehand."

Millicent and Pansy exchanged amused glances. "You can't just wait for information to come to you, Rigel," Pansy said patiently. "Millie and I have been proactive over the break."

"My second cousin is engaged to the niece of the—you don't care." Millicent cut herself off as Rigel's eyes glazed over against her will. "The point is, one of the task creators let it slip that the fourth task is some kind of scavenger hunt. You'll have to find things within a set time limit."

"What sorts of things?" she asked.

"No idea," the dark-haired girl confessed. "But each blood champion is to be assigned a different set of items—you won't be in direct competition, except for the time."

That was somewhat comforting. After the third task, Rigel didn't want to go head-to-head with anyone unless she absolutely had to. She'd been hoping to focus on other things until the task was officially announced. Now, however, she had a responsibility to begin preparation for some sort of retrieval task. Rigel knew Millicent just wanted her to succeed, but part of her wished her friend could have waited a few days before telling her.

All she said was, "Thanks. I appreciate you keeping an ear to the ground for me." At Millicent's knowing look, she added, "Really, I do. I'll brush up on my locating spells this week. Anything on the political front I should know about?"

Her friends tried to politely stifle their expressions, but only Blaise was successful, and it was difficult to tell whether he was even listening any longer.

"You're talking about the marriage law?" Pansy clarified. "It won't be voted on until the end of the spring session. Both sides are ramping up the public information campaigns, in the meantime."

"It helps that the halfblood everybody is talking about right now is gorgeous and utterly unthreatening," Draco said, cynicism in every syllable.

Realizing he meant Delacour, she frowned. Was that the reason Riddle had so carefully ensured the weaker girl would beat out Antiope to the finals? The part-Veela undoubtedly made a more attractive advertisement for marrying halfbloods than the fearsome, uncompromisingly capable Athenai. "Is there any angle Riddle isn't working?" she muttered.

"He seems to be having trouble with yours, actually," Pansy said.

"I've been winning the tournament for him," Rigel disagreed. "Can't get much more 'pureblood supremacy' than that."

Millicent and Theo winced, but it was Blaise who responded. "You could, actually. Of all the participants, you're the one who has been the least vocal in support of the New Triwizard Tournament. It's obvious to anyone watching that you'd rather be anywhere else and you don't agree with the premise. Even the muggleborns are better champions of the spectacle than you."

It wasn't exactly a compliment, but something in Rigel's stomach thrummed in satisfaction.

"It's only obvious to those paying attention to the politics," Theo disagreed. "Most people are watching for the blood and glory."

Millicent reached over to whack the boy upside the head. "Don't tell him that."

Rigel sighed. "I suppose Theo is right, though. Only a few people watching will consider what the tournament really means."

"Those are the only people who matter," Draco said soothingly.

"You only think that because 'those people' include you," Theo muttered. "The common people matter, too. They can start riots and make things difficult for the upper crust."

"They also have thoughts and emotions and valid human experiences," Blaise said dryly.

"Sure, maybe." Theo shrugged. "The point is, disregard their lust for fear and blood at your peril."

"Enough with the blood." Millicent groaned. "You're not helping."

Theo blinked at her. "Helping what? I thought we were just talking."

Draco pinched the bridge of his nose with a low curse and even Pansy sighed. Rigel chuckled. "Let's talk about something else, instead. What else have you all been up to?"

"Theo, why don't you tell Rigel about your winter break?" Draco suggested swiftly. There was an unkind edge to his tone.

The sandy-haired boy's face darkened momentarily. He cleared his throat and said, "There isn't much to tell. Well, Zach and I broke up, but what can you expect with his family dripping a constant stream of poison in his ears? We never had a chance." He gave a dramatic sigh and said, "Think Aldon will let me cry on his shoulder about it this term?"

Rigel let out a surprised laugh. "Rosier?" she asked, incredulous.

Theo waggled his eyebrows at her. "He's fit as anything—don't tell me you haven't noticed."

She grimaced. Somehow, Rosier's looks were always eclipsed by his confounding personality and deliberately obtuse intentions.

"You may have some competition, Theo," Pansy said slowly. "I saw Aldon in a very engrossing discussion with Rigel's cousin at the ball."

Her eyes sharpened. She'd forgotten, but Pansy was right. Archie had been speaking to Rosier for a brief time. "Did you hear what they were talking about?" she asked Pansy.

The blonde girl paused delicately before saying, "I believe it was about the marriage law, actually."

Rigel stared at her. "You're joking."

Pansy gave a helpless lift of her shoulder. "I don't know the whole of it, but…well, is it so surprising? In the current political climate, there's a good chance the law will pass. It's smart to test the waters now. My parents are even looking at a few halfbloods for my own prospects," she admitted. "More and more, the well-positioned ones are going to be seriously considered."

Rigel scowled. "I don't care how smart it is. No one should be considering Harry. She's spoken for."

"After the spectacle she made of her affections for the American muggleborn at the ball, you can't be surprised that people have figured out your engagement isn't in earnest," Millicent said gently. At Rigel's frustrated frown, she shook her head. "Really, you can't protect her forever, Rigel."

"I certainly can," she muttered.

Draco changed the subject abruptly to whether the others had managed to finish their holiday assignments or not, and Rigel let the conversation drift away from her.

Why hadn't Archie mentioned his conversation with Rosier? Had it seemed unimportant to him or had the emotional distraction of being in proximity to Hermione again pushed the interaction to the back burner? She supposed it didn't matter why he hadn't told her. Rigel still had to decide what to do about it.

If Rosier thought he could sweep in like some kind of hero and save Harry from the marriage law, he would shortly be divorced from that idea. She had no intention of entertaining pureblood suitors keen on snapping up the 'well-connected' halfbloods as soon as the law went through. And the law is not going through, she added with a mental growl.

Do you mind keeping your angst to a dull roar?

With an internal jolt, Rigel recognized Dom's voice echoing in her ears. I wasn't talking to you, she thought at him.

You, me, what's the difference? I'm just asking you not to shout down the stars in here.

Sorry, she offered, a bit put out to be apologizing for the thoughts in her own head. It's not as though she enjoyed the fact that he was privy to them.

I heard that.

With a silent snort of amusement, she glanced around the compartment and saw that the others were engaged in a lively debate over the diplomatic effect of the tournament on Magical Britain's foreign relations. Figuring they could do without her for a short while, she settled back into her seat and closed her eyes.

She was by now used to barreling her way through the storm at the edges of her mind. Dom met her in the cozy heart of her mountainscape, a mug of hot cocoa in hand. The marshmallows oscillated weirdly from the bottom of the cup to the top, as though they couldn't decide whether to float or not, but otherwise it was a passable imitation.

"How's your work progressing?" she asked after settling into one of the armchairs by the fireplace.

Dom, garbed in a padded housecoat with matching slippers, put a pipe between his teeth and took a long pull before blowing the smoke out in a thoughtful stream. His bit of theatre complete, he said, "Very well, thank you for inquiring. I've finished with the last portion you gave me."

He pulled a sphere of her magic from his pocket and tossed it toward her. She caught it, though a bit of cocoa dribbled down the side of her cup. Her magic clung to her with a prickling that was almost like static electricity. She squeezed it gently in a sort of one-armed hug, steadfastly ignoring Dom's amused smirk, and, with a thought, sent it zooming back to her space room to join the mass of magic that had already been sifted through. A rough mental catalogue of what remained surprised her.

"You're almost finished," she said, not hiding the relief in her voice. "That's good. I found out he can still perceive the magic, even though it's separated from him. Riddle can identify me without touching my skin if I'm nearby."

Dom raised his eyebrows. "This enemy of yours is more powerful than you've led me to believe."

She stared at him. "I told you, he's the most powerful politician in the country."

"Political power does not always equate to actual power," he said.

"You've seen all my memories of him," she reminded him. "How could you not understand how powerful he is?"

"I've seen him destroy some furniture and let out a bit of power to intimidate a thirteen-year-old," Dom corrected her. "This is…something else. How far away can he perceive the bit of magic in you?"

"I haven't extensively tested it," she said stiffly.

"You should."

She shook her head. "No point. As soon as you've gathered it all, I'm going to get rid of it."

He frowned. "Are you sure that's wise? We may be able to find a better use for it. Releasing it into the world would just allow it to flow back to him. What if you could reverse his intention and use this magic to track the rest of him instead?"

"I'd rather be rid of it. Wait, what do you mean 'flow back to him'? Wouldn't it just dissipate into the universe?"

Dom tapped his pipe on the edge of his armchair slowly. "Not necessarily. If he has such a strong connection to his magic that it remains identifiable as his even after intermingling with yours, and if he were close enough when you released it, there's a chance it would find its way back to him. The lesser part will always be attracted to the whole."

She thought about the way the pieces of her magic she separated from her own core required a stern inflection of will to keep from fusing back together within her mindscape. "Is that true for all magic? Can it come back after being cast if the original core is close enough?"

"If the magic can cause noticeable resonance at a short distance, then it retains the intrinsic qualities that make it yours. Such magic can be reabsorbed. Do your potions cause resonance when you hold them?" Dom asked rhetorically.

"No." That would have been hard to miss.

"Spells are much the same," he said, nodding. "Once you force your magic into such a shape, it loses the ability to meld back into your core smoothly. You could unravel the shape, I suppose, and something in the magic that remains might be recognizably yours once more, but it would require a great deal of effort. Have you ever seen a magical work unraveled?"

"I don't think so. It's not a usual application, though." Nothing like it had ever been mentioned in any of her reading or classes, at least.

"Nothing about this is usual," Dom said, waving his pipe for emphasis. "Don't bind yourself to the limits others accept without question. You're finally almost free of this interloper's influence. It's time to explore your magic's true nature."

She frowned. "What do you mean? Has it calmed down without Riddle's magic?" She hadn't noticed any significant difference since Dom began the filtration process, but she could always hope.

He tilted his head consideringly. "I wouldn't say it's calmer, exactly. Your magic will never be entirely tame, dear. It does seem noticeably nicer, however: also younger, more impetuous. Like a wild horse—but without the burr in its blanket." He smiled wide and slow. "Perhaps it's time to try a full gallop."

"If only I had somewhere to gallop to," she said drolly.

Dom shrugged, artful indifference that she didn't believe for a moment. "One day you will, and I'll be ready with your tack and saddle."

Rigel set aside her cocoa and stood with a sigh. "The delusions of grandeur are my cue to go."

"Can't buck your destiny forever," he said calmly.

She shoved the mental equivalent of an eye roll at him and retreated from the inner recesses of her mind. Rigel might be grateful to him for maintaining the different levels of her mind and combing Riddle's magic out of her core, but that didn't mean she had to humor his unsolicited ambitions.

The sun took its long, slow dive into the horizon and the train settled with a groaning sigh at the Hogsmeade platform. Students poured from the contraption like rats from a sinking ship. Rigel made her way with the others toward the carriages, but before she could follow Pansy and Draco into one, her elbows were captured in twin traps that spun her in a circle.

"Puppy!"

"You're riding with us."

Rigel sent her friends an apologetic smile, and it was a testament to dozens of of similar situations that they merely waved her off with promises to save her a seat at the feast.

Fred and George towed her to the next carriage along the line and opened the door—only to find it occupied.

"Eet is you." Fleur Delacour sat on the left bench, Beauxbatons uniform perfectly pressed and hands folded demurely in her lap.

"Our apologies, milady," Fred said with a flourishing bow.

George copied him, adding, "We had no inkling this conveyance was spoken for."

Delacour tilted her chin at the empty seats. "We are all going to ze castle, no?"

The twins exchanged several sentences in a glance, then grinned.

"To the lady's insistence—"

"—we defer."

Rigel found herself boosted unnecessarily into the carriage and took the seat next to Delacour with what little dignity she could scrounge after the twins' manhandling.

"How was your holiday, Delacour?" she asked politely.

"Not too different from yours, I daresay," Delacour said with a pretty shrug. "Always questions about ze tournament. At least I got to see my sister."

Rigel nodded. "I know what you mean. It seems we won't really escape it until this year is over."

Delacour sent her a hard-to-read look beneath her silvery lashes. "Someone will not escape it even zen."

A pang hit her stomach. She kept forgetting the purported 'grand prize.' Rigel was prevented from further comment by the slamming of the carriage door and the rocking jolt that came as the thestral shot forward.

"So, to business," George said, clapping his hands briskly.

Fred nodded along solemnly. "As your official PR reps, we've been considering how to help your public image bounce back from the hit it took during the third task."

"Honestly, Rigel, blood magic?" George's face said plainly that he thought better of her.

Rigel grimaced. "Well…yeah." At the time, it had seemed inspired. In retrospect, she perhaps should have put stricter limits on herself prior to stepping into the ring.

Fred reached over to pat her knee gently. "Not to worry, Pup, we have a plan."

"Winning hearts and minds—"

"Projecting an image of youth and innocence—"

"It's all very simple, really."

"Really." Rigel offered a skeptical look.

The twins grinned unabashed. "Pranks," they chorused.

She raised an eyebrow. "Are you sure that isn't your innate prankster bias talking?"

George looked offended. "I'm sure we wouldn't know if it was."

"Clearly there's no way we could, and therefore we can only proceed with perfect clarity," Fred assured her.

"Pranks?" Delacour moved her eyes between the three of them incredulously. "'e 'as a tournament to focus on."

Fred smiled reassuringly, and it was not at all reassuring. "This is directly related. Tournament scores are irrelevant if no one wants you to win."

"Public support will influence the judges," George added hastily as Delacour looked ready to argue. "Amazing that the three finalists are all good looking, well-spoken, and entertaining to watch, isn't it?"

"Not at all, Gred."

"Quite right, Forge."

Delacour's scowl melted away and thoughtfulness replaced it. "Antiope should 'ave advanced," she admitted quietly. "Eef she 'ad been more charming, zey may 'ave put her in a different spot for ze duels."

"People enjoy cheering for those they admire on a personal level even more than the players that are simply good at the game." George concluded. The expression on his face was gentle, but it clearly communicated that he agreed with Delacour's assessment of the third task.

"So you see," Fred said earnestly, "It's really, positively vital that you take our advice."

"For the sake of your reputation—"

"—your popularity—"

"—and your viability in the tournament as a whole."

Rigel wasn't convinced. "How would pulling a conspicuous prank make people admire me?" she asked. "If Delacour's reaction is standard, then most people will take it as a sign of arrogance that I do anything other than prepare seriously for the tasks ahead."

The redheads traded pitying looks. George shook his head. "Rigel, Rigel, Rigel. What is the fastest way to a man's heart?"

"Between the fourth and fifth ribs," she drawled.

Fred wagged a finger at her. "None of that! And no more blood magic. We're going for charming-and-kind-hearted Rigel, not mop-the-stage-with-the-boy-who-hurt-his-friend Rigel."

"We're sort of a package deal," she said, amused.

George waved a hand unconcernedly. "People can only see one side of things at a time; so, let's show them your fun side."

"And the answer to my esteemed colleague's question was food, Rigel. Food is the fastest way to a man's heart," Fred clarified.

"My mistake." She smiled sweetly.

"We should have rescued Puppy from Slytherin before things got this bad," George confided in his brother's ear.

"If he refuses the prank, we'll know for sure he's going Dark."

Rigel scowled. "Let's hear it then, wise masters of publicity."

"Doctorates, actually," Fred said, almost absently.

Delacour muffled a chuckle, but Rigel didn't give them the satisfaction. After all this build-up, it had better be a pretty terrific prank.

George cleared his throat. Fred produced a detailed blueprint of the Great Hall and the kitchens beneath. They explained. Rigel's eyes narrowed, then grew wide. Delacour hid an admiring sigh behind one delicate hand. In the end, there was only one thing she could say.

"The Marauders are going to be erased from the annals of history. Doctors Weasley have ascended."

Settling back into an academic routine felt like trying to fit into a coat she'd nearly outgrown. After the relative freedom of study the break offered, forcing her attention to the topics her professors required was difficult. The only exception was her lessons with Snape. Rigel fell back into freebrewing as easily as fish slipped into a stream.

As their evening lessons progressed, Rigel became more decisive. She got faster at choosing ingredient combinations and orders, but was also quicker to make mistakes as a result. Each mistake taught her more than following a dozen recipes correctly ever could have; knowing what reactions were intellectually likely and watching them unfold in real time were very different levels of knowledge. Sometimes she could counteract the problem as it unfolded, but other times she realized too late what she ought to have done sooner. That, too, was a valuable kind of learning.

Her protective apron was still pristine, something that at turns fascinated and frustrated her Head of House. He seemed to take some amused affront at the unstained garment, but it was hardly Rigel's fault. A dirty apron might be the sign of a daring innovator, but her magic reacted too swiftly to allow any impending explosions to gain steam.

When another night passed and Rigel hung her spotless protective gear on its hook once more, Snape gave a wry twist of his lips as he commented, "If ever your effects hang in the National Potions Archive, no one will ever believe their authenticity."

"Proof of my preeminence will fade into legend, but you and I will always know the truth." She grinned.

Snape met her grin with a sneer. "Pray your mythology remains as unstained as your apron."

"What cynicism," she said, fighting a laugh. "I suppose I should follow your example and preemptively sour my own reputation, is that it?"

Surprised offense looked out at her from his dark eyes. "My reputation is beyond reproach in our community."

Silently savoring the phrase 'our community,' Rigel clarified. "Your professional reputation is immaculate, true, but a man's mythology is more than just his work alone. People are just as fascinated and intimidated by your personal character, sir." For the most part, she was joking; it was fun to see the unflappable Potions Master flustered for a change. "I've always wondered, did you deliberately cultivate the aura of mysterious genius or does is come naturally?"

"What rubbish," the man muttered, a dark scowl deeply at home on his face.

"My theory has been that it is mostly natural, but that you also happen to enjoy thwarting the shallow curiosity of the fickle masses at every turn," she continued blithely.

Her mentor snorted. "Now who's cynical?"

"I learn from the best," Rigel agreed.

"And yet I've apparently neglected to teach you when to shut your mouth." His words came out on a growl, but she could tell by the dismissive way he shooed her out the door that he wasn't truly upset. "Get out of here before I remember my original impulse to pickle your organs and be done with it."

She turned back with a frown. "Wait, when did you—?" The door shut firmly in her face. She clucked her tongue doubtfully. "Human organs aren't even that useful," she muttered as she began the winding walk back toward the common room. "He'd probably just put them on display to intimidate first-years."

She fell silent as she walked, mentally cataloguing the things she still had to do that week. Out of the silence there came the steady click of expensive shoes on stone floors, and as she merged with the main corridor that led from the stairs, she crossed paths with Rookwood and Rosier.

By the way Rosier's step faltered slightly at her appearance, Rigel guessed she hadn't imagined how he'd been avoiding her since the beginning of term. Her eyes narrowed. "Evening, gentlemen."

"Rigel." Rookwood inclined his head politely. "How fortuitous our paths should meet."

"Yes, what are the odds?" Rosier drawled, giving his best friend a measuring look.

"I believe Pansy mentioned you'd been looking for us?" Rookwood continued evenly. In step with the older boys now, Rigel could see the mischief glinting in the tall upperclassman's eyes.

She smiled, a small, sharp thing. "It was really Aldon I wanted to speak with."

"You don't say?" Rookwood made a noise of contemplation like a mountain shifting its weight. "Well, why don't I leave you to it?" As he lengthened his stride and easily pulled ahead of them, Rigel reflected that he must always be slowing his gait to keep pace with Rosier.

Rosier mouthed the word 'traitor' to his friend's receding back, but turned with an attempt at charm to say, "Rigel! It's been too long. I trust you aren't finding the new year too arduous?"

"Not as yet," she said mildly. "You know how it is, though. One little inconvenience can snowball when you least expect it. I find it best to deal with small problems before they become larger, don't you?"

"Ah, well, it depends," Rosier said. He cleared his throat and offered a wry smile. "If the snowball rolls down the hill and into your neighbor's yard, you don't have to deal with it at all, do you?"

Rigel tilted her head, the sharp smile never faltering. "I've never been the type to let other people handle problems I am capable of squashing myself."

The golden-eyed boy winced, and his lips silently repeated 'squashing' with an uneasy glance at her expression. Rigel wondered with a morbid kind of self-recrimination whether he was remembering her rather violent showing in the third task. It disturbed her to think that people who once condescended to her might now be a little bit afraid of what she could do, but in that moment, she was willing to use whatever tactic worked.

To her mild surprise, Rosier collected himself with a slow roll of his shoulders and paced to the edge of the corridor, where he could lean against the hard stone and cross his arms. Despite the defensive regrouping, he met her gaze squarely as she followed him over. When she was close enough that neither had to raise their voices above a low murmur, he said, "This is about your cousin, yes?"

Glad to be done dancing around it, Rigel nodded. "I want you to stay away from her."

Rosier's eyebrows rose at her blunt declaration. After a slow blink, he said, "Respectfully, Rigel, shouldn't that be her decision?"

"What did she say at the ball, then?" she asked, a knowing tone in her voice. "Did she seem at all interested in your proposal?"

Astonishment crept into his bright eyes, followed by a flicker of understanding that he seemed to seize upon. A grin tugged at his mouth and he said, "She didn't tell you? Did you have to hear about it from Pansy?"

Rigel's annoyance spiked at his smug amusement. "I honestly doubt Harry considered your conversation worth mentioning."

That wiped the humor from Rosier's face. "How interesting that you considered it worth stalking me for, then."

"My cousin can be a bit naïve," she said easily. "While I don't doubt she dismissed your attentions out of hand, she doesn't know how persistent you can be, Aldon. So here we are. Regardless of how your conversation went, I'm telling you now to leave Harry alone."

Rosier tilted his head back and stared at the torchlight as it played across the ceiling. "Don't you even want to know what we spoke of, first?"

"Not particularly," Rigel said honestly. She could imagine well enough Rosier's enigmatic overtures and Archie's bemused unconcern.

"Why so hostile?" Rosier complained. "I thought you'd be glad."

"You thought I'd be glad, so you avoided me for two weeks?"

His gaze flicked down to meet hers guiltily. "Well, Pansy may have warned me after your outburst on the train."

Outburst? Rigel rolled her eyes. Why did everyone act like she was crazy for wanting to keep 'Harry' out of their calculations?

Rosier grimaced. "I really didn't mean to upset you, Rigel. You know I value our friendship." He lifted a hand as though he would make a gesture, but then let it go limp at his side again. "Listen, Rookwood and I heard about the law going through committee, same as everyone else. My parents are better connected than most, however, and significantly worse at keeping secrets." He took a slow breath, as though preparing to do something he knew he'd regret. "What they told me, what no one else will be saying out loud yet, is that matches between Party purebloods and halfbloods are not going to be left to chance."

She stared at him, startled, for the moment, out of her anger. "What does that mean?"

"There is an Arithmancy algorithm," he said quietly, his voice nearly a whisper. "Lord Riddle has been working on it for some time. My parents say he will match the scions of the old families to optimum candidates. They didn't understand it well enough to explain everything, but their impression is that Lord Riddle can calculate which matches will result in the most powerful offspring. The older a line is, the more important it is that they conform to his plans. Do you understand, Rigel?"

Rigel felt herself shake her head slowly. Her mind was reeling. She'd already figured out Riddle's law was at least partly an attempt to slow the declining Dark wizard population. That he had gone so far as to plan exact marriages between actual children should not have surprised her, but somehow the fresh reminder of the man's pathological need for absolute control hit her like a bucket of cold water.

"That…crazy mind-buggering bastard," she hissed when words came back to her at last. A wordless growl escaped her before she tamped down on the pure fury boiling in her veins and snapped her attention back to the concern at hand. "But no, I don't understand. Harry isn't in the Party and she isn't a pureblood. He can't control who she marries. So why are you dragging her into this?"

Rosier's expression moved through genuine confusion, then realization, and settled on pity. "Rigel, you brought her into this. It's not her prospects Riddle will want to control. It's—"

"Me." Rigel closed her eyes as the truth swooped down on her. "The Blacks are one of the oldest lines. Of course he's thought up an 'optimum candidate' for me. It's not Harry, I take it?"

Rosier shrugged helplessly. "I don't know who, but you have to admit…the odds of it being her, out of everyone, are low. I know you won't let Riddle dictate something like that without a fight," he added before she could assert just that. "He's outmaneuvered you before, though." The words were said gently, but Rigel felt them like a slap.

She ran a hand through her hair and took a shaky breath. An algorithm. How was she supposed to predict something like that? "After this year, he has no hold on me," she said. She tried to believe it, as though a strong enough conviction could make it so.

"I hope you're right," Rosier said. "If you're wrong, though…your cousin should have back-up options. Just in case. If you're forced to break your betrothal when you come of age, it won't take long before someone else tries to take advantage."

So that was it. Or at least, that was what Rosier had decided to tell her. Rigel huffed out a frustrated grunt. "I get what you're trying to do. It's not your responsibility, though."

"Why is it so hard for you to accept a little help?" Rosier snapped. "Rigel, you can't spin the world by yourself. You can't be everywhere and fix every outcome. If I want to do this for you, and for her, why can't you just let me?" The irritation faded and a hint of uncertainty crept into his voice as he added, "Do you think me such a bad option? You think I can't protect her?"

Rigel scowled lightly. She wasn't going to let him twist this around on her. "I don't see why you'd want to, Aldon. You've met her, what, once?" She shook her head. "I'd understand if a stranger tried this. Lots of people might assume they could influence the House of Black through Harry, or get in my good graces by 'protecting' her. You know me, though, and you know her, albeit a little. You know she isn't really as influential as her friendship with me makes it seem. She's not in such immediate danger that someone needs to sacrifice themselves to save her, and she's not so useful to you to make her worth that gesture absent a pressing need. So why?"

Rosier's stare was back, only this time it was reproachful. "Careful, Rigel, or you'll start believing your own publicity."

She frowned. "What is that supposed to mean?"

"Have you forgotten your cousin has accomplishments in her own right?"

"I haven't," she protested. "Most wouldn't see an academic career as an asset in a woman, though."

Rosier sighed. "I didn't mean for this to be so confusing for you," he said, softly sardonic. "Is it so hard to credit that I've a genuine interest in her?"

Saying 'yes' would be churlish, but what did it say that he only mentioned the hypothetical possibility that he'd be interested in Harry herself after exhausting other routes of convincing her?

"Of all the halfbloods I've met, she's the most interesting," he said after a moment. Something uncomfortable rippled in his golden gaze, and Rigel supposed it might have cost him to admit to a personal curiosity toward Harry. While she doubted he'd met many halfbloods, she could admit wryly that 'interesting' was about the most complimentary thing he ever said about another person.

This is so messed up, she thought. Unbidden, a memory of what he'd said to her before the tournament started floated up from the depths of her mind. The things we do because we want to will always outweigh those we do because we have to.

All of a sudden, she was tired. "What did she say, then. When you asked her about it?"

Rosier's eyes widened, and a cautious hope she didn't want to see surfaced in them. "She babbled something vague and noncommittal and ran away, actually. Sometimes, the two of you are really alike, you know?" Rigel grimaced at that, but didn't contradict him. Rosier cleared his throat and said, "So, do I have your permission to court her?"

"You need her permission, not mine," she said begrudgingly.

"Could have fooled me."

She wrinkled her nose. "Well, originally I thought you were doing something weird." He gave her an offended look, but she brushed past it to add, "Ask her as many times as you want. Just don't expect her to go along with it. She only reluctantly agreed to our betrothal in the first place. Once she's of age, even if we break the betrothal, I wouldn't expect her to accept another one. Harry has no intention of marrying anyone, law or no."

"Well, that's not entirely true," he corrected her. "She seemed very interested in marrying Miss Granger. Only the new law wouldn't let her, would it?"

Rigel flushed involuntarily. Archie really had made a spectacle of his emotions. Being in America had dissolved what little subtlety her cousin may once have possessed. "She'll grow of out that, I think," Rigel muttered.

"Either way, she'll have options," Rosier said firmly. "That's all I wanted."

Somehow, despite all the explanations and assertions that had just passed between them, Rigel still wasn't sure she believed him.

As Millicent sat down at the lunch table, the surrounding Slytherins automatically slid down to make room for her persistent companion.

"Good day to everyone," Tahiil said cheerfully to the general assembly. The colorfully clad boy had a new accessory—a black-and-gold striped tie that he wore proudly, much to Millicent's chagrin.

"Hello, Tahiil," Pansy said with a genuine smile. She liked the Majeerteen muggleborn, and Rigel suspected part of it was his undimmable happiness. "How is your family settling in?"

Tahiil had received special dispensation from the Headmaster to remain at Hogwarts for the rest of the year. While Dumbledore could not offer him a true scholarship or actual credits, due to his being muggleborn, he had managed to secure the boy's place there for a few months longer with the argument that the Board of Governors had already approved the attendance of each of the competitors for up to a full year. After all, when the tournament began it was unknown which of the nine would be continuing for a second term.

None of the other runners-up had elected to remain, but Owens' girlfriend, who was evidently heiress to a prominent American pureblood family, had arranged to stay on as an exchange student for a term to support him. Tahiil had embraced the opportunity with gusto. As the boy pointed out, it wasn't as though he had a school to go back to. He hadn't been officially Sorted, but sometime in the first week of the new term the House of Badgers had unanimously adopted him. Despite his enthusiastic participation in Hufflepuff class sections, however, it was Millicent he chose to spend most meals with.

"Very well, thank you," Tahiil said with a contented grin. "The most generous Headmaster has gifted my mother and brother with stones just like mine," he revealed, moving the hand that was not piling food on his plate to touch the orange necklace with its embedded Translation Charm. "They like this funny-named village very much. Each day I bring them something different to eat from the castle. My brother is most anxious to know what I learn of wand-focused magics. I think I will try to make him one."

"Make a wand? That's difficult work, especially if you want it to work right," Theo said. "Just buy one."

"The gold I was given for entering the tournament has brought much ease to my family, but I do not think the expense of a wand would be justified, as he can also get along without one," Tahiil said. He shrugged. "Still, it would bring him joy to have even a poorly made one."

"Is your brother as good at wandless magic as you are?" Draco asked.

"Of course," Tahiil says proudly. "He showed his ability much sooner than I did. The elders began teaching him at only three."

The Slytherins in earshot, most of whom had been afforded a good amount of pre-Hogwarts magical education, were nevertheless suitably impressed by the idea of beginning training so young.

"Is he an Animagus, too?"

Tahiil shook his head ruefully. "My brother has found his inner animal, but he has not yet connected with it."

"What do you mean?" Rigel asked. She was no closer to achieving the proper transformation than she had been over the break. Perhaps Tahiil had some insight from his training that could help.

Tahiil considered the question carefully as he chewed through a spiced potato. "It is not enough to know which animal is within your soul. Many people can reach that realization. You cannot become the animal until you are the animal." Seeing the blank looks around him, he struggled to articulate his point. "For some, it can be hard to admit that the animal is not merely a part of you; it is you. The good and the bad. Unless you can accept the core impulses of that animal as your own, you will never achieve the transformation. It is not lack of magical ability that prevents you; it is lack of self-knowledge or unwillingness to accept the uncomfortable truths that the animal reveals about your soul."

Rigel considered that quietly as she finished her meal. What were the 'core impulses' of a raven? Curiosity? Cleverness? She had no trouble identifying with that. She must be missing something deeper.

After the meal, she made her way to the library. In the now-familiar stacks containing books on rituals, she found World Symbology Anthology and hefted it over to a table to flip through. The 'raven' entry wasn't the longest, but neither was it brief. Certain phrases jumped out at her.

A bird of clear-thought and memory, evoking insight and prophecy…Mischievous and curious, the raven is both messenger and trouble-maker…A raven is selfish—opportunistic, cunning, and hungry, it takes what it can from the world…Commonly associated with lost souls, the black bird can signal transmutation and rebirth...Secret-keepers, thieves, protectors, providers—

She shut the book with an annoyed sigh. How was any of that supposed to be helpful? She suspected an animal could be assigned any meaning a person wanted to see in it. None of the human-created associations would tell her what impulses the animal itself might identify with, however. Perhaps she'd have better luck with her animal biology texts.

The descriptions afforded to ravens in the biological sense were easier to reconcile, she found.

Predator and scavenger as needed, adaptable to different environments, fast-learning, acrobatic flyers, cooperative, social, and familial—she was particularly keen to discover that unlike other, more competitive species, older raven siblings helped defend the nest to protect the chicks while the parents were away. That was a sentiment she could identify with easily.

None of the information she compiled on ravens seemed to be easing the transformation, however. Try as she might, no amount of magic circulating through her veins was enough to trigger the Transfiguration. The book Sirius had directed them to made it very clear that manually transforming oneself a piece at a time into the animal would not work—likely, it would kill a person instead. She could not force it. Rather, she was supposed to meditate until she reached a 'stage of enlightenment' in which the 'animal emerged naturally' from the soul.

It frustrated Rigel no end. All her understanding of Transfiguration was secondary; what mattered was achieving some sort of wooly mutual understanding between her conscious mind and the animal beneath it. How she was supposed to do that with no way to communicate with the animal in the meantime, Rigel didn't know.

In the quiet hours stolen in her private laboratory, Rigel divided her time between slowly perfecting the medical potions for her shaped-imbued first-aid kit and testing the theory she'd come up with while talking with Dom on the train.

If a piece of magic retained the ability to resonate with the core, then it could be reabsorbed by it. That was what Dom asserted, and she grudgingly admitted he'd probably been around long enough to know. Never before had she spent so much time contemplating the nature of magic. There was wild magic—the natural magic that existed, unbound, in all things. When it collected in certain stones, animals, plants, and people, wild magic took on properties that were determined in turn by the characteristics of the thing it was shaped by. Magical beings were the only species known to have conscious control over the magic within them. Rigel had to recognize, however, that even wizards did not fully appreciate which aspects of their magic they could and could not affect.

Rigel could shape her raw magic into spells, molding it into manifesting in a myriad of different ways. She could not, however, change the way her raw magic itself was shaped by its very inhabitance within her. She had learned in her first year that every witch or wizard had unique aspects to their magic. Cores formed differently, unconsciously molded to suit the individual. Inherited magic could tend Darker or Lighter depending on generations of subtle efforts to shape it through genetics. Finally, every being with magic had their own individual signature: miniscule variations in output that were largely undetectable at the macro-level. Like radio waves, each supported a unique frequency, only compounded by a modulation algorithm that existed somewhere deep in a person's soul.

Something about that unique signature became warped when a wizard consciously shaped their magic into a spell. To a casual observer, every levitation charm looked and felt the same, no matter who originally cast it. Even the Weasley twins, both adept at reading and mimicking auras, probably couldn't read the fingerprint off a spell once it had already been cast. She'd heard that Aurors could track the traces of a wizard's signature with enough time and sample size, but casting evidently changed the signature enough that it was an extremely difficult art. It was easier to track a wizard's wand instead, which kept echoes of spells cast for quite some time afterwards.

Once it was shaped, it wouldn't resonate with the original core any longer. Rigel had to wonder whether, if a person could emit raw, unshaped magic and trap it into something neutral, that same person would be able to reabsorb the magic at leisure. As long as it was never shaped, the signature should remain constant.

After all, wasn't that how blood magic worked? The magic within a person's blood was utterly raw—unshaped. When you put blood into something, weren't you really just imbuing it with your unshaped magical signature? The blood itself was symbolic but superfluous. In fact, she thought with a touch of irony, if one looked at it that way, there was no such thing as a pure- or halfblood—only pure or wild-magic-diluted magical signatures. The great blood debate came down to nothing more significant than the swirls on everyone's fingertips.

Perhaps she would write a satirical short story: a terrible account of the war between clockwise-swirlers and anti-clockwise-swirlers. Those poor souls whose fingerprints swirled neutrally from the middle of their fingers would be tragically caught in the middle. Friends would betray friends, families would be torn asunder. She winced as her thoughts took a dark turn. On second thought, it was too soon. Maybe a couple centuries from now, when the purebloods died out of their own inbreeding and blood purity was looked upon with the same awkward discomfort as other forms of bigotry.

It's sad that polite embarrassment feels like it would be a win, she thought with a depressed sigh. Dom sent her the echo of a good feeling, and the unexpected flicker of cheer jolted her out of the morose cloud she'd drawn around herself. Now is no time to be despairing for the state of the world, she chided herself.

While she had him, Rigel asked Dom something that had been bothering her lately. Why weren't you integrated with my magic when I absorbed you?

It would destroy me. The answer came swift and sure. If I allowed myself to be changed by you the way raw magic is changed when you absorb it ambiently, I would no longer be me. I would be you. A pause came before Dom added. Is that what you hoped? That one day I would simply dissolve into the fire of your core?

She shook her head physically, then added, because he wasn't in her lab to see, No. I just wondered. Is the reason you are able to resist it because you are powerful?

It is because I have excellent control, he corrected her. Just as your enemy must, to keep his own magic from melding fully with yours even so removed from his physical influence over it.

Rigel mulled that over carefully. That Riddle had superior control of his magic was unquestionably true. Was that enough to explain why he had not lost all awareness of the magic after injecting her with it? You said that Riddle must be very powerful, too, to sense his magic in me at a distance. Could I do that, if I put magic into something and someone else carried it?

With enough power and control, you could do anything.

She didn't like the way he said 'anything,' but was pleased that her experiment was theoretically possible, at least.

Rigel had a medi-mini in her palm. The imbuing toy glowed faintly when she poured raw magic into it—the same unshaped way she would put magic into the crystal meter that measured rate of magical expenditure. Now that she knew what resonance felt like, she could appreciate the slight buzzing to her magical senses for what it was. So she could, if she concentrated hard enough, recognize her own unshaped magic in other things.

The next step was harder. She set the medi-mini down one foot away on the lab table and let go. The already subtle resonance immediately stopped. Rigel frowned at it, extending her magical awareness out until the training toy was within its sphere. It felt like a little ball of magic, but she wasn't certain she could identify it as hers.

Rigel would need someone else's help to complete the experiment, then. Determined, she closed the lab and wandered upstairs in search of some hapless soul. She found two in the Entrance Hall—or rather, they found her.

"All set to go on Phase One, Pup." Fred fell into step on her left, his brother only a beat behind.

"We're calling it: The Mysterious Box," George added as he took up position on her right.

"Figured a weekend lunch is the perfect time to introduce it," Fred went on as they walked through the Great Hall doors. "It's casual."

"Innocuous."

"Downright subtle."

Rigel turned her head toward a crowd of curious students, all clustered around a red-paneled box underneath one of the nearest windows. Through the throng, she could make out cheerful silver tassels hanging from the box's edges; flanking it were a pair of tall golden candles, flames soft and calm. An arched emerald banner was strung between the two candles, and above the heads of those pressed close Rigel read the silver letters with amusement.

Sacrifice Food Here!

"Subtle, you said?" Rigel shook her head with a smile.

George inclined his head gravely. "It doesn't even explode."

"Or fizzle."

"Or whir."

"Or ooze."

"Or—"

"Yes, yes, it's the picture of restraint," she conceded. In a lower voice she added, "Did the Headmaster agree?"

"He seemed positively keen," Fred revealed.

George nodded, looking a bit bewildered. "Said if we pulled the whole thing off, he might give us a special service award."

"'Course we told him if he did that, the whole thing would be ruined," Fred said sagely.

"Good pranksters don't take credit." George elbowed Rigel in the side and grinned. "Suppose that makes you our patsy, then."

"Not yet," she said sternly. "We agreed to ease into it."

The twins waved her words aside. "We know," said Fred.

"This one's for the long game," George concurred.

They dropped her at the table, and Pansy leaned in as Rigel considered the food choices. "Know anything about that charming new altar, Rye? So far, any food placed inside of it disappears when you close the lid."

She met the blonde girl's eyes and smiled secretively, but only said, "I need help with an experiment. Have you covered conscious imbuing yet in Potions?" Pansy blinked at her. Rigel took that as a 'no.' "Anyone else able to push magic into an object consciously?"

"What kind of spell are you casting?" Theo asked, only sounding vaguely curious.

"It's not a spell," she said. "I need someone to put raw magic into this." She pulled out one of the red rubber balls.

"Medi-minis again, Rigel?" Millicent said from across the table. "I haven't seen you with those since first year."

"Let me try," Blaise offered, holding out a hand. She passed the ball over and Blaise curled his fingers around it gently. After a long pause, it bled from red to brown and finally to green. "There. Just like imbuing a runic array."

Rigel grinned. "Thanks." She took out the one she had imbued earlier and gave it to him as well. "Now mix them up behind your back and don't tell me which is which."

With an intrigued glint to his eyes, Blaise did as she asked. When he offered them to her again, one in each hand, he asked, "Are you going to try to differentiate them?"

"Exactly," she murmured, drawing in her focus to press her magical senses outward. She could feel both balls, warm little orbs of magic side by side. "Draw them apart a bit," she said, frowning. As Blaise drew his hands apart, she tried to compare the two spheres.

The magic in them wasn't static—magic never was. It churned through each of the small toys in restless circles, but there was definitely a difference. One spun with a purpose, while the other sort of drifted. She thought one of them felt warmer, in a way, but did that necessarily mean it was hers?

Rigel hesitated, then reached out to point at the one that felt warmer and more energetic. "Is this one mine?"

Blaise smiled. "Correct." He seemed impressed, but Rigel wasn't satisfied.

"Your magic is pretty different from mine. Maybe I should test it against another fire core." She flipped through her memories of the sleeping sickness and said, "Millie, your core is fire, right?"

Millicent shrugged. "Suppose so, but I don't know how to transfer magic like that."

"It's easy—" Rigel began.

At the same time, Blaise said, "It's tricky—"

They glanced at once another, and at Blaise's raised eyebrows, Rigel relented. "Well, perhaps you should teach her, Blaise."

Her dark-eyed friend smiled wryly. "Give us a few weeks, and you can attempt the next stage in your experiment."

Rigel wanted to sigh at having to wait so long when she was impatient to know the answer now. She refrained, as it would likely come across as ungrateful. "Thanks," she said. "I appreciate the help."

"What will you do once you know whether you can recognize the magic you split off?" Millicent asked. "If it's something to do with that mysterious red box, count me out; I'm not going to the trouble of learning a difficult skill just for one of your pranks."

"My pranks?" Rigel put a hand to her heart. "You really think I have time for pranks with all that's going on this year?"

"You have time to experiment with esoteric magic," Theo pointed out with a teasing grin.

Rigel had no response to that, and her friends shared a laugh at her expense.

"Is it your mysterious box, Rigel?" Draco asked quietly from beside her as the conversation around them moved on. "Or are those Gryffs roping you into something again?"

She grinned a little and said, "That would be telling."

"Salazar help us; it is your box," Draco muttered on a sigh.

"It's really everyone's box, in a way," Rigel said lightly.

Draco narrowed his eyes in flat suspicion. "What does that mean?"

She promised he would find out with everyone else, and ignored his argument that being friends ought to gain him insider information about such things. The mysterious box was one prank she didn't want to mess up, even if it meant keeping her friends in the dark, too. The Weasley twins had been very selective about whom exactly they'd enlisted to help them pull it off, and the least Rigel could do after all the trouble they'd gone to was keep the details need-to-know.

As January waned, the boxes multiplied. The signage varied, as did the method of appearance. Some, like the one with a mouth drawn in the lid saying simply 'feed me' appeared overnight. Others, such as the one proclaiming 'donate here to make wishes come true,' hopped itself into the Great Hall one morning in a manner that very much suggested the animator twins were in on the game. When, the first week of February, a box with the banner reading 'the god of anonymous valentines demands tribute' appeared, the accusations came flooding in. It seemed a good number of people still remembered that prank.

Rigel enjoyed playing the reticent trickster, allowing her eyes to twinkle in her best Dumbledorian impression whenever someone worked up the courage to ask whether she was, in fact, behind the strange and elaborate boxes.

After several weeks, most people seemed to have simply accepted the boxes as part of the Hogwarts aesthetic—that the professors, at the Headmaster's behest, did nothing about them added an extra element of the surreal. Curious students regularly tested the boxes, but each time the result was constant: food (and anything else) put inside it disappeared. A particularly irritated Anthony Goldstein climbed into a box midway through the fourth week, but he was not whisked into non-being, to the general disappointment of those watching.

Her most fervent accuser, somewhat surprisingly, was Zhou. The Ravenclaw stopped by the Slytherin table several times a week to say, "I just know you're the one behind this, Rigel. Won't you tell me what you've planned?" Rigel gathered the other 'claws had elected Zhou, as Rigel's only close Ravenclaw friend, to inquire into the mystery as often as feasible. The lot of them couldn't stand being left in the dark.

She gave increasingly enigmatic responses. When Zhou dropped by the table again the morning before Valentine's Day, Rigel gave a vague smile and murmured, "Ah, yes, the offerings are most generous of late. Many blessings abound."

As Zhou smiled wryly and sauntered back to her impatiently awaiting housemates, Pansy gave a small sigh beside from beside her and said, "Really, Rigel, you're going to have to let her down more firmly at this rate."

Rigel shook her head patiently. "I told you, she and her housemates are just curious. As soon as the boxes are understood, this interest will die down."

"Give it up, Pansy," Theo said on a laugh. "Blokes like Rigel will always attract the hopeless romantic types."

Before Rigel could decide whether she ought to be offended, the post arrived. Hands made way automatically for claws and beaks and conversation paused as the owls made their presence insistently known.

They'd scarcely recovered their utensils when Millicent hissed under her breath, "Here she comes again."

Zhou appeared at Rigel's elbow slightly out of breath and slapped a periodical on the table beside her plate. "Is this real?"

Rigel blinked at the magazine before gingerly lifting it to eye the front cover. It was The Quibbler, and the headline shouted up at them: "Mysterious Food Donations Appear Nationwide! (First Signs of A House-Elf Revolution?)"

A snort escaped her before she could stop it. Despite the absence of any mention of them, it had Fred and George written all over it. "Where did you get this?" she asked, amused.

"Lovegood, of course," Zhou said impatiently.

"You can't believe anything you see in that rag," Draco said with a frown.

Zhou tossed her hair impatiently. "Yes, normally, but look at the article." Draco and Millicent both grabbed for it at once, and wound up holding it awkwardly between themselves as they both scanned the content swiftly.

"The date of the first reported incident matches when the first box appeared," Millicent muttered as she read. "Of course, with Lovegood here to report on it, that doesn't mean anything necessarily."

Draco made a noise of agreement, but added, "It says these unsolicited food donations have appeared everywhere from St. Mungo's to the Diagon Alley Food Kitchen to Dumbledore's new halfway home for squibs. With places this high-profile, the truth would be easy to verify."

"We've got everyone who knows someone at any of the locations cited already writing letters for more information," Zhou said briskly. Her eyes were bright with excitement as she grinned down at Rigel, who was struggling to keep a blank expression on her face.

"Smart thinking," Rigel said blandly.

"Might be unnecessary, though." Nott drew everyone's attention to the other side of the Great Hall, where a towering red and white confection that might have been a cake hidden under a pile of taffeta hearts was progressing steadily across the room.

Fred, George, and the animator twins carried it together between them, and the lack of struggle with the enormous pastry suggested magical assistance at work. The hall held a collective breath as the four boys lowered the cake carefully toward the newest box. The lip of the box stretched gluttonously until the entire six-foot concoction slid unobstructed into its gullet. The lid snapped shut after it, and the Great Hall exploded with the speculation of a thousand students.

"That's going to be hard to miss," Zhou murmured.

"I rather think that's the point," Blaise said dryly.

As usual, the dark-skinned boy was entirely correct. The next morning, students at every table awaited the post with an almost palpable anticipation, built up over weeks of unsatisfied curiosity and confusion. Rigel even saw Professor McGonagall tapping her plate impatiently, eyes trained on the open doors.

All around her, Rigel saw Valentine's Day packages ignored in favor of the nearest Daily Prophet; the collective occupants of St. Mungo's Children's Ward smiled out of the front page, a piece of distinctive taffeta-topped cake in every hand. Rigel leaned closer to Pansy's copy to pick out the words beneath.

VALENTINE'S SURPRISE AT ST MUNGO'S!

Yesterday St. Mungo's was the recipient of a six-tier, hundred-pound holiday surprise: a cake large enough to serve the entire hospital appeared without warning or explanation in the kitchens just after breakfast. This wasn't the first such surprise donation, however; for weeks, St. Mungo's, along with a number of other charitable institutions throughout the Wizarding World, has had a rash of anonymous food donations. Without fail, these donations appear seemingly of their own accord in kitchens and donation bins, never accompanied by so much as a word of explanation.

According to eye-witnesses, no apparent portkey apparatus has been noted, and of course our readers understand that it is impossible to apparate an item sans wizard to transport it. How are these donations finding their way to these institutions, then? It is, as of now, a mystery.

The Ministry was contacted as the first of these food offerings began to pour in, and officials reportedly conducted extensive testing to ensure the mysterious donations were safe to distribute and not a malicious prank. Auror James Potter, current Department Head, assures us, "No evidence of mal-intent or foul play was uncovered. We've determined these anonymous donations are just that—contributions to the less fortunate meant in charitable spirit."

When asked to comment on the strange phenomenon, the Director for Outreach at St. Mungo's had this to say: "Thank you! Whoever you are, however you're doing this, we're grateful. You have our assurance that as long as the donations last, they won't go to waste."

Rigel leaned back with a smile on her face. If she'd ever questioned the Weasley twins' talent for public relations, the proof was in black and white. They were geniuses.

"How did you do it?"

She turned to see Zhou, this time accompanied by at least a dozen of her housemates, standing with an awed expression on her face. Rigel tilted her head. "Still so sure it was me?" She didn't deny it, and by the looks of sharp suspicion in the 'claws' eyes, that didn't pass unnoticed.

"The Weasley twins are obviously in on it," Anthony Goldstein opined. "Those Slytherin twins, too. But this is bigger than some prank."

"It's a publicity stunt or something, right?"

"What are you trying to get out of it?"

"How did you even do this?"

The questions came too fast to pick out all of them, but she got the general gist. With a shrug, Rigel asked a question of her own. "Do you know what happens to the food we don't eat every day?"

The group around their table fell silent. From behind her, she heard Pansy say, "Some of it is fed to the creatures in the forest."

"Some gets composted, too," an older Ravenclaw said slowly, his face scrunched in thought. "I had to turn it into soil in detention for Sprout once."

"And the rest?"

"Vanished," Draco muttered.

Rigel put a hand to her ear. "What's that, Draco?"

Her friend scowled at her, but raised his voice. "The elves vanish it after every meal. I've seen them do it." Rigel knew he had—she'd been there, too.

Raised eyebrows and understanding murmurs circulated for a moment before Zhou said slowly, "So you set up a way for excess food to be…transported to other places that can use it. But how, Rigel? Is it like a vanishing cabinet? Or a one-way Floo?"

Rigel blinked at the girl, a devilish mischief alight in her heart. "Who said I set up anything?"

The Ravenclaws groaned, and the Slytherins snickered into their plates.

"Honestly, do they expect him to admit it?" Theo chuckled.

The group dispersed with grumbled words of disappointment, and Rigel went back to her now-chilly porridge. Her friends were all eyeing her, so she raised an eyebrow at them. "What? You, too?"

"You don't have to tell us." Millicent sniffed. "I'm just wondering how you got the staff to go along with this for so long."

"It's not much of an extra expense," Rigel said quietly. "Most of the food put into the boxes really would have been vanished anyway. The cake was just to make a point."

"The house-elves are the ones moving the food, though, aren't they?" Pansy murmured. "They don't need vanishing cabinets to do something so simple."

Rigel grinned. House-elves really were amazing beings. Fred and George had sent her as the emissary to convince them to alter the way they dealt with leftover food. With the Headmaster's approval, the kitchen workers had been thrilled to take a few extra steps after each meal. The elaborate boxes were just for show—house-elves did the real work, transporting anything put in them to similar boxes below in the kitchens, the same way food was transported back and forth between the house tables and the four parallel tables downstairs.

The elves would sort out unsuitable items left in the boxes—half-eaten or contaminated food—and the rest was sent to where it could do more good than vanishing into nonbeing. Eventually, the idea was to have one permanent donation bin by the Great Hall doors, where anything that a student no longer wanted could be given to someone in need. With this as an alternative, the elves could stop relegating lost items to the Come and Go Room entirely. Dumbledore, according to the twins, thought the 'prank' would instill a charitable awareness in the student population without seeming condescending or overly superior, as it might if introduced by the staff.

Fred and George, of course, were simply hoping to turn Rigel's public image on its head after the somewhat gritty aura she'd gained. As she considered the way her schoolmates were responding to the prank—as curious and incredulous as the twins had envisioned—Rigel thought they might just succeed in all three goals at once.

As though Riddle feared any ebb in public fervor, the announcement informing the champions of the fourth task was dovetailed with a press conference. On the castle lawn, another of the DMGS' many temporary stages was erected. All three of the finalists were obliged to answer questions from those of the press corps invited for the event, and while Rigel was far from keen to face off against the grating Ms. Skeeter once more, she had to admit the woman was dangerously good at her job.

With a tenacious smile that was almost eclipsed by the blonde curls that clung to her head, Rita Skeeter neatly cross-foiled Delacour's remark that the tournament was a proving ground of traditional magical abilities with Owens' assertation that creativity and problem solving were at the heart of every task.

Somehow, and Rigel herself wasn't quite sure whether Skeeter had engineered the statement or not, the reporter got Owens to say, "The real competition hasn't started yet." She was sure they'd be seeing that tag line splayed below the photograph of the three blood champions in their smartest robes, Hogwarts beautiful and snow-capped behind them.

She wondered whether Riddle had engineered this backdrop with a particular intention. He stood tall in sweeping, silver-trimmed robes of deepest black. Against the snow, he cut a dramatic figure, all the more so for how at home he appeared with the seat of his opposition rising triumphantly behind him.

Rigel sensed Skeeter's eyes when they landed on her, like carrion beetles alighting on a meal. She had time to turn her attention back to the small crowd of reporters before the woman raised a single, acid-green-clad hand and the clamor around her snuffed itself in anticipation.

"This one is for the young Mr. Black," Skeeter purred. All Rigel could think was that Binny sometimes called her the very same thing.

"Yes, Ms. Skeeter?"

"All of Wizarding Britain has been atwitter over a wave of mysterious food donations this month."

"That sounds more like a statement," Rigel said, a genuine smile finding its way into her voice. If Skeeter was leading where she thought, then Fred and George had truly come into their own.

Amusement and anticipation threaded through the assembled members of the press as Skeeter's leading statement found purchase in their imaginations. The savvy woman smiled with approval, even as she let out a tittering laugh for strategic effect. "I heard a rumor, Mr. Black. Some of the students at this very school believe they have evidence that paints you as the mysterious architect behind this widespread charitable phenomenon. My question," she drew out the word like a boa constrictor might indulgently squeeze its catch, "is this: if you are the one behind it, what made you take time away from preparation for this dangerous and prestigious tournament to pull such a stunt?"

Rigel let a coy smile curl about her lips and cast her eyes to the side as though she were thinking about her response. When she looked back at Skeeter's sharp gaze, Rigel caught respect there for a brief moment. "I can neither confirm nor deny the rumors of my involvement. On an unrelated note, I'd like to say that the Cora Foundation is a non-profit initiative backed by the Black and Malfoy families to get life-saving potions to children in need." She paused to allow the reporters to scribble down the name, then added. "Minister Fudge was instrumental in its creation. Isn't that right, Minister?"

Put on the spot, Fudge preened and launched into a long-winded account of his personal interest in the good of the wizarding community. Rigel stepped back and smiled at the way Riddle's press conference dissolved into curiosity about this new cross-party charity. Eventually, Riddle had no choice but to step in to bring focus back to the tournament.

"I'm sure you're all wondering just what the fourth task will entail," he proclaimed with a clap of his hands. Attention snapped back to him like a stretched bow string abruptly released. "Much like the first task of the preliminaries, the first task of the finals will take place in a unique arena. Instead of the Dark Forest, our next task will take place in…the Black Lake!"

Rigel frowned as the questions burst one-by-one from the impatient reporters.

"Did you say in the Black Lake?"

"How long—"

"—but what precise task will there—"

"Lord Riddle, will the observation orbs be used again?"

At Skeeter's question, Riddle inclined his head. "Indeed, and three of the runic mirrors will be recalled to Hogwarts for the viewing pleasure of all who secure tickets to this fantastic task. Can you picture it? Our champions will brave the cold, oxygenless depths of the mysterious Black Lake, swim through its murky waters, evade the countless creatures of the deep, all to find…well, that would be telling."

Millicent and Pansy were right, then; the task was some sort of treasure hunt. There were plenty of valuable things in the lake. A dozen rare ingredients came easily to mind. Rigel had never harvested anything underwater, and the thought that the fourth task might be like a subsurface scavenger hunt was cheering. Much better than duels, at least.

After a flurry of questions, Riddle stepped back to allow Misters Crouch and Bagman to expound on how the tournament was fostering international relations. Heavily emphasized in their speech was the assertion that the assessed value of increased trade had already outstripped the losses from restitutions paid following the "unfortunate World Cup incident."

Whether by accident or design, Riddle's retreat brought him to stand beside Rigel, his proximity like a concentrated aura of ill omens. She was unlikely to get an easier chance to speak to him without approaching him directly, but Rigel wondered whether he would be able to control his reaction to the question she wanted to ask. She supposed, either way, his reaction or lack thereof would tell her something.

"I heard a rumor, too," she hissed near-silently. Her mouth barely moved to accommodate the sibilant language.

"About your self-painted altruisssm?" Riddle sounded bored, but he answered her in Parseltongue, nonetheless, careful to keep it below the register of human hearing.

"About a mutual enemy, ressurfacccing in London." Rigel cut her eyes to watch Riddle's expression as she added, "At leassst, I asssumed the rogue conssstruct wasss your enemy. Perhapsss I wasss missstaken."

Riddle's attention swung toward her with an almost audible snap. His brilliant eyes drilled into her, shock warring with anger and disbelief. His first words were a denial. "You lie."

"To what end?"

"To dissstract me from the presssent climate."

"Thisss isss directly related to the presssent climate, or can't you sssee that much?" Rigel rolled her shoulders and pretended to look about the crowd, pleasant smile fixed in place for the sake of the press.

When she chanced another glance at him, Riddle's face was sharply closed, and his eyes had gone still in thought. "The extremisssstsss" he whispered, almost too quiet for Rigel to hear. "The attacksss…you believe it isss all the work of that failed experiment?"

"If you are not behind it yourssself," she said, a shrug in her voice despite her still and relaxed posture. "I did entertain the thought that you may be working together."

Riddle's answering hiss was onomatopoeic in its wordless outrage. "Collaborate with that mad, broken thing? Never."

"It makesss sssenssse, though," Rigel argued. She was more than half convinced of his sincere indignation, if nothing else, but she drew the accusation out to be sure. "What a coincccidenccce that the attack thisss sssumer happened to make thossse in power desssperate for more revenue—and along comesss your competition."

"My tournament wasss approved long before the attacksss began." Riddle spat the words through his teeth, even as he smiled dashingly for the flashing cameras. "I ssstrongly sssuggessst you refrain from further accusssationsss, lessst I forget that we have a mutual enemy at all."

His threat was hollow, if his anger and shock were real. Rigel raised a hand to acknowledge the gesturing photographers, even as she hissed, "Then asss the enemy of your enemy, I'll tell you to watch your back—it isss poaching your people to flesssh out itsss ranksss."

"It daresss!" Riddle's reaction was so vehement, Delacour, who was closest to where they stood, rubbed her ear as some of the unintelligible sounds in the human range reached her. The politician reined in his fury, barely, and demanded, "Who?"

"Barty Crouch," she said blandly. "Apparently you have not kept him busssy enough thisss year."

Riddle's anger vanished in an instant, like lightning into a rod, as though the promise of an eventual outlet was enough to ground it for the time being. It was mildly terrifying to witness, and Rigel felt a strange gratitude that it was not she who would ultimately face the tempered wrath.

"How sssoon he forgetsss what favorsss he owesss me," Riddle mused, soft as a sigh but much more sinister.

Rigel couldn't resist. "Technically, he isss ssstill ssserving you—"

"That missscreation isss not me! My followersss ssshould know better. It wasss not that mad thing that raisssed them to the exhaulted posssition they hold today." Riddle's words came fast, hissed together in a string that would have been difficult for even an actual snake to follow. He seemed to have forgotten that Rigel was there as his ire flowed hot once more—except, of course, that Riddle never lost touch with his surroundings.

Except when he did, she amended after remembering the rage he'd flown into at the Malfoy summer garden party after second year.

"Who beat the cobwebsss off a desssperate, entombed platform and forged it into a monument that could withssstand the modern ssstomach? Who drummed a political movement from tatty tradition and disssenfranchisssed elitesss? Who fassshioned legessslation and lasssting change from naught but old complaintsss and stubbornnessss? How quickly they forget, thessse ratsss of the presssent age."

Riddle was really on a roll, and Rigel hated to interrupt him but the tournament organizers were looking their way, clearly waiting for him to dismiss the press conference. "Crouch is—" she began, but Riddle's quiet vehemence latched onto the name before she could finish.

"Crouch! The turncoat. Doesss he think the conssstruct can better ssserve his ambitionsss? Who dealt with hisss father when—"

"Hisss father is waiting for you to disssmissss everyone," she hissed through a mouth of teeth clenched so hard she felt them creak.

Riddle moved his eyes from the distant line of trees he'd been silently scorching with his gaze to the group of people waiting politely, if a bit unsurely, for his go-ahead. The man's shoulders twitched subtly, as though shaking off an uninvited hand, and he favored each of the assembled with a smile that was both personal and promising. "I'm afraid that's all the time we have today. Please direct any further inquiries to the DMGS staff. I'll see you all in three days' time for the fourth task."

The gathered began to scatter, in twos and threes as cameramen packed up their accoutrements and made for the school gates. Delacour left at once, but Owens lingered. When Rigel met his gaze, she found an unexpected heat there. His usually relaxed face was taut, a deep-seated flame flashing in the shadows of his eyes, like a knife glinting in dark. His gaze slid from her to Riddle, who was watching the departing press, and the fire was banked. When Owens looked back at her again, a crooked smile crawled across his cheek and he winked. Rigel blinked, and the expression was gone. All-around American boy Jacob Owens was back, strolling his way off the stage without a care in the world.

She frowned after him, but Riddle regained her attention with a quiet word.

"Rigel."

She turned to find the man imperiously close to her, head slightly tilted in a way that was certainly meant to be intimidating.

"Riddle," she said flatly, unperturbed.

"I trussst you will not ssshare thisss rumor with anyone until I have dealt with it."

Rigel scowled at his presumption. "I will deal with it asss I sssee fit, asss will you." She already had, besides.

"Do not toy with me on thisss, boy," Riddle hissed. He leaned further into her personal space, and Rigel bristled.

Her magic flared out in a wave, much as it had with Caelum at the first Yule Gala she'd attended. Unlike Lestrange, Riddle wasn't moved. The magic washed over him like a wave breaking on a rock. Amusement turned his lips.

"It'll take more than that, I'm afraid." His posture relaxed as he slipped back into English, and the man turned to go.

That sounds like a challenge, Dom whispered in her ear.

She narrowed her eyes and sent another pulse—this time at the stage beneath his feet. The wood wrinkled, Riddle stumbled, and the few remaining reporters tittered unkindly. He spun back around and a whip of magic raced through the air between them, faster than her senses could track. She only knew it was there by the sting that bloomed in her cheek on its heel. Rigel stood unflinching, rooted to the spot at the realization that Riddle's magic had moved quicker than hers could react. Riddle could fling his magic faster than an explosion, which her magic was more than capable of intercepting.

Rigel kept her gaze steady until Riddle, apparently satisfied, recovered his dignity and quit the stage. I regret nothing, she thought, consciously unrepentant in spite of the welt she could feel forming on her cheek. Her own little construct chuckled lowly. 'Atta girl.

Her good feeling about the fourth task lasted until she mirror-called Archie to explain it.

"It's probably some sort of scavenger hunt," she said, smiling. "Should be pretty low-threat, aside from the creatures that live in the lake."

Archie stared at her from the glass, eyes wide. "Uh, Rigel, has it occurred to you that you'll be in the lake?"

She nodded, unconcerned. "Of course. Don't worry, Archie. I actually have the perfect potion for this task, but it seems a shame to waste something so rare. Gillyweed will do just as well, I think. Professor Snape said the task isn't planned for longer than an hour."

"No, I mean—you'll have to go swimming in the lake. In something you can swim in. Which will probably not be loose-fitting." Archie's voice grew increasingly high as she blinked at him. "Rigel, you're going to make me look like a eunuch!"

She hushed him and peeked out of her silenced curtains just to be sure none of her roommates had wandered in. "Don't be dramatic. No one will be looking at that."

"Everyone will be looking at that!"

Rigel frowned. Surely not. Then again, when had her faith in humanity been rewarded? "You…think so? I could wear several layers…and the water is going to be cold."

"Not that cold." Archie groaned. He ran a hand over his face, and then a disquieting grin crept across it. "All right. Don't worry."

"I am abruptly worried."

"I'm going to send you something. Don't ask any questions! This is about my reputation as a man."

Rigel sighed. "I swear if you send me a rolled-up pair of socks—"

It was so much worse than socks. Rigel received a nondescript package the next morning—plain brown paper and no return address. It was so innocuous that every student at the Slytherin table eyed it with interest. She tucked the wand-sized box under her arm with a grimace and decided to open it in private.

Her intuition hadn't failed her. In an out-of-the-way-alcove, under the Invisibility Cloak, Rigel opened the box to reveal a lurid-pink calling card that flashed the words "Innocent Illusions, Hogsmeade's Premier Adult Toy Shop" in metallic script. With a choked laugh that bubbled out of unadulterated horror, Rigel lifted the card aside to reveal a length of turgid silicon nestled in purple cloth. 'Self-Adhering Strap-On' was helpfully embroidered on the silk covering. She poked it. The apparatus had a strange amount of give, and it was flesh-colored, which somehow made it worse.

With a mortified groan, she closed the box again and rubbed her eyes in disbelief. Seriously, Archie, what the hell? Did he really expect her to wear it?

Of course he did. After several long breaths she opened the box again and tried to look at it clinically. She dug to the bottom and read the directions. Twice. It would adhere to her with a simple spell could be released with another. Truly, it didn't seem complicated. According to the advertisement, the artificial member would even function like a normal one, rising and…falling as her own bodily fluctuations dictated.

I never needed this much fidelity into the male form, she thought silently. She had almost made it over the hump from disturbed to darkly amused. The few times she'd Polyjuiced as Archie had been more than enough for one lifetime. She did have to admit that Polyjuice itself couldn't solve this problem. There was no time to brew the Modified Polyjuice, even if there hadn't been a large probability that changing the ultimate sex of the gene fusion ritual would noticeably change her appearance, too.

If she looked at it objectively, Archie's plan was an elegant solution. The trouble was, she wasn't completely convinced the problem even merited a solution at all. Rigel still doubted people would be paying attention to what she carried between her legs when so much life-and-death action was unfolding.

It would make Archie feel better if she wore it, though, and her cousin had asked precious little of her all year. Rigel wrapped the box in her cloak and tucked the whole thing into her bag before securing it firmly. Eleven-year-old me would have been hard-pressed to predict this, she thought, giving into the humor completely. I hope it doesn't make it harder to swim.

CHAMPION OF CHARITY: BLACK GIVES BACK

Just days before the resumption of Triwizard Tournament tasks, this reporter got a chance to speak face-to-face to the three finalists. The delectable Fleur Delacour, dressed for winter weather in a sable-trimmed over robe, expressed admiration for the varied trials presented thus far, while Jacob Owens, Ilvermorny heartthrob, admitted genuine trepidation regarding the coming tasks. "The real competition is just getting started—everything before was a warm-up." There is little doubt that the road ahead will bring both danger and delight for our beloved Blood Champions, but for one of the finalists, there is a more pressing challenge to be faced.

My readers have no doubt been following the recent accounts of spontaneous donations made to a rash of charitable institutions. While each contribution was made anonymously, this reporter has tracked them back to their source: Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. Multiple eye-witnesses confirmed that the extravagant Valentine's Day cake delivered to St. Mungo's last week was in fact present the day before in the Great Hall. Evidently, a series of donation boxes have been appearing in the hall, one after another, for weeks. Given this, coupled with the fact that every mysterious donation appeared without portkey, this reporter suspects the instrument of miraculous delivery to be none other than the Hogwarts house-elves.

But who ordered the house-elves of Hogwarts to begin making these impressive charitable donations? When questioned on whether he sanctioned the bequests, Headmaster Albus Dumbledore had this to say: "Hogwarts students have long been disposed to the occasional prank. Tradition dictates that, absent any pressing danger or harm, the faculty overlooks such expressions of creativity."

This much, all of us blessed to attend the great school can attest, but are we to believe that students orchestrated what some are calling, "the greatest concentrated effort to raise public awareness of the decade"? This reporter went to the students themselves and asked one question: who do you think is behind this prank?

"It's not a one-man effort," said one seventh-year who wishes to remain anonymous. "I think someone has united the pranksters of Hogwarts for a larger purpose."

"The Weasley twins were seen carrying the cake," another student agreed. "The animator twins [a pair of young Slytherins suspected to be associated with elaborate pranks], too. That said, this whole thing is sort of Black's calling card."

"Rigel Black is behind it—it's always him," a young Ravenclaw assured me. "He did a Valentine's Day delivery service before. Romantic Rigel, we called him." She provided a list of past pranks associated with Heir Black, compelling evidence of a trend toward the altruistic.

Arcturus Black, called Rigel by his close friends, has made an impressive showing in the tournament thus far, but he was making a splash at Hogwarts long before he was chosen to represent the school. Readers may recall that Black was directly involved in curing the Sleeping Sickness at just eleven. Potions Master Severus Snape cited the boy's help in developing the latest improvement to the Wolfsbane Potion at twelve, and academic records acquired from the Ministry's official file system reveal that last year this dedicated student somehow acquired an astonishing number of credits across the spectrum of magical specialties. Accounts from those close to him describe Black as a compassionate soul who consistently goes out of his way to help others. With a portfolio like that, accomplishing a demonstration of the scale we have seen these past weeks is not at all beyond his capabilities.

What does Black himself have to say? The modest boy takes no credit for the donations. Instead, he used the opportunity presented by this reporter's question to speak of a new charitable project called the Cora Foundation. The foundation is the brain-child of Lords Lucius Malfoy and Sirius Black, an unlikely combination of benefactors, to say the least! This reporter had to double-check the facts before printing them, but it's true: the Malfoys and Blacks have teamed up to turn what started as a single joint donation to the St. Mungo's Children's Ward into a far-reaching social endeavor aimed to ensure equal access to costly life-saving potions.

It's safe to say that Black has his eye on the bigger picture. Following his tongue-in-cheek stunt, a tidal wave of donations from all over the country has come pouring into big-name charities such as the Orphan Fund. Local centers, too, have benefited, with contributions up fifteen percent across the board. As one reader put it, "When a Hogwarts student can do this, it puts the rest of us adults to shame!" One thing in this mystery is clear: the New Triwizard Tournament lived up to its claims to procure the finest young wizards and witches in the world. If the tasks tested virtue alone, this reporter would bet it all on Black.

Rigel could only hide behind the paper for so long. At Millicent's impatient cough, she lowered the crisp pages to the table and offered a grimace to her friends' expectant faces. "Would you believe me if I said this wasn't my doing?"

"Yes," Draco said with a snort.

Millie only smiled. "It doesn't matter who did it. Rigel, you're society's darling."

"Until tomorrow, at least," she muttered. Cynicism seemed the only possible response to anything by-lined by Rita Skeeter, despite the objective victory to Archie's reputation the article represented. She would have to get the twins something truly excellent for their birthday this year.

"Focus on today, then," Theo suggested. "You've got a task to win, don't you?"

As though she could forget. Rigel was already wearing her swim costume under her robes, which consisted of several compression shirts, an uncomfortably snug pair of shorts, and Archie's special gift, which she was emphatically not thinking about.

After all the hype, the fourth task still seemed almost anticlimactic. Even underwater, what was a scavenger hunt compared to a race through the Forbidden Forest, a death-defying obstacle course, and a grueling series of one-on-one duels? She made her way down to the lake without any noticeable nerves. Pansy and Draco wanted to walk with her, but were called away by Professor Snape to answer for a discrepancy in one of their joint assignments. Rigel didn't mind. For once, she was completely prepared for whatever happened.

When she reached the lakeside, it was to see only a small group of people waiting in the cold. Some practical soul had decided that, as they were going to be viewing the task through the observation orbs anyway, there was no need to drag spectators away from their usual seats. The audience would remain at the Quidditch pitch, which left the champions to prepare in relative peace at the Black Lake's rocky shore.

"Mr. Black, you can leave anything you don't want to get wet in the tent." Crouch gestured to a modest pavilion, from which Delacour was just emerging in a shining silver swimsuit. Rigel ducked inside and shucked her outer robe with a shiver. A couple of firm Warming Charms, and she felt comfortable enough to abandon her shoes and socks as well. From her robe pocket, she unwrapped a wad of viscous Gillyweed. Her Liberespirare Potion would live to see another use.

She hesitated over her pocket-watch. It would be good to have an easy way to check the time, but she didn't know whether it was waterproof. There was a latch behind the watch-face that she'd never figured out how to open; for all she knew, there might be something delicate inside, like a piece of paper or a lock of hair. In the end, she left it on top of her robes. She hoped the Tempus Charm worked underwater.

Rigel picked her way carefully to the edge of the water. Delacour gazed thoughtfully into the dark water, but Owens looked over at Rigel as she approached.

"Now we can start," he said with a friendly grin.

"Actually, we must wait for the appointed hour," Crouch disagreed.

"Makes it easier to judge your times," Bagman added with a self-deprecating laugh. He held a trio of headbands out. "You remember these beauties. Blue for the lady. Yellow for our American contender. And green for our resident Slytherin, of course."

Next, Crouch produced three metal bracelets. Rigel recognized them as more permanent versions of the parchments they'd each been given in the first task. The bracelets clamped down over their wrists and covered the skin between hand and elbow. Concentric circles were etched in iridescent color that would no doubt glow underwater. Three dots blinked on each one. Rigel noted how carefully Crouch determined who would get which bracelet. Whatever the dots tracked were not all the same, then.

"Today's task is collection," Bagman said bracingly. "Each champion has three items to collect, the general location of which is displayed on your wrist gauges. The first to return to the surface of the lake—not necessarily the shore—with all three of his or her respective items will gain the most points. Partial credit will be awarded for the retrieval of only some of the items."

"Is there a time limit?" Owens asked.

"No." Crouch said firmly. "But once you surface, you cannot return below again."

Rigel exchanged a look with the other two champions. She could tell they were thinking the same thing—if there was no time limit, why would anyone come back with less than all three items?

"What are ze items?" Fleur asked, examining her bracelet with a frown. "Eet does not zay."

Bagman laughed loudly. "You'll know them when you see them. Each is unmistakably marked."

Rigel supposed they would be color coordinated, like the headbands. With the clock ticking toward the hour, Bagman and Crouch hustled the three champions into their starting positions, spaced by several dozen paces along the waterline. At the organizers' urging, Rigel put on her headband, feeling the observation magic activate as the inside band touched the skin of her forehead. She kept her gaze forward toward the rippling, mirror-black surface of the lake, even as she steadily fed herself the slimy weed that had been kept warm by her hand.

She had only just swallowed when Bagman's magnified voice rang out. "BEGIN!"

Rigel heard the others begin to wade into the cold water, but she paused a moment to let the change brought on by the raw ingredient shudder through her. Amazing plant, Gillyweed. Cultivated for centuries by a reclusive coven of hags, its modern form was only discovered when an Herbologist on a collection trip fell in love with what he believed to be a human-mermaid hybrid. The transformation was both akin to Polyjuice and not, more a blooming than a twisting, followed by an intense, unqualified urge to get in the water.

She surged forward, some animal instinct more in control of her than she was, and it wasn't until the water closed over her head that clear thought returned and she was able to take stock. Her body had indeed taken on the characteristics she'd read about, but knowing and experiencing were different things. Rigel took an experimental swipe at the water and marveled at the way her webbed appendages propelled her forward with ease. This was another reason she'd gone with Gillyweed over other options—Rigel was not a particularly strong swimmer, and her new fins would give her an advantage. As the water passed through her gills, air came into her lungs without effort, and the brief discomfort of holding her breath was gone.

She peered through the murky blue water without trouble. It took her a moment to notice that her headband was emitting a light of its own. It cut a strange path of illumination in the direction her head was pointing, unnaturally clear wherever the beam landed. She supposed the spectators needed something worth seeing down in the depths. Rigel tilted her wrist to check the closest item's bearing and took off in that direction with a whooshing displacement of water. Once she found a rhythm, she crossed the vast distance with astonishing speed.

Focused on the steady pull through the water, she found it difficult to mark time passing. The terrain, too, seemed meaninglessly disordered. How much ground she covered was impossible to say without distances printed on the bracelet. The closest dot on the tracker took her into a field of long lakeweed, which snaked around her in ebbs and flows as she passed, like slimy wheat swaying in an invisible wind. She dove in and through it with a playful enjoyment that didn't seem entirely hers, allowing her webbed feet and hands to carry her forward in spiraling dives, which she sort of hoped made at least a few of those watching queasy.

A grip on her ankle arrested her mid-spin, and Rigel twisted, expecting to find it tangled in the weed bed. Instead, she caught a pale green Grindylow latched on, pointed teeth readying to bite. Rigel kicked her other leg around and rapped it sharply about the head, mindful to avoid its little horns. It startled, jaws clicking together on nothing, but its strong grip didn't waver. She palmed her wand and pointed it threateningly, but the creature seemed to have no appreciation for the danger it represented. Admittedly, it probably wouldn't have encountered a wand in its own backyard before, unless a first-year had dropped one over the side of a boat.

She didn't really want to kill it, despite the annoyingly strangling grip it maintained on her ankle. Aside from the unnecessariness of such an action, the blood could attract anything. Ex-Headmaster Dippet had a number of suggestions for gentle extraction from an unreasonable foe, and it was with a smile that Rigel tried a spell she'd been looking forward to with a bit of morbid curiosity for some time.

Rigel flipped her wand around and pointed it at herself before mouthing, "Lubricus Corpus."

Slime bloomed from every pore, and Rigel had to fight the urge to squeak at the sensation. It was somewhere between ticklish and uncomfortable, but it left her coated as effectively as a good basting. Her ankle slipped from the Grindylow's grasp like a fish, and she shot away from it with a grin. The creature snarled at her and tried to pursue, but when she bent her appendages to the task, she easily outstripped it. If anything, the slick glaze covering her entire body helped her move even faster through the water.

The blinking dot on her forearm was the only indication that she was heading in the correct direction. It drifted closer to the center as she wove around ridges and knolls, through gulleys and gorges. Her path took her right to the edge of a cliff, where a field of giant spirulina ended abruptly before a drop-off. At the very precipice of the bluff something glinted, reflecting the light of her headlamp. She approached carefully, but there didn't seem to be any protections set up to stymie her. Tied to a stake that had been unceremoniously thrust into the lakebed was a golden circlet no bigger than a grapefruit. She eyed the emerald green sash that secured the ring and supposed this was what they meant when they said the items would be unmistakably marked for each champion.

Rigel circled the golden prize carefully, searching for a ward or trap. It seemed too easy that all she had to do was collect it. She shivered as she drifted over the deep water of the drop-off. The cold seeped up to surround her suspended form like a tangible shadow. Though she knew it was only a natural consequence of the mingling depths, the chill still set her teeth on edge. It felt like a warning, urging her to hurry up.

She dove, wand brandished at the ready, but encountered nothing and easily looped her left arm through the golden circlet. Rigel paused for a moment to tap it with a mild Sticking Charm. Once assured that it would stay in place, she gave the mental equivalent of a shrug, thinking, Maybe it really is that simple. After all, there's every chance the dangers of the lake itself will be enough of a challenge.

Rigel spun slowly in a circle to orient herself toward the next item. Both remaining dots on her tracking bracelet were relatively far away, blinking in the outer-most ring of distance markers, but one was slightly closer. She set off toward that one, her course taking her away from the shallow field of underwater grass, out over the drop-off.

Colder water pressed into her despite the Gillyweed's thermo-regulating effects. The light of her headband did nothing to penetrate the fathoms below her, and though she was loath to leave the little sunlight that had filtered down to her present depth, Rigel knew the odds of her next item being suspended conveniently in the water were slim.

She dove, water sliding over her still-slimed skin like air under the wings of a bird. Occasionally, something flickered at the edge of her vision, but for the most part she passed unmolested into the deeper trenches of the lake. If she still had ears, she'd have worried about the pressure, but they'd been sealed into something dense and muffled by the Gillyweed. She felt vibrations that might have been sound with her whole body, but for the most part they were easy to block out, the white noise of the underwater world like a persistent but mostly-steady thrumming deep in her bones.

Rigel was halfway to her second item when the water around her fluctuated sharply and began to drag her sideways without warning. She struggled against the current and the mild panic that something she couldn't see was sucking her in. Her beam of light caught a mottled purple and red tentacle to her left and the sensation became clear—the giant squid was passing by, and she'd been caught in its undertow. She flailed inelegantly for a minute before giving into the displacement and allowing the water to tug her sideways in the squid's wake.

A curious tentacle reached out to stroke her arm as she grew near, slime meeting slime for a brief moment of surreal connection. The casual strength of its suckers pulled Rigel along for a time, as a child might drag a teddy bear aimlessly. She kept as still as she could so as not to strain anything accidentally. She doubted the squid meant any harm—it was notoriously domesticated and had never, to her knowledge, harmed a student in all the years it lived in the lake—but a creature so large could have little concept of its own strength.

When it lost interest and released her, Rigel found herself somewhat off-trajectory, but a great deal closer to her goal than before. Taking the luck as it came, she adjusted course and found herself approaching a sunken shipwreck. For a moment she could only stare.

How in Merin's name did a shipwreck get here? The idea of the tournament organizers arranging it for dramatic effect was not out of the question, but the established algae colonies looking quite at home all over its wooden surface put doubt to it. Come to think of it, the squid was a saltwater creature, wasn't it? How had it come to be in a Scottish Loch? Those deep trenches she'd passed over gained a new context if she considered the idea that the lake might contain some sort of passageway to other waters in its unfathomable reaches.

Awed and a bit intimidated by the notion, Rigel had to force her attention back to the task at hand. Her tracking beacon led her into the ship's cracked hull, and she carefully slipped through the jagged jaws of broken boards. Her headlamp crawled across the waterlogged cargo hold as she scanned it slowly. She startled a school of fish and had to flatten herself against a barrel as they scarpered past. In their trailing bubbles, she found the treasure she sought. An enormous golden locket was fastened to the pole of an emerald flag, which had been fixed to one of the blown-out portholes.

Rigel's webbed fingers were not up to the task of unhooking the clasp, but after tearing the heavy flag from the pole, she managed to lift it free. She settled the long chain of the locket around her neck and stuck the gaudy thing to her outer shirt with magic. Just one more item remained.

The final dot on her tracker was relatively close. It took her deeper as the terrain sloped downward, toward what she suspected was the very center of the lake. An eerie glow gradually replaced the darkness in the distance, and her eyes strained to understand what she was seeing. Eventually, she understood the towering silhouettes of light in the dark to be the spiraling skyline of an underwater city.

Merfolk, she realized with a touch of wonder. She knew selkies and merrows resided in the Black Lake, but somehow it had seemed unlikely that the tournament organizers would involve them in the task. Of course, common sense would have argued against involving the centaurs of the Dark Forest, too, so really Rigel should have expected no less. The outer limits of their settlement began as any city might, with small mud residences pocketed by neatly tended fields of lake grass. These dwellings shifted gradually to denser structures of stone as the tunnel-like streets between them gained an appreciable order.

Rigel wove her way warily toward her beacon, keeping an eye out for potentially unfriendly locals. The occasional face peered out at her from a window or doorway, but, other than one scowling selkie who brandished a lobabug at her disagreeably, none came out to either greet or impede her.

As the dot on her bracelet drew close to the center, she slowed her progression. Up ahead, in the heart of the mercity, she could see an area clear of buildings that was probably used as a town square. She darted between stone pillars cautiously. The task had been too easy. The tight feeling in her stomach made her all-too reluctant to rush ahead, despite the knowledge that she was being timed.

Rigel cupped a hand over the light on her headband and peered over a low stone wall into the city square. It had been cleared of vegetation completely, so nothing impeded her view of the squad of Aurors floating in a loose circle as though they had any business being at the bottom of the lake. Each of them wore a red wetsuit and a Bubblehead Charm, which distorted their features creepily. Behind the Aurors, in the center of the circle, she could see glimpses of two more people waiting, but the reason for their presence wasn't immediately clear.

Where was the last item? It must be valuable, to have actual guards, she thought. Maybe one of the two figures in the center of the protective circle was holding it. Would she have to duel someone after all?

She crept along the wall several meters, until she could get a better look at the two people the Aurors were encircling. When she finally caught a glimpse of one of their faces, the tight feeling in her stomach redoubled. It was Owens' girlfriend, Johanna something-or-other. Her eyes were closed, black hair adrift, and Rigel was slow to realize the girl wasn't floating the same way the Aurors were. She hung suspended, motionless, only tethered to the lakebed by a rope around her legs. There was no Bubblehead Charm on her, and for a terrible second Rigel thought she might actually be dead.

Don't be stupid, Rigel admonished herself as she ducked back down behind the wall, heart pounding. What would Aurors be doing guarding a dead body? She checked her wrist again, but her dot still blinked stubbornly at a distance that suggested her item was indeed within that circle of Aurors. Why would Owens' girlfriend have my third item? Then it hit her. The other figure in the circle.

Her heart in her throat, she darted further along the wall and looked again. There—between a burly Auror with a mustache and a woman she was vaguely sure she'd met before, Rigel saw her.

Pansy.

Her friend floated limply, blond hair a halo around her pale, slack face. Rigel's limbs jerked in an aborted spasm that she only barely quashed. Anger, boiling hot, coursed through her at the sight of sweet, fragile Pansy tied like a balloon to the lakebed. She didn't know whose idea it was to involve the champions' friends in this bloody spectacle, didn't know whether Pansy herself had agreed to it or been taken unknowing to this fate, but she did know that someone would answer for it.

Pansy didn't seem to be breathing. There was no indication as to whether she was unconscious or asleep, but when Rigel forced her eyes to peer harder through the gloom, she made out a series of numbers hanging over her head, glowing faintly: 11:48. It looked like a date or a time, but it wasn't November and—no, not a date, she corrected as the fourth number changed steadily before her focused gaze—a timer. It was counting backwards. She didn't care to find out what would happen to Pansy when it reached zero.

Rigel eyed the Aurors with unmistakably-aggressive intention. They were between her and Pansy, and that was their mistake. Eight of them and one of her. With a little over ten minutes left to something, taking them head-on was out of the question. It would have to be distraction.

She knew a few things about Auror protocol. A disturbance in the distance would not entice them to abandon the primary objective. The only thing that came before mission success was the individual safety of the squad's members, assuming the mission wasn't deemed worth the loss of life. Somehow, she doubted the tournament qualified.

How to threaten their safety without actually harming any of them? If she thought about it, she could probably come up with something from Dippet's book. Something elegant. Compassionate, even. Unfortunately for the Aurors, she was pressed for time and feeling a bit indignant on Pansy's behalf. Regardless of what would actually happen when the clock ran out, the mere implication that Pansy's airflow was at risk flat-out infuriated her. The Aurors would survive a small taste of that fear, she decided.

There was a spell that Healers used to transfer potions directly into a person's stomach. It wasn't ever to be used against a person's will, and Mediwizards took stringent oaths to that effect when they became licensed. Harry was not a Healer, and hadn't taken any such oath. She pointed her wand at the familiar-looking woman and hesitated. The Bubblehead Charm made it difficult to recognize her, but Rigel was pretty sure on second look that it was Nymphadora Tonks. Sirius might take it amiss if she targeted his cousin specifically, she reflected, and adjusted her aim slightly.

She didn't have a potion on hand, but, in a way, they were surrounded by a very simple one. Rigel spelled water directly into the burly Auror's Bubblehead Charm. Not enough to drown him, but enough, this far underwater, to terrify. It wasn't nice. It wasn't honorable. But it worked.

He thrashed in panic, no doubt thinking his spell had failed, and the Aurors on either side of him turned immediately to help. In the confusion, no one noticed her rope-severing charm until it was too late. Rigel summoned Pansy with a grunt of effort, and it was only the fact that the blonde girl was slightly less dense than Rigel that allowed the summons to work. If Pansy had the greater mass, Rigel would probably have flown toward her instead.

The Aurors did notice their hostage shooting away from them, but Rigel's spell pulled Pansy through the water faster than they could swim. Rigel shot up from behind the wall to catch her and called up a shield that emerged slightly slower than usual in the watery environment. The Aurors shouted something at her, but Rigel couldn't hear them. She didn't have proper ears, and their words didn't travel the same underwater in any case. Before the Aurors could shoot any spells at her, Rigel disillusioned both herself and Pansy, all the while swimming away as quickly as her finned feet would take them. She dropped the shield when she was far enough and twisted sideways to throw off their sense of where she'd gone. Then she stopped moving, letting them drift in the water with only the slightest trail of bubbles from her gills to give away their position. The Aurors looked around and gestured for a time, but it was clear they were not supposed to move far from their remaining captive.

As Rigel drifted upward, Pansy cradled securely in her arms, she saw Tonks carefully draining the water from her comrade's Bubblehead Charm. She wondered with a glance back at Johanna just where Owens was. Delacour had obviously already collected her third item, which meant Rigel really ought to be racing for the surface. The Vow urged her on, but her conscience worried at her. Would the other girl be all right? She wanted to believe the tournament organizers wouldn't really hurt an innocent. They wanted dramatic stakes, to be sure, but the death of a hostage would be too far…wouldn't it?

People had died before in the Triwizard Tournament, though.

Rigel's stomach clenched again. She couldn't just abandon the other girl. The clock above Pansy's head read: 03:34. If Owens were going to show up and claim his girlfriend from the Aurors, he would have had to make an appearance by now. There was no rule against taking someone else's item. Perhaps, if she brought both girls to the surface, she could claim Owens' points, too.

It was the last, brutally mercenary thought that settled the Vow and kept her blood below an uncomfortable simmer as she carefully kicked her way back down toward the ring of Aurors, who were now looking quite alert and annoyed. With no time to spare, she pooled magic into her wand and abandoned subtlety entirely. She sent the strongest Repulsion Jinx she could muster right into the middle of their ranks. Every one of them was taken by surprise as the spell exploded at their backs. They hadn't, evidently, expected her to aim a spell right next to the hostage. Underwater, the Repulsion Jinx looked like an ever-expanding bubble of hot water that propelled all before it—all except Johanna, who was tied securely in place. While the Aurors tumbled arse over kettle in every direction, Rigel made quick work of severing the dark-haired girl's tether and summoning her as well. With Pansy to anchor her, Rigel had more than enough mass to bring the girl securely to her side.

As the clocks moved down from 01:25, Rigel kicked upward with all her might. The surface beckoned, light dawning just ahead, and yet no matter how fast she swam, it didn't seem to be getting any closer. She must have been much farther down than she thought. The girls were light at first, but seemed to grow heavier as the seconds ticked on. Her limbs were tiring, she thought, but as a pain made itself known in her lungs, she realized that wasn't it; rather, her Gillyweed was wearing off.

Thirty seconds. She counted them in her head as she strained to focus on something other than the burning in her lungs, the trembling in her arms and legs. Rigel made it to twenty, and spots crept over her vision. She felt herself twitch against the need to gasp. This wasn't working. She had to get the girls to the surface somehow.

Rigel readied herself to use the last of her strength propelling the two girls upward. If she pushed with everything she had, they might make it, even if the effort sank her own chances. The Vow simmered angrily in her veins, just as something in her rebelled, though it took a fraction of a second to realize it wasn't her.

Are you a witch or not!? Don't just die, stupid!

Dom? Wha—

A spell, the words and shape and feel of the magic, slammed into her conscious mind so hard she saw stars. Ascendio. Ascendio! ASCENDIO!

Her wand reacted, whether to her command or Dom's she didn't think to wonder until later. Rigel clung to the two girls with everything she had as they shot to the surface like a cork coming out of a shaken butterbeer. She gasped, heaved and coughed as she took in water along with the air, then gasped some more. It was several deep breaths before she noticed she was not the only one gasping.

Pansy was flailing, barely treading water as her eyes darted this way and that, a decidedly panicked glaze to them. The American girl was faring slightly better, craning her long neck around worriedly but keeping her head and chest above the lake just fine.

"Pansy, it's all right." Rigel held out a hand to comfort her friend, and Pansy latched on for a moment before letting it go and slapping the water once more in sheer fright.

"Rigel," she gasped. "What on earth—what's going on? Why are you…slimy?"

"We're in the lake, Pan," Rigel said, her voice a bit hoarse from the water she'd swallowed. "The fourth task in the tournament. I had to come get you, but I did, and we're going to be fine now, okay?"

"No," she said brokenly, panting for air. "No, I'm not feeling fine, Rigel. I can't swim very well."

She could see that. Pansy had her chin tilted all the way back to keep her nose and mouth as far from the water as possible, and the school robes she was wearing were only exacerbating the problem. Rigel looked around for help, but of course there was no one. They were in the middle of the lake, and the shore was at least a mile away. Bloody buggering planning on Bagman and Crouch's behalf.

"Hey, Black," Johanna cut in, her American accent thick. "Where's Jacob? What happened to him?"

"I don't know," she said honestly. "I collected you myself because the time clock above your head was almost out."

"The what?" Johanna was still looking around as though Owens might pop up any moment. "Are you saying Jacob is still down there?"

Rigel shook her head impatiently. "I don't know. Let's get to shore and we can find out."

"I'm not leaving him," Johanna protested, her wide grey eyes horrified. "He could be in trouble."

"How can you help if he is?" Rigel asked, trying to be reasonable. Pansy's movements were getting increasingly uncoordinated. "Owens has a monitoring headband, same as me." She gestured to the green band on her forehead. "Everyone on land will know exactly where he is and how he's doing. Please, will you help me get my friend to safety?"

Johanna's expression was torn, but she could evidently see that Pansy was not exaggerating her inability. "Yeah, okay. Listen, girl, you've got to calm down. Understand?"

Rigel could see Pansy gritting her teeth as she replied, a bit breathless. "I am trying. No one told me I would be swimming, however." She made a valiant attempt at slowing her movements to something more controlled, but fear crept into her expression when the more measures strokes caused her to sink a few inches. "Rigel," she stuttered. "I would like to get out of the water now."

So would I, thought Rigel, but barring someone coming along on a broom and lifting us out—hang on; I can do that much.

"Pan, I'm going to levitate you," she said firmly. "Don't struggle." She pointed her wand at her friend and said, "Wingardium Leviosa."

Pansy stilled her arms as Rigel's spell carefully lifted her part-way out of the water. Once she was only in waist-deep, Pansy took several slow breaths and said, "Thank you, Rigel. Here." She took the wrist of Rigel's wand hand in her own to steady the spell. "You can't keep that up forever, though. What are we supposed to do from here?"

Rigel, who was focused on keeping Pansy semi-aloft while treading water herself with her free hand, didn't notice Johanna swimming closer until the American girl tapped her in the forehead sharply.

"Hello? People watching on those giant TV screens?" The girl scowled into the runic array from a foot in front of Rigel and clapped a hand on Rigel's shoulder to keep her from moving away. "Now would be a great time to send someone to come and—"

Her words cut off as a hook jerked all three of them into nonbeing.

They reappeared in the center of the Quidditch pitch, sopping wet and stunned by the shock of having been force-apparated without warning. No, not apparated—she recognized the magic receding into her headband as a portkey. A crowd roared down at them from the stands, and all Rigel could do was stare uncomprehendingly until her wits came back to her. The noise, after an hour of near-silence in the lake, was overwhelming. Rigel wanted to clap her hands over her ears and shut her eyes and make everything disappear, but of course she couldn't. This was the Triwizard Tournament, and she had a role to play.

"I'm going to kill them."

Draco barely paid the words any attention—it was not the first time he'd heard them since Pansy's face had appeared, ghost-white and devoid of all life, in Rigel's transmission mirror. Aldon had said it faintly the first time, then again when Pansy's head broke the surface and they could see how utterly unprepared she'd been to come to in those surroundings. Now, watching her rebuild her dignity piece by piece with trembling pride down on the pitch, the words were almost a growl.

"I mean, I'm really going to—"

"Pansy doesn't need us to kill someone right now," Edmund rumbled. Despite his reserved words, Draco could hear an anger at least as great as Aldon's, maybe greater, running hot in his tone. "She needs to be checked out by a Mediwitch, and then she needs comfort and familiarity and calm."

"I can calmly kill them—"

"Just go see to her, already," Draco snapped. His eyes were fixed on his best friends, and he'd never felt more helpless. He wanted to go to them himself, but didn't trust himself not to explode in a pathetic mess of unresolved impotent fear and rage.

"Why aren't you?" Edmund asked, though he was already moving past Draco out of their box.

"I will in a minute."

"Don't tell me you want to watch Owens try to figure out his third item is already gone," Aldon said, scorn in his voice.

Draco tore his eyes from Rigel just long enough to raze the seventh-year with a look. "I will. In a minute."

They left him there, and Draco rewarded his restraint with a muttered curse. Everything about the fourth task hacked him off. First, Snape lured them away from Rigel right before it started with a story that turned out to be made up specifically to rope Pansy into this blasted nightmare. Of course she had agreed, when the obvious alternative was Draco. Pansy was as protective of them as they were of her. Snape made it sound innocuous. She would sleep through the entire thing, he'd said. No harm would come to her. Except mental and emotional harm weren't factored into the calculation, were they?

Draco let out a sharp breath. He needed to get his shit together. Pansy and Rigel needed his support, not his anger. Well, Pansy not so much, he amended as Edmund and Aldon collected her from the field. They wrapped the soaking girl in blankets and bundled her away to the medic tent. Rigel watched her go until she'd disappeared behind the canvas, the very picture of a concerned beau. Draco wondered if Rigel knew how they had cast him and Pansy. The contrast between Owens and his girl was unmistakable.

Owens. What an idiot. Even now he was swimming back toward the merfolk settlement, both of his other items secured and not a care in the world. Draco wasn't interested in watching that prat swim, though. His emotions thoroughly under control at last, Draco made his own way down from the stands. Rigel was still standing in the middle of the pitch, dripping and probably tempting the mother of all colds. No one had even fetched him a blanket yet.

Draco grabbed two on his way past the mediwitch tent and jogged the rest of the way to where his friend stood. Rigel looked a little lost, though it was obvious he didn't mean to. He'd taken off his headband and the tracking bracelet, but otherwise remained as he had since leaping into the lake.

"Rigel."

The boy turned at the sound of his name, a smile finding easy perch on his face as he caught sight of Draco approaching. "Dray," he said, his voice almost a sigh. "Come to keep me company until the scores are announced?"

"Come to keep you from catching pneumonia, more like," he said, gesturing to the towels in his hands. "Here; you're dripping all over the place and the grass doesn't need watering."

Rigel chuckled as he took a towel and rubbed it over his head quickly. The rest of him was treated the same, and Draco manfully did not watch, even though a voice in his head kept pointing out that this was the most he'd ever seen of Rigel's skin. His friend wore sweats to exercise and always changed in the bathroom. The sight of long, muscular alabaster limbs was almost indecent, somehow. Not that he was looking. Rigel had made his feelings clear—well, mostly clear—on the subject of Draco's attraction and he was trying, Salazar help him, to respect that.

He did note with some distant confusion that nowhere did Rigel carry signs of an unusual skin condition. Then again, perhaps it wasn't visible at the moment. Maybe his friend had applied a glamour for the task. That sounded like something Rigel would do.

"Thanks, Dray. I do feel much warmer now." Rigel let one of the towels hang about his shoulders and secured the other around his waist. Draco was silently grateful, as the distracting way those wet shorts clung to everything was a painful taunt in each accidental glimpse. "So, how'd I do?"

Draco stared at him. "How'd you do? Rigel, how do you think you did?"

"I don't know," Rigel said, shrugging. "I assume Delacour got back before me, since her hostage was already gone when I got to the mercity."

"That's not a word," he began, but then he shook his head. "No, never mind. Rigel, Delacour quit the task as soon as she saw her sister. She'd only collected one of her other items when she got to the settlement, but she took her sister straight to the surface and forfeited the rest of her time."

"Oh." Rigel blinked slowly. "I hadn't thought that the others might get to their hostages first. I supposed in a way I was lucky."

"Lucky." The word came out slightly strangled, despite Draco's best effort to keep it even.

"Mmhm," Rigel said, nodding blithely. "I mean, lucky that I didn't know about Pansy being down there until I'd already found the other two items. If I'd come across her first, I don't know what I would have done."

"You'd have done what Delacour did," Draco said firmly. He was sure of it—Rigel was the guy who put others first, period.

The dark-haired boy frowned uncertainly. "I don't know if I could have," he said softly. "I have to do my best in every task. I can flex a little as long as I still have a good chance at winning, but giving up prematurely…I don't know."

Draco's breath caught as what Rigel was saying sunk in. Could his deal with Riddle have made him choose winning over Pansy? If so, then it could make him choose winning over anything. Somehow, that hadn't fully registered until now. He didn't know what to say in the face of such a horrifying thought.

Rigel was rambling on without his input, however. "Salazar. All the cryptic instructions at the beginning make sense now. That's why there's no time limit: because it's a choice they want us forced to make. Save your friend and forfeit the remaining points, or risk your friend to try and get the other two items before their clock runs out."

"That's what Owens did," Draco said. "He came to the city first, then dithered around and wasted time trying to stall Delacour from getting to her person. It was incredibly idiotic—not only did he waste his own time, but when Delacour realized he was attempting to keep her from her sister, she snapped. Why anyone would purposely nark off a Veela, even a part-Veela, is beyond me."

"So that's why he's still down there," Rigel said, glancing up at the screen. Owens had reached the city, only to find his girlfriend gone. The transmission mirror relayed his conversation with the Aurors, who explained that one of the other champions had escorted his girlfriend to the surface, and that the time on that 'item' had run out in any case. Rigel looked over to where the girl in question was huddled near the medic tent, a troubled frown on her face. "What would have happened when the time ran out?" Rigel asked quietly. "Did they explain while we were down there?"

Draco nodded. "When the clock reached zero, the Aurors were to portkey them out. So you'd lose the opportunity to get points for 'collecting' them, but they wouldn't be at risk of drowning."

Rigel grimaced. "I knew I was being overdramatic. My head wasn't entirely clear. All I could think was that I'd put nothing past Riddle and his little band of psychopaths."

"It came across as noble," Draco said, shrugging uncomfortably. "You look like a saint compared to Owens. And you got all three items, where Delacour has only two."

"She finished faster, though," Rigel said thoughtfully. "How did she get past the Aurors?"

Draco wanted to laugh, but also to cry. "Rigel, she didn't have to 'get past' them. The Aurors weren't there to stop you from taking Pansy."

Rigel stared at him, completely nonplussed. "What? No, they were guarding them."

"From the merpeople," Draco said slowly, "And the giant squid and the grindylows and who knows what else down there—the Aurors were protecting the girls. Delacour swam right up and demanded her sister. They handed her over and even helped untie her."

The pale boy shook his head, bewildered. "Why didn't they say so?"

"They yelled it at you, Rigel. Right after you tried to drown one of them."

Rigel flushed. "The Gillyweed sealed my ears. I couldn't hear anything while I was underwater. Anyway, I wasn't trying to drown him. Just scare him a little."

That explained it. Trust Rigel to think he was meant to fight eight fully grown wizards for his friend's life. "It says something that diplomatic negotiation didn't even occur to you," Draco drawled. Then again, it said about their country's law enforcement that Rigel had succeeded. Twice. "If you had stopped to say hi, incidentally, the Aurors would have explained that your headband would act as a portkey to shore when you surfaced, as long as you and your passengers were all in physical contact." It had been agonizing to watch them flounder in the water trying to figure out how to get Pansy to shore when all they had to do was touch hands for half a second.

Rigel scowled. "Well, if someone you cared about was tied up at the bottom of a lake and eight guys with wands were standing around them, would you ask questions before shooting?"

Draco wisely did not dignify that with an answer. Owens and the squad of Aurors appeared not far from them on the pitch, and Rigel grimaced.

"I suppose I should explain," the boy muttered. "Or cousin Dora will think I'm a psychopath."

He jogged over to where the Aurors were, and Draco let him go alone. It gave him time to watch Owens' girlfriend march across the lawn like a Valkyrie going into battle.

SMACK.

The whole stadium went quiet as the incensed girl slapped her boyfriend across the face. The transmission hadn't stopped on his headband yet, and the sound echoed from the mirror like a crack of thunder.

"YOU LEFT ME! HOW DARE YOU, JACOB? DO YOU KNOW HOW WORRIED I WAS WHEN I SURFACED? ONLY TO BE TOLD THAT YOU WERE STILL SWIMMING AFTER SOME BURIED TREASURE INSTEAD OF TAKING ME TO SAFETY!?"

The whole stadium could hear the argument, but Owens, demonstrating for the nth time that morning what a complete idiot he was, didn't take off his headband before firing back. "I KNEW YOU'D BE FINE."

Draco winced. Even he knew that was not the right thing to say.

"FINE? AT THE BOTTOM OF A LAKE? ANYTHING COULD HAVE HAPPENED TO ME, JAKE. THAT GIANT SQUID COULD HAVE EATEN ME FOR ALL YOU KNOW!"

"THAT'S WHAT THE AURORS ARE THERE FOR," Owens said defensively. Draco thought he was rather missing the point.

"I SHOULD HAVE GONE BACK TO ILVERMORNY INSTEAD OF LETTING YOU CONVINCE ME TO STAY IN THIS MISERABLE, COLD PLACE. WE'RE THROUGH, JACOB. YOU HEAR ME? THROUGH."

Everyone heard her, of course, and Draco was sure the angry little spitfire was well pleased about that. Girls likes a bit of drama when they were upset. Rigel rejoined him after finishing his conversation with Andromeda's spawn.

"Did you avoid a blood feud?" he asked politely.

Rigel grinned. "Tonks thought it was hilarious once I explained. The guy whose Bubblehead I messed with was less than pleased, but he did admit it was a good lesson. Did you know all eight of them are trainees? Apparently, the Head of Training, Auror Moody, volunteered them for the task."

"He must really dislike them," Draco said.

Before Rigel could give his opinion either way, Bagman finally put them all out of their misery and announced, "THANK YOU LADIES AND GENTLEMEN FOR YOUR PATIENCE. WITH THE FOURTH TASK NOW CONCLUDED, IT IS TIME TO HEAR WHAT THE JUDGES HAVE TO SAY! IN TODAY'S TASK, CHAMPIONS WERE TESTED ON THE FOLLOWING CRITERIA: EFFICIENCY IN CONQUERING THE AQUATIC ELEMENT OUT OF TEN POINTS, NUMBER OF OVERALL ITEMS RETRIEVED OUT OF TWENTY-FIVE, AND MORAL FIBER OUT OF FIFTEEN POINTS."

Draco blinked, taken aback. "Moral fiber was only five points in the first task. Now it's more than the magic you used to survive underwater is worth?"

Rigel's face took on a cynical cast as he said quietly, "It's worth more points because Riddle is surer of his ability to predict my actions, now. There's a reason my items were, in order of distance from the starting point, also the order that would prevent me from even having to tackle the morality issue at all."

That was…exactly what Draco would do, if he were trying to rig the tournament for Rigel to win. If anything, Draco was a little grateful that someone was playing to Rigel's strengths. Somehow, he didn't think that was what his friend wanted to hear, though.

"FLEUR DELACOUR FINISHED FIRST WITH TWO ITEMS RETRIEVED IN THIRTY-FIVE MINUTES," Bagman went on. "SHE USED THE BUBBLEHEAD CHARM TO SUFFICIENT EFFECT. FOR CONQUERING THE UNDERWATER ENVIRONMENT, EIGHT POINTS. FOR ITEMS RETRIEVED, NINETEEN POINTS. DUE TO HER DETERMINATION TO RETRIEVE HER LIVING ITEM POSTHASTE, MISS DELACOUR RECIEVES FIFTEEN POINTS FOR MORAL FIBER. THE TOTAL SCORE: FORTY-TWO OUT OF FIFTY."

Delacour looked shocked from where she was huddled around her tiny silver-haired clone. No doubt she'd expected to be slapped with the book for abandoning the task in favor of getting her sister to safety.

"ARCTURUS RIGEL BLACK FINISHED SECOND WITH ALL THREE ITEMS RETRIEVED IN SIXTY MINUTES. HE USED GILLYWEED TO SUPERB EFFECT, NOT ONLY OVERCOMING BUT ADAPTING TO THE AQUATIC NATURE OF THE TASK. FOR THAT, HE RECIEVES FULL MARKS IN THE FIRST TWO CATEGORIES. UPON DISCOVERING THE OMINOUS TIME-LIMIT ASSOCIATED WITH THE LIVING ITEMS, BLACK PUT HIMSELF TO ADDITIONAL TROUBLE IN ORDER TO RECOVER BOTH REMAINING PERSONS FROM THE DEPTHS. FOR MORAL FIBER, THEREFORE, HE ALSO RECIEVES FULL MARKS! MR. BLACK'S TOTAL SCORE IS A RESOUNDING FIFTY POINTS! WELL DONE, MR. BLACK!"

Rigel's mouth fell open. "Full marks? What are they playing at? Delacour doesn't get anything for reaching the hostages before me? And I get extra points for unnecessarily, it turns out, stealing Owens' third item?"

Draco shook his head with a small smile. "You can't pretend to be surprised, Rigel. You already admitted the whole thing is rigged."

"They could be less obvious about it," he grumbled.

The crowd was unabashedly in favor of the verdict. Most had by now heard about the piece that Skeeter published in the paper that morning. There could be no doubt that Rigel Black, the 'charitable champion,' would receive full marks for moral fiber on any scale. Rigel was looking up at the stands with a helpless frown. Draco gave a fond sigh and said, bracingly, "I know this isn't the way you would prefer to win, but don't forget that you do want to win this, Rigel. Be glad that your goals are still on track. You'll have time when it's all over to assuage your conscience in other ways."

Rigel nodded slowly. "Thank you, Draco. I…you're right. It's stupid to be upset that things are going my way."

That wasn't exactly what Draco meant, but Bagman had given up on the cheers dying down and begun to simply shout over the crowd's roar.

"JACOB OWENS FINISHED LAST WITH TWO ITEMS IN SEVENTY-FIVE MINUTES. HE USED THE VERY RARE LIBERESPIRARE POTION TO IMPRESSIVE EFFECT."

Draco saw Rigel's head whip around in shock. "There's no way," the boy muttered, staring at Owens like he's just sprouted wings.

"What—?"

"Tell you later," Rigel said, waving the question away before it could form.

"—WILL RECEIVE TEN POINTS. FOR ITEMS RETRIEVED, TWELVE POINTS. WHILE MR. OWENS REACHED THE LIVING CAPTIVES THE QUICKEST, HE CHOSE TO ATTEMPT RETRIEVAL OF HIS REMAINING TWO ITEMS BEFORE RETURNING TO ESCORT HIS PERSON TO THE SURFACE. AS A RESULT, AND REGARDLESS OF MR. BLACK'S ACTIONS IN RELATION TO HIS LIVING ITEM, MR. OWENS RETURNED AFTER THE TIME LIMIT FOR THAT ITEM HAD EXPIRED. IN TERMS OF THE IMPLIED SCENARIO, HIS LIVING ITEM IS CONSIDERED LOST, AND IN CHOOSING TO PERSUE THE REMAINING TREASURE HE DEMONSTRATED SELF-INTEREST AND AMBITION ABOVE CONCERN FOR THE WELLBEING OF ANOTHER. MR. OWENS WILL THEREFORE RECEIVE NO POINTS FOR MORAL FIBER. HIS TOTAL IS TWENTY TWO POINTS OUT OF FIFTY."

Draco winced as Owens' girlfriend, no longer magnified through the mirrors but nevertheless exceedingly strident, shouted that he was a self-serving snake who deserved to lose the entire tournament.

"Snakes always get a bad name," Rigel said, somewhat tiredly. "Pretty cruel of the organizers to use his girlfriend, in any case. That was asking for this kind of fall out. I'm glad they didn't take Harry, come to think of it."

"It would have been too difficult to move her from America," Draco said with a shrug. "Delacour's sister was already going to be here, since she hasn't missed a task yet, and Owens' heiress was right there for the taking, of course."

"Is Pansy all right?" Rigel asked, his attention drifting to the medical tent now that the scores had been announced. A bit of anger crept back into his expression as he added, "She was trying not to show it, but I could tell she was terrified, Dray."

"She had a bad experience swimming near her parents' estate in France as a child," Draco explained. "They told us she would be asleep through the whole thing, which is the only reason she agreed. I suppose it leant a better sense of drama if the witches awoke when you 'crossed the finish line,' so to speak."

Rigel's eyes found Lord Riddle as he was leaving the judges box. His voice was a dangerous growl as he said, "Then I hope the puppet master is pleased with his little show. He only gets two more, after all."

He was not, precisely, pleased. The last thing he wanted to do after a successful stratagem was sour the day with unpleasantries. The odious chore of reminding his followers exactly where they stood in line was necessary, however. The simpler the wizard, the more often he needed reminding, and he had left this particular correcting too long.

Barty was waiting, as instructed, in the boat house. For a moment, Tom allowed a faint, nostalgic smile to tug at his lips. He'd conducted much business, in his early days on the rise, in this very boathouse. Its walls were witness to things, plans and decisions, and corrections, too, that few still living would be able to relate. He paused inside the door, taking in the twitchy, sullen-faced man staring out the window at the Black Lake.

Despite being a wizard grown, Barty looked much the same as he had that first day, when he'd come to Tom begging like a dog for scraps in Bellatrix's wake. It had been nearly fourteen years since the favor that sealed the boy, now a man, into his service. Fourteen years of loyal subordination, and now this.

At his pointed footstep, Barty spun and dropped into a low bow. "My Lord," he said deferentially. His restless tongue made an appearance as his eyes roved. "Was the task to your liking?"

"It was…surprising, Barty," he said silkily. "Did I not express the desire to have Draco Malfoy stand in for Black's third item?"

Barty twitched and scowled. "The Malfoys have enough pull. Looks better, anyway, to have a pretty girl on the post, doesn't it?"

Tom sneered at the fool's transparent motivations. "I'm aware that the Parkinsons are your closer cousins. No doubt you wanted to share in their prestige, being connected so openly to the popular pureblood champion. Where you miscalculated, Barty, was in forgetting that it was not your decision to make. You work for me. This is my tournament."

"You gave me creative license," Barty whined.

"Too much, it seems." He drew himself up to his full height and said the next words very clearly. "You overstep of late." The silence stretched between them, Barty's fear, growing steadily, a trembling, wind-buffeted thing. Into that silence, he snapped, "Were you behind Greyback's little joy spree in the first task? The blood wall in the second?" The whites in Barty's eyes confessed his sins like a caterwauling charm. The only question he really wanted answered, however, was, "Did you honestly think I wouldn't notice, Barty? That I couldn't perceive how your devotion strays?"

"M-my Lord," Barty stuttered. "I don't—"

"Oh, Barty, you really don't think much of me, even after all our years of association. I. Always. Know." He softened his voice until Barty had to lean closer to catch each syllable. "You should have come to me, when you began to doubt. Did I not arrange personally for your father's disgrace and demotion, that you and others like you might be freed from his oppressive anti-Dark agenda? Have I not been a good lord to you, all these years?"

"You have always pushed for our liberation from the tyranny of discrimination," Barty said carefully. He never could quite cage the whine in the back of his voice. "It's just—change is slow, My Lord. Should we not push harder?"

So that was the problem. Plain, predictable impatience. He resisted the urge to sneer. "Push harder?" he asked, no inflection in his tone.

Emboldened by a lack of swift correction, Barty licked his lips and nodded, half to himself. "Yes, we must strike out boldly. Harder, and faster, too. It is the only way to shake up society—to shake down the forbidden fruit they keep locked away out of fear and take it for ourselves."

"Take care you don't cut down the tree that feeds you while you're at it, Barty."

"But it's working!" Barty burst out. "The masses are paying attention. After the World Cup—"

Tom's temper ignited. "You admit to being one of the masked revelers, too? Idiot child. We have not worked—I have not worked so long for credibility only to allow brash young fools to give into a base desire for anarchy the very hour our victory comes into sight. We are this close, Barty." He could not help but seethe at the uncomprehending mulishness in Barty's eyes. "When Rigel Black wins the Triwizard Tournament, the pureblood argument will be irrefutable. Our political power will solidify under the banner of accepted truth, the way forward for society paved inexorably by us." Barty muttered something resentfully, and Tom made an irritated jerk of his chin. "What was that?"

"It isn't enough," Barty repeated, more firmly. "They should be punished for the way they've treated us. They should bleed."

"Blood will not solve the problem." It took a hard-earned well of fortitude to disguise his exasperation as forbearance. "Don't you think I considered that? It is a pipe-dream. Revolution inevitably leads to uncontrolled depravity with no clear-cut agenda. No nuanced strategy can survive that environment. Chaos rules. The only certain result is that every friend to common decency and morality rallies against us, don't you see?" Tom pinned Barty with all the ice in his gaze. "Tell me you understand this, Barty. I need you, of all people, to see the big picture clearly."

It would be extremely tedious to navigate a sudden change on the tournament planning committee, especially with only two tasks remaining. If the fool would not see reason, however, Tom had every intention of replacing him. He could afford no rogue pieces on his board at this stage in the game.

Barty's face betrayed his struggle, but in the end, he bowed his head. "I understand, My Lord," he said. "You are wise, of course. Your plans never fail. Forgive me."

Tom allowed his uncertainty to fester. "You will renounce these radicals, Barty. No member of the S.O.W. will be party to that pathetic fearmongering campaign. Its leader will be dealt with soon enough," he promised, adding with a thread of steel, "The last thing I want is to lose you to a doomed cause."

Barty gulped. "Yes, My Lord." He bent into a deep bow and said, head hanging, "I don't deserve your mercy."

"That is the nature of mercy," he said. Satisfied that Barty's foolhardy foray into violent protest had been corrected, his mood took a cautious upswing. "The next task will be exactly to my specifications, Barty."

"Yes, My Lord. Whatever you say."

Chapter 12

She finished the fourth task angry and sick with a kind of incomplete vertigo, as though she'd swung too far in one direction and was waiting for the world to pull her back to equilibrium. A perfect score, she thought with no small amount of disgust. Did Riddle want people to realize it was all a farce? Perhaps he didn't care, or perhaps he wanted to make it so overwhelmingly clear who the 'best' competitor was that he didn't mind being brash and heavy-handed about it. Rigel watched the politician climb down from the judges' box with a sneer she could not quite contain. Draco made no comment on her dark expression as they left the pitch together.

"Mr. Black!"

Arranging her face into something less disgruntled, Rigel swung around to face Lugo Bagman as he waved her down on her way through the stadium's exit. "Mr. Bagman," she said. "I suppose you want all this back?" She gestured to the collection of jewelry she still wore from the lake, as well as her headband and tracking bracelet.

He laughed at her words, but the sound was tinged with condescension, as though she was a particularly precocious child. "Just so! I'll take your monitoring band and, yes, the wrist tracker. The golden ring next, if you please. No, the locket you keep."

Her hand paused over the clunky necklace chain and she frowned. "Keep?"

Bagman's broad grin was entirely too anticipatory. "That, Mr. Black, is your clue for the next task."

"Clue?" Draco peered down at the ugly locket. "There haven't been clues for the other tasks."

"Adds an element of intrigue, doesn't it?" Bagman said. "It'll give you something to do until mid-April, too. Each of the champions had a clue hidden in one of their miscellaneous items today. If you uncover the secrets of the item, you'll have an edge in the fifth task."

Rigel's eyes narrowed. "Delacour didn't collect her other items."

Bagman waggled his eyebrows. "Pity for her, but lucky for you, Mr. Black. Now, don't forget your effects—they've been moved to the healers' tent." He clapped her on the shoulder and added, "Great showing today! Keep it up, and you'll make a good many people happy."

She let a scowl bleed over her face as the man walked off. "What's that supposed to mean?" Rigel muttered. Was Bagman a member of Riddle's party too? She hadn't thought so.

"He probably bet on you," Draco said quietly. His nose wrinkled as though he'd smelled something unpleasant. "Father says Ludo Bagman's gambling problem means he's always in someone's debt."

Rigel blinked. It hadn't occurred to her that people other than the Ministry and Riddle could be making money off her competing in the tournament. The thought made an already tiresome undertaking feel dirty as well. Wanting nothing more than to shower the residual slime from her skin, she made a bee-line for the medic tent and found Pansy being escorted out under the combined glowers of Rookwood and Rosier.

"Pan, are you all right?" she asked at once. "I'm sorry about all this." She'd never dreamed that her friends would be directly endangered by the tournament, but it seemed Riddle knew no boundaries when it came to the show he sought.

The blonde girl nodded with a weak smile. She looked nearly mummified by the number of towels that were wrapped around her. "Of course. Thank you for returning me to shore." Before Rigel could do more than nod, Pansy was walking toward the castle. "Forgive me, but I'm going to lie down for a while. Well done today, Rigel."

Draco and Rigel exchanged a look. "Maybe you should go with her," Rigel suggested. "She doesn't really seem all right." It riled her blood all over again to see her normally composed friend shivering like a kitten. Draco's mouth twisted. He gave her a look that said he didn't want to leave her, but Rigel gave him an insistent nudge. "Give Millie a heads up, too, if Pansy would rather be shut in her room."

Unable to argue with good sense, Draco sighed. "Come find me in the common room after you've changed. We can break another deck of Theo's Exploding Snap cards or something."

She felt her mouth hitch up on one side. "Sounds fun."

They parted, and Rigel continued alone into the healers' tent. It wasn't empty. Owens stood to one side, shirtless, next to a small table stacked with clothes. The taller boy glanced over as she ducked inside, and as she made to turn around with a mumbled apology, he barked out a laugh.

"Modest? I didn't expect that from someone like you."

Rigel hesitated, then gave a casual shrug. "As long as you're not bothered." She affected disinterest and strode past him to pick her clothes out of the pile. The over-robe she shrugged on over her swimming attire and the rest she gathered up to carry with her. Her pocket watch tumbled out of her shirt and fell to the earth with a muffled thump. She bent over to retrieve it, but Owens got there first.

He'd shucked his swimming trunks and pulled on a pair of sweats, but hadn't yet reclaimed his shirt. She averted her eyes as she held out a hand to take the watch, but when he didn't immediately relinquish it, she was forced to look up with a frown. There was fire in his gaze, again, and she felt her hackles raise automatically to meet the silent threat.

"My watch, please."

The American boy's fingers clenched over the rounded edge so tightly she saw his knuckles go white, but then he fairly shoved it at her. "Just dripping in Slytherin heirlooms, aren't you, Black?" His eyes lingered on the ugly locket still around her neck.

She let her face go slack with genuine surprise as she slipped the watch back into her robe pocket with careful fingers. "I'm not sure what you mean by that, Owens. Not everything with snakes on it is related to Salazar Slytherin."

Owens' face washed from dark anger to something more snide, and his voice was laced in irritation as he said, "Who do you think you're kidding?"

If he was going to demand answers from her, then she could do the same. "Where did you get the Liberespirare potion?" she asked, eyes watching his annoyed expression closely.

"Maybe I made it," Owens said, his sneer shifting closer to a smirk.

"It takes two people to brew," she told him. "I can't think of many here at Hogwarts who have the skill to help you, much less the inclination."

Owens laughed, but there was no humor in it. "I have more friends around here than you'd think. What's it to you?"

"Just professional curiosity," she said, turning away with a lift of her shoulders that was stiffer than she'd intended.

"Well, keep it to yourself. You should know better than to ask such questions at this stage in the game. We can't afford any hiccups now."

Rigel whirled back at the implication behind that statement, but Owens had left the tent. She shoved her feet into her shoes with more force than necessary. What in Merlin's name was Owens trying to convey? 'We', he'd said, as though they were on the same side. Rigel replayed everything she'd noticed about Jacob Owens and had to wonder how much of his performance in the tournament might have been just that—an act. He had some impressive connections to come up with a Liberespirare on short notice, and to imply that he was playing the same game she was…if taken out of context of the literal game they were playing, it sounded as though he was playing for higher stakes than advertised, too.

Lord Riddle does not gamble unless all the odds are stacked in his favor.

Rosier's words came back to her, as they had numerous times over the course of the tournament. A number of the candidates had been hand-picked, that much she knew already. It was not a stretch to think that others beside herself might have made additional deals on the side. As Bagman had so helpfully pointed out, more interests than just the Ministry's and Riddle's were at play in a spectacle this big.

The feeling of vertigo hadn't gone away. If anything, her sense of unbalance was growing stronger.

Rather than probe the locket in the common room where someone could get hurt, Rigel took it to her Head of House's office that evening. If Snape was surprised to see her so soon after the fourth task, he didn't show it. He merely conjured her a comfortable armchair before his desk and gestured for her to sit.

She sank into the chair, acutely aware of every ache in her muscles now that they had a chance to relax, and pulled the golden necklace from her robe pocket. Sliding it across the desk toward him, she said, "This is supposedly my clue for the next task. Considering the source, I thought I should get it checked for traps before I try to open it."

"That's unusually prudent of you," Snape commented, taking out his wand and leaning closer to peer at the locket without touching it.

Rigel acknowledged that truth with a tilt of her head, which sent drops of water from her freshly-showered hair down her neck. She shivered. "Owens suggested it was a Slytherin heirloom. It seemed preposterous that the Ministry would send such a valuable museum piece to the bottom of the Black Lake, but the gems on the front could be an 'S,' I suppose. I reckoned you would know either way."

Snape levitated the locket to his eye-level with an economic flick of his wand, an intent but closed expression on his face. "Slytherin did have a locket—he wears it in his portrait in the Great Hall. This could merely be a convincing replica, however."

That made more sense than risking the damage of something so precious. "Symbolic, then. I wonder if the objects the other champions collected had any greater significance."

"As Delacour never collected hers, that would be difficult to confirm," Snape murmured. His eyes narrowed. "Owens did have a golden cup, in addition to a ring similar to the one you collected. Assuming the cup was Hufflepuff's famed Chalice of Truth, Delacour's clue could be either something of Ravenclaw's or Gryffindor's." He sneered, adding, "That great hulking sword would be difficult to swim with, but Ravenclaw's diadem would be the right size. It has long been thought lost or part of a private collection, however." The Potions Master tapped his long fingers on the desk. After a considerable pause, he gathered his thoughts and tucked them away where Rigel couldn't see them. "Regardless, while this necklace is undeniably enchanted, it does not appear to be cursed."

He plucked it from the air and turned it over in his palm a few times. The clasp didn't open at his touch, but Snape wasn't surprised. "Locked with Parseltongue, no doubt," he said with a nod. "If you'd like to open it now, I'll ensure nothing nasty escapes."

Rigel stared at the innocuous-looking piece of jewelry as Snape set it back on the desk between them. "Can you tell how it is enchanted?"

Her professor shook his head slowly. "Slytherin's original locket was purported to have a number of powers. Clear-sightedness, for one, as well as the ability to forewarn its owner of threats or ill-intentions. If this is that locket, it would explain the exceptionally strong magical signature buried deep within it. I doubt it would be possible to access the locket's true power without being a direct blood descendent of Slytherin's line, however. My examination did reveal a rather tacky illusion spell that has been clumsily attached to the locket very recently, but that magic is not malicious. Likely, it is the clue you seek."

She cast her own awareness out toward the locket, to see if she could sense what he meant. There was something clinging to it in her mind's eye, a thin, glittering strand of magic that felt like tinsel and moved with a fluttering ripple. Rigel tried to mentally filter through it, to sense what lay beneath, but all she got was the slow, undulating presence of something before it twisted away from her grasp. She eyed the piece of jewelry with new respect; whatever magic lay not-quite-dormant within, it had to be seriously subtle to curl away from a direct probe.

The tinsel-strand of magic seemed to wave frantically as she pulled back her awareness, desperate to be activated. With a nod to Snape, Rigel focused her gaze on the emerald 'S' and hissed, "Open."

With a snick that sounded too contrived to be real, the locket creaked slowly open. She caught a glimpse of a bright eye blinking out from one of the doors before smoke obscured anything about the inside of the locket. Thick and grey, it poured up from the gaudy neckpiece to hover in the air between them, churning in a way that reminded her of something. Before she could place the memory, the smoke coalesced into a sphere and a ghostly voice emerged, dripping ominous verse in cadence.

"A fortnight past the equinox,

three heroes will ascend.

Their path is clear; their way is not,

confusion through them wends.

If hearts are hale and minds robust,

their bodies strive for height,

But all ascension to be made

relies on clearest sight."

They listened to it twice in silence before Rigel shut the locket. "I hate riddles," she said with an annoyed sigh.

"Certain you aren't biased?" Snape drawled. He gestured to the necklace dismissively, adding, "In any case, this is a clue, not a true riddle. 'Riddle' implies an answer that may be deduced by an average listener solely from its own content. This drivel relies on specific context."

She clenched her toes in her boots slowly, turning the words of the poem over in her head. "It's definitely not a prophecy…right?"

"It matches no known prophetic structure," Snape said at once. He sounded absolutely certain, though Rigel hadn't thought he had any interest in the study of Divination.

Rigel was grateful for his sureness, whatever the source. She moved on to dissecting the clue itself. "When it says 'clearest sight,' do you think that means we're going to be blindfolded? It would explain 'their path is clear; their way is not.'"

"Possible, though a simple blindfold lacks the element of macabre drama we've come to expect." Her Head of House turned his gaze back to the gaudy necklace. "Don't forget that the item itself is part of the clue. Slytherin's locket was known to lend its wearer clear-sightedness."

"I can't access the locket's powers if I'm not an heir. If I'm not meant to literally use it, then it must have symbolic significance," she said. "The other Founders' items are similar in theme, right?" She cast about in her mind, trying to remember her history lessons. "Hufflepuff's cup lets the possessor read the true intentions of those around them, and Ravenclaw's diadem gives wisdom, which is a sort of clear-mindedness, I suppose. What about Gryffindor's sword?"

Snape's mouth twisted unpleasantly, but he admitted, "It imbibes only that which strengthens it."

"Clarity of body!" she exclaimed. "Together with the others, that's clarity of mind, heart, and eyes, all of which are mentioned in the clue. The task must contain an element that is designed to trick us."

"'Confusion through them wends'…" Snape murmured. After a moment, his eyes widened and a smirk drew itself across his face in a slash. "A potion."

Rigel blinked, a surprised smile curling at her lips. "I'm an idiot," she breathed. A potion could easily devastate a person's clarity of mind, body, heart, or sight. Which would be affected, though? It could be any potion, and they hadn't been told what items would be allowed in the fifth task yet. She could carry a bezoar, but it might not be a poison. A thought pulled her up short and she frowned at Snape. "Has Riddle asked you to brew for this task?"

His smirk dropped away like a stone falling from a cliff face. "He has not. There is more than a month until the task, however. When the request comes, I will inform you."

She nodded in agreement, wondering when the idea of pursuing underhanded means to win the tasks had stopped bothering her. It was as though the closer she drew to the finish line, the faster her periphery shrank until, some moments, the tournament was all she could see.

The first Saturday after the fourth task was a Hogsmeade weekend, and Rigel's friends wouldn't let her spend it cooped up in the castle. She had endured their pointed comments in regards to the healthy need for relaxation through dinner the night before, and by the time the post arrived the next morning, she was close to giving in.

"It's been so long since we all went together, hasn't it?" Pansy said idly, stirring her tea in precise circles.

"Usually Theo has a date and Rigel has some project that keeps him from coming," Millicent agreed.

Theo swallowed his mouthful of scone and said, "I'm free this time."

All eyes turned to Rigel and an expectant silence descended. She opened her mouth to give an impenetrable excuse, but an owl's insistent beak at her elbow distracted her. She took a letter from its leg, noting Archie's writing on the front of the envelope. Draco cleared his throat from beside her and she looked up to see her friends still waiting. She sighed. "I should be preparing for the next task."

"Which you haven't explained to us yet," Millie muttered.

"You just want to brew some more," Draco accused, half amused, half exasperated. "You know we can tell when you come to breakfast smelling like a sewer, right?"

Tahiil's eyes widened. "That smell is you? I thought perhaps this table sat over an open drain."

Several people nearby snorted into their pumpkin juice, and Rigel's eyebrows rose in her own defense. "I can't imagine why you'd want a smelly fellow like myself to accompany you in a closed carriage to Hogsmeade," she said with dignity. Her composure was somewhat undermined when the same owl flapped up to her head and raked her short hair in its talons. With a hiss, she extracted herself and relieved it of its second letter before it could do further damage. She eyed the owl mistrustfully. "Did he tell you to do that?"

The owl gave her an affronted glare and appropriated one of her potato skins in revenge for the insinuation. Rigel frowned down at the two envelopes she'd liberated. The first was thick, as though a great deal of parchment was stuffed inside, and the second was considerably lighter, though it had 'Rigel Black' in red ink on the outside. Not for opening at the table, then. Her curiosity eating at her, she didn't hear Blaise's question until he repeated it.

"I said, at the rate you've been brewing, you're bound to need replacement supplies soon."

She nodded slowly. "That's true, but I have a fairly regular owl order from the apothecary in town. I won't run out of anything."

"Isn't it better when you can pick out the ingredients yourself and ensure the quality?" Millicent tried.

"If I received inferior ingredients, I would simply send them back." After a pause, she added, "Or donate them to the student storeroom."

"Oi! Is that why our potions never work in class?" Theo said, outraged.

"That's like asking if the reason Pan can't bake a pie is because she's not using top-shelf flour," Rigel said musingly.

Pansy sniffed at her from across the table. "You won't dissuade us by being rude, Rigel."

"We only have a couple Hogsmeade weekends left this year," Draco reminded her.

"You've been brewing so much in your lab we hardly see you," Millicent added.

"It's only one afternoon—"

"You're more than prepared for whatever they throw at you next task—"

"Think of your poor, lonely friends—"

"All right! Okay. You all win." Rigel blew out an amused breath. "I'll take the day off from brewing and task prep."

A localized cheer went up from their section of the table, and Rigel resisted the urge to roll her eyes. Her friends certainly thought they were amusing. She stood, brandishing the letters. "I'm going to go sort through my post before we leave, then. See you all at the carriages."

She took the letters to her lab, thinking she might as well pick up her list of ingredients that were running low while she was at it. It really was more satisfying to pick them out for herself at the apothecary.

Treeslider lifted his head as she unlocked the door. "Ssspeaker isss back with food?"

She pulled a wrapped mouse from Binny out of her pocket and smiled at the snake's pleased hiss of approval. Knowing he didn't like moving from the stone she kept hot with a Warming Charm, she set the mouse where he could reach it and turned to the letters.

The thicker packet turned out to be less like a letter and more like a roughly-drafted Mastery thesis. Hermione had evidently asked Archie to pass on her notes on the Fade. Rigel had been anticipating something substantial, having enough experience with the formidable Miss Granger to expect nothing less than strictly organized brilliance. Still, she had underestimated the girl.

Dozens of pages, meticulously numbered and organized into chapters, were bound by string and accompanied by a neat title page with a note requesting that Rigel check the information for discrepancies. Rigel could honestly say she'd never seen a sheaf of notes so large it required its own table of contents. She set the packet carefully aside for later reading and moved onto the next envelope, which contained two separate letters. She saw immediately why Archie had forwarded them in red. Both were addressed to Harry Potter, one in Leo's easily recognizable handwriting and the other in a vaguely familiar script that took her a moment to place.

She started with Leo's, a smile on her lips that faded as she absorbed his news.

Harry,

How are you? Probably buried in schoolwork and brewing too much for Krait besides. I hope you don't exhaust yourself this term. I worry when you're away, probably because whenever you come back you look like you've climbed through hell to get here. I know, I know—you resent it when I fuss. I sound like an old grandma, but it seems as though the world is growing less predictable every day.

The Ministry raided the Lower Alley shops near Diagon, again. No mention of what they were looking for this time, beyond a vague 'suspicious persons.' Any person could act suspicious when you invade their homes and businesses on a whim. I shouldn't complain about the Aurors to you, but I hate to let the others see how helpless I feel. Some things I can control; so many more I can't.

I'm dancing around what I really wrote to tell you. I'm sorry to bear nothing but bad news, Harry. The Carpathian Clan snapped last night. No one knows what set them off—maybe the raids, so close to their coven, maybe something else—but the Carpathian vampires moved in force against the Shrouds sometime just after dusk. The damage was localized to the Lamia Lodge, for what consolation that's worth. Half of it burned, and the Strigoi Shrouds lost several of their coven to the fire. Gavril was caught in the fighting and injured by a queer device. He's still alive—undead, that is—but considerably weakened. I know you are on friendly terms with him and thought you ought to hear it from me. I don't know when he may recover. Count Aurel believes his second to be affected by a strange sort of poison, though he has not ever encountered a substance able to lay a vampire low in such a way. When there is more news, I will send it straight away.

Until then, please take care of yourself. Just come home to the alleys, whatever it takes. I'll feel better when I see you safe for myself.

Leo

She read the letter twice, wringing it for every drop of information. A raid in the alley wasn't unusual, but the Carpathians breaking the code to attack their rival coven unprovoked? The vampire covens wouldn't fight unless tensions were ratcheted sky high—they prized their immortal lives too preciously to be wasted over anything less than grave insult or violent desperation. It was difficult to believe that one Ministry raid could push them over the edge so quickly.

Conscious of the group of Slytherins waiting for her in the Entrance Hall, Rigel sped through the second letter with only a hint of the usual amusement that came when she imagined Caelum Lestrange deigning to write his halfblood pen pal a letter.

Brat,

I don't doubt you're languishing in some underfunded American laboratory at this very moment. Never fear, I am here to provide word of the civilized world to you. I have, you will find, completely mastered your Shaped Imbuing method. I daresay I have improved it slightly, in fact. I may be able to find time this summer, in between preparing for my Mastery exam and writing my thesis, to give you a few pointers.

Master Whitaker has more than prepared me for Mastery, of course, but he advises that it does not do to ascend the ranks too quickly. It gives the wrong idea about one's priorities. Thus, I shall wait the traditional length of an apprenticeship before getting the formalities of Mastery out of the way. I suppose there is always some small improvement to be made, though I fear I shall soon surpass what my Master can hope to teach me. It is not surprising; true talent always rings through the noise. Just think of how quickly I was able to master your quaint brewing trick—even my father was impressed. He has a colleague with an idle curiosity regarding the strange process who had mentioned it to him, and you should have seen his face when I told him I could replicate it flawlessly. He should expect no less from the Lestrange Heir, of course, but you understand that outsiders to the art often underestimate even its most gifted practitioners.

One day, potioneers will get the recognition we deserve. When the world sees the true power of my brews, my genius will be undeniable. Don't fall into your own cauldron before I have a chance to show you my improvements.

C. Lestrange

She tucked the letter away with the others, a mixture of feelings in her stomach that wasn't easy to sort through. He hadn't said anything about the Liberespirare potion, though she couldn't imagine why Caelum of all people would have reason to give a rare and expensive potion to a muggleborn American. Where would they even have met? It was exceedingly unlikely, but Rigel was starting to suspect conspiracy behind every coincidence.

On the other hand, there was an undeniable warmth at what Lestrange had not said—he hadn't said thank you, but she could tell that's what he meant. The part of her that had bullied the arse into dinner at their student showcase was glad that his parents were finally recognizing his talents, and that the Shaped Imbuing training had helped him claim some of the respect he felt he was missing in their eyes.

She did wonder whom Lestrange Sr. had heard about the process from. As the inventor, she'd expect that anyone with questions would come to her, but there was every chance that certain members of society would be too proud to approach a halfblood, no matter their academic interest in the subject. Probably it was someone else in Riddle's Party, though if that was the case, Professor Snape could have answered their questions, too.

Rigel double-checked her shopping list against her existing stores, bid a sleepy and full Treeslider farewell, and left for the Entrance Hall. Despite Caelum's odious manner of attempting to impress her, she was curious to know how he had 'improved' the Shaped Imbuing process. A wicked grin crossed her lips as she imagined him writing his Master's thesis about her new brewing process. She would never let him live it down.

They had to split into two carriages, and Rigel automatically turned to follow Draco and Pansy, but Millicent forestalled her with a touch to her elbow. Blaise held open the other carriage's door with a small smile, and Rigel climbed in, bemused.

When the thestrals lurched into motion, Millie pulled a green orb from her pocket. "I did it," she said, just a little smug.

Rigel brightened, academic enthusiasm pricked like a the ears of a werewolf by the call of its own kind. "That was fast, Millie. Great job. Hang on—" She took her bag from the floor of the carriage and rummaged through it until she found her own imbued medi-mini. "Take this, and mix the two up behind your back."

Millicent took the green orb from Rigel with a small frown. "Is that the same one from before? How long ago did you imbue this? Mine don't stay green for more than a couple of days."

Rigel blinked at her. "I…don't remember. Mine just stay that way."

"Indefinitely?" Blaise leaned forward to catch Rigel's surprised gaze. "That is quite unusual, I think. Mine will fade eventually, too, as the magic slowly breaks up and disperses back into the air."

"I thought the medi-minis were designed to trap the magic in the orb." That was the whole point, after all.

"Yes, for a time, but the runes that trap imbued magic into these training tools aren't particularly potent," Blaise told her. He took out a small notebook and jotted down a sequence. "See? It's just these five, plus a few to make the imbued magic non-reactive."

Rigel wasn't on Blaise's level with runes, but she knew enough to agree with his assessment. Magic had a natural half-life once it was separated from a wizard's core. Just as potions had expiration dates, no spell lasted forever. Structure, commonly provided by runes, patterns, or other ingredients, helped—the more complex, the better, which was why big, long-lasting magical projects were so incredibly difficult to engineer. Even wards designed to last centuries had to be renewed with fresh magic after a time—as Blaise said, it eventually would escape its structure and merge with the atmosphere, released back into the world, as some put it.

She'd simply thought the medi-minis had a complex enough magical structure to trap her magic for several years. Rigel turned the problem over in her mind. If Blaise and Millicent were using the same type of medi-minis, and theirs only lasted a few days…

"Either you are imbuing significantly more magic into your orbs or your magic has an additional source of structure that ours does not," Blaise said succinctly.

Rigel pressed her lips together. "I stop when it turns green." That left only the latter explanation. "My magic has always been…different."

"You used to talk about it as though it was sentient," Millicent recalled slowly.

"It is," she said. At the look Blaise and Millicent exchanged, she sighed. "I know how that sounds. I've gone deeper than most people in my Occlumency study, though, and I've seen it. I've interacted with it, and it interacts back with me."

Blaise spoke as though he was choosing his words carefully. "A reaction to stimuli is not necessarily sentience."

"And if I said I've witnessed it acting independent of my conscious will?"

"Some people would say that sounds like possession," Millicent said quietly. "I'm not saying that," she added quickly. The dark-haired girl wet her lips and took a slow breath. "But some people might. If they heard about it."

Rigel grimaced. "I don't tell people, generally. This might affect our experiment, though." The unspoken –and I trust you both was heavy in the close space between them.

"I thought you merely wanted to know whether you could recognize your magic after it was separated from your core," Blaise said.

"That's step one," Rigel said distractedly. She didn't know if the experiment would be useful at all if her magic was going to be such a skewed variable. "What I really want to know is whether I can reabsorb magic after it's been separated from my core."

Millicent spluttered. "What, call a spell back into your wand?"

Blaise hummed in interest. "That would have astounding applications. I've never heard of such a practice—a kind of reverse-imbuing?"

"Something like that," Rigel said. "I know it's not normally possible—once your magic takes on a foreign structure, it changes the signature too much to be readily identifiable as yours. At that point, once it's been shaped into a spell or a potion, it definitely can't be reabsorbed. The medi-minis don't shape your magic, exactly, though. They just trap it, so its signature stays pretty much the same, until it breaks up over time, I suppose. What I want to know is whether that means that as long as it hasn't broken up yet, it can be reintegrated into a person's core."

"To do that, you'd have to not only be able to identify it as yours, but be able to manipulate it when it's already outside of your body, too," Blaise said quickly.

"That's step two," Rigel shot back, a grin tucked into her cheek. It turned a little sour as she added, "It's going to be more difficult to determine general limits to the theory if my magic is freakishly keeping its signature structure longer than other people's, though."

Millicent shook her head, looking a little overwhelmed. "How did you come up with such a thing?" she asked faintly.

"With Occlumency," Rigel explained. "I can separate parts of my magic from the majority of my core in my mindscape, and whenever I go to re-merge them, they sort of snap together, like a smaller magnet meeting a larger one. I started wondering how far I could carry that phenomena from the physical core."

"That's quite a leap," Blaise said. "It's brilliant. Can you imagine being able to store magic, even for a short period of time, and reabsorb it on demand—say, right before a duel? Anyone could become more powerful."

"I don't know that it's possible for a person's core to hold more than its normal level of magic," Rigel said apologetically. The natural storage limits of a core could not be significantly stretched, according to most scholars. "It might be useful to replenish your magic quickly if you were very tired, though."

"Is that what you're thinking of using it for?" Millicent asked. "If it works, that is."

Rigel tilted her head. How much should she say? "Sort of. I've also been reading about different rituals for transferring magic. In most cases, once magic is moved from one person to another, the original person loses their affinity for it and can no longer sense it."

Blaise nodded easily. "Because the core of the recipient converts the magic according to their own core's mechanics. It takes on the signature of whoever's core it resides within."

"What if it didn't, though?" Rigel said. "I read about a case where the original magic retained just enough characteristics from its original owner to cause resonance-like symptoms whenever the donor and recipient were in physical contact."

The dark-skinned boy narrowed his eyes sharply. He whipped a quill and ink out of his pockets and began jotting into his notebook. "Do you have a reference for that?"

Rigel nodded. "I got it from Dumbledore. I'll get you a copy of what I have, if you're interested."

"I'm fascinated," Blaise murmured. "There are so many implications…I see now why you'd take the time from the tournament to continue looking into this. It's amazing that no one else is studying this."

"Maybe they are," Millicent said. "It's not as though the international wizarding community is known for its stellar cross-border academic cooperation."

Rigel made a noise of agreement. "Most archives are poorly organized, too. Even the library here is difficult to navigate for any but the most basic of school-level assignments. There's every chance that someone has stumbled across this phenomenon before and simply didn't do a good job of promoting their findings."

Blaise shrugged with equanimity. "Then you're still the first discoverer, as far as the general public is concerned."

"I'd rather not re-invent the wheel just to claim the copyright," Rigel said dryly.

Millicent patted her knee sadly. "Our Rigel is a hopeless academic purest. He probably wants the knowledge for its own sake or something."

She made a face. "I'm not a Ravenclaw. I want the knowledge so I can do something with it."

"What will you do, then? You still haven't said," Millicent pointed out.

"This is just a stepping stone. If I can confirm what circumstances exactly allow a person to absorb—or reabsorb—magic, then maybe I can unlock the mystery behind why some people can't." She saw Millicent's eyes go wide, then shutter with a grief that was intensely private. Rigel lowered her voice to something gentler. "If we can analyze the way magic is integrated in and out of a core to the extent of being able to manipulate it, maybe…we could give it back to those who've lost it."

"You think you can cure the Fade?" Millicent's question was bitter, but not entirely dismissive.

"Not alone. And not just the Fade. There are a number of conditions that involve a disorder of the magical core. Seifer's Syndrome. Squibhood. The truth is, we don't fully understand what our healthy cores are doing right, so how can we know how to fix it when it goes wrong? I want to help solve this aspect of the problem, if I can." Rigel didn't want to give her friend unfounded hope, but she did think there was a connection there that hadn't been drawn yet. In all the research on the subject, she didn't think anyone was currently approaching the question from the angle that puzzled her the most.

Infants with the Fade lost magic somehow and weren't able to produce enough to counteract it. What if there was a way for them to reabsorb it? If the magic could be trapped before it lost its signature, or if it was possible to artificially mimic that signature…well, it was several jumps in logic from where she currently stood, but the only way to know for sure was to leap and see where she landed.

Blaise put his notebook away and cleared his throat. "It's a tall order, and it isn't going to fill itself," he said. "Let's see if this experiment works, to start."

Millicent put the medi-minis behind her back and juggled them randomly for a moment before presenting them to Rigel in closed fists.

Rigel flexed her magical awareness across the carriage, feeling and dismissing the bright return off her friends' magical cores in favor of focusing on the much smaller distillations of magic that sparked in Millie's hands.

Both fire-formed spheres were restless and warm. With the basic information the first few returns carried back to her, she couldn't definitely differentiate them. She needed a more detailed look, so Rigel brought her focus fully to bear on the two balls, blocking out the movement of the carriage, the hoofbeats on the ground outside, even the soft sound of her own breath. She let it all fade away, her magical awareness the sole lens through which she refracted every mental beam of attention at her disposal.

Hey, what are you—

Not now, Dom.

She needed absolute concentration to understand in minutia what her magical awareness had to tell her. Faster and faster she pulsed her magic toward the balls, getting quicker and stronger returns as she reached the peak of her rhythm. Gradually, with increasingly nuanced returns, the two spheres began to sharpen in her mind's eye.

The one on the left held a simmering sort of heat, like oil bubbling in a cauldron. In the ball on the right, she found the familiar warmth of a full-throated sun and smiled. Buoyed by success in the first stage, she transitioned from passively perceiving the signatures to attempting to fling her will itself toward the medi-mini, as an arrow was flung toward a target.

It was nothing like controlling the magic in her veins. She could feel the magic in the ball, but exerting the force of her will on it felt like trying to move a boulder with only her mind. There was nothing directly connecting her to the imbued magic, no pathway through which she could channel her resolve.

With only a burgeoning headache to show for her mental effort, Rigel flared her magic toward the ball again in frustration. As before when she used her magical awareness, a portion of it bounced off the sphere and beamed back to her, but this time, the ball twitched—the barest of movements that was nevertheless so surprising that Rigel snapped out of her meditative trance with a gasp.

"—bloody nonresponsive—Rigel! Are you all right?"

She blinked spots away from her vision, and felt a hand move away from her shoulder. Blaise retreated from her personal space, a worried look in his eyes, and Millicent snapped at her from across the seat.

"Rigel, what in Salazar's name was that?" Millie demanded, her usual calm tone an octave higher.

Rigel made to speak, and her jaw creaked as it unclenched. With a wince, she massaged it as she panted, "Did you see it move?"

"It? The medi-mini? Rigel, you were so deep in that trance you stopped breathing. Forget the experiment; are you all right?"

"Where did you go?" Blaise asked quietly, his eyes intent.

Belatedly, she realized she was breathing heavily and dizziness had hold of her vision. Rigel caught her breath and shook her head in confusion. "I've meditated for hours at a stretch before and never stopped breathing. I—I'm not sure why this time would be different. I was just focusing my attention on the medi-minis." A smile crossed her face as she recalled, "I did it, though. I can recognize my own magic. When I get enough details, it's easy to tell the difference, even though on the surface, with a hazier picture, they seem fairly similar. I'm sure I felt it move, at the end," she added excitedly. "Are you sure you didn't see anything?"

Millicent's face was set into a deep scowl. "Is this the kind of shite you make Pansy and Draco deal with all the time? No wonder they want to strangle you so often."

Rigel sat back against the seat. "I don't think I've ever stopped breathing in front of them before," she defended. "I suppose…I did suppress the sound of my breathing so I could focus better."

"That's a scary level of mental control," Blaise said, almost curiously. "You must be very good at Occlumency indeed, if your unconscious mind took the re-prioritization of your conscious attention as a direct suggestion."

As though on cue, Dom's voice came roaring back into her head. —imbecilic, self-destructing fleshbag! Do you think I want to perish in this magic forsaken—

Rigel grimaced and nudged a silent apology his way. She'd have to explain later, when he'd calmed down. "Sorry if I alarmed you," she offered her friends. "I will have to think about how to avoid that next time, but—"

"Next time?"

"—I definitely think I felt the medi-mini move. If I can expand on that, then it may be possible to manipulate magic with an in-tact magical signature after it has lost its initial connection with a wizard's core." Rigel looked between the two of them with satisfaction. They didn't immediately return her enthusiasm, but she supposed it was hard for them to understand; experimentation was always dangerous. This was less scary than almost blowing up a cauldron of unstable ingredients, and that happened nearly once a session in her free-brewing lessons. She thought the realization that wizards might be able to exert control over their magic long after it had lost a direct connection with one's core was certainly worth being a little out of breath.

The carriage pulled to a stop, and for an awkward moment, no one spoke. Finally, Millicent said, "You can have this back." She handed over the medi-mini that contained Rigel's magic. "If it really does retain your magical signature, you should probably be more careful about who you hand those to. And Rigel—don't ever ask me to be part of your experiments again. I'm glad you're trying to research this aspect of—of the problem." Her voice hitched briefly, but she pressed on. "I don't think I want to watch you go any further, however. Please be more careful in the future."

Millie held Rigel's gaze until she offered, "I will."

Millicent's mouth hitched ruefully and she exited the carriage. Blaise paused a moment to say, "You aren't a very good liar, Rigel," before following after her.

Rigel took a moment to examine her conscience. She felt mildly guilty for worrying her friends, but it was muted by the thought that she couldn't possibly have anticipated that particular experiment being dangerous. Meditation wasn't intrinsically dangerous—how could she have known to be careful of drawing her mental faculties away from vital functions when it had never happened before? Now she knew. Now, she could be more careful in the future.

With a nod to cement that intention, Rigel climbed out of the carriage to find Pansy waiting for her. "The others went on to Honeydukes," Pansy told her. "I thought you and I could go to the apothecary while they brave those hideous crowds."

Rigel raised an eyebrow. "I can pick up whatever supplies you need, Pan; I know you detest the preservative smell."

Her blonde friend sniffed and looped her hand through Rigel's arm in subtle rebuke. They began to walk slowly up the street. "I certainly do not shop for my potions supplies in person, Rigel. I would like to accompany you because I miss you." Pansy looked seriously into Rigel's face for a long moment. "You've been so busy this year. I can't help but feel that…we are drifting apart."

Rigel's forehead creased. Had she been distant? She hadn't felt any more removed than usual from her friends' lives. Her every waking moment was occupied with a task or activity, but in four years that had usually been the case—Rigel filled her free hours intentionally, where most of her peers were content to see where the day's schedule took them.

"We still exercise most mornings," she said slowly. "And there's Draco's dueling club."

Pansy inclined her head, but said, "Lately, in the mornings, you're so focused, Rigel. It's hard to even banter, much less have a meaningful conversation. The other times I see you—meals and the like—are in group settings. I suppose I just wanted a little one-on-one time, to see how you've really been doing."

Attempting to lighten the mood, Rigel put a hand to her heart, "Our hour in the Black Lake together meant so little?"

The shorter girl narrowed her eyes. "You'll be devastated to know how many potential suitors that little escapade has apparently cost me."

"Devastated," Rigel repeated, hiding a smile. "It must be intimidating for your trail of hopefuls to try competing with the great Rigel Black."

"Perhaps this tournament has been too easy for you, if you can joke about it," Pansy shot back, equally deadpan.

Rigel's face fell into more serious lines. "I wouldn't say that."

Pansy nudged her apologetically. "I didn't mean it, Rye. I know it's been awful for you. Anyone else would have buckled under the pressure, but you still maintain one of the highest academic averages in our grade, not to mention your numerous side projects and bursts of 'philanthropic energy.' From the outside, it does seem as though you've got it all under control. That's why I wanted to speak privately with you, however." Pansy tugged them off the main path toward a window display of anthropomorphized hats. Her voice low, Pansy continued. "I flatter myself that I can see the strain others don't. You've been skipping evening study hour, and you miss more meals than you show up for. When you do come around, your eyes are far away, your attention fractured."

"I'm sorry—" she began.

"I don't want an apology, Rigel. I want to help you." Pansy's gaze was imploring. "Is there anything I can take off your plate? Millicent and I have been trying all year to help in our own way, but it occurred to me that what I see as important does not align with your priorities, and therefore is less helpful than I assumed. What do you want help with?"

Rigel stared for an embarrassingly long moment before clearing her throat. "I—er, I'll have to think about it." A brief survey of her highest-priority projects had her discarding most of them out of hand. Pansy couldn't exactly help her with freebrewing, poison study, animagus training, or the potion recipe she was working on for Fred and George. Hermione was already spearheading the Fade research, Archie was there to help with the ruse, and Professor Snape was available for anything tournament-related that came up.

"Well, take your time," Pansy said firmly. "I don't mean to add more to the list of things you're thinking about, just the opposite, but—"

"Hang on," Rigel interrupted. The word 'time' had reminded her of a curiosity she'd put aside for later investigation. She dug into her pocket and pulled out the silver watch Archie had given her what felt like a lifetime ago. "What do you think of this watch?"

"The—what?" Pansy blinked at the watch and then looked at Rigel in confusion. "That's your watch, Rigel. You've had it since your cousin gave it to you two years ago, right?"

"Yes, but I can't open it," she said, prying at the edge to demonstrate. "It never bothered me before, since the watch face is on the outside, but recently someone suggested it might be much older than I thought."

Pansy took the bright silver and turned it over in her hand, but ultimately shook her head. "Have you tried all the basic opening charms?"

Rigel nodded. "I even tried Parseltongue," she said, half-hoping for some sort of recognition or reaction. If it had been an heirloom of Slytherin well-known enough for Owens to recognize it, then surely Pansy, steeped in such history and tradition since the cradle, would notice it, too.

Her friend only laughed, however, and handed the watch back. "Parseltongue? That would be a heady coincidence. There aren't so many Parselmouths in the world that their artifacts crop up at random, I'm afraid."

Rigel smiled back, replacing the watch with relief. If Pansy didn't recognize it, Owens must have been trying to unsettle her somehow. "Suppose you're right. Maybe I should make some. I'll discreetly distribute gaudy things with snakes on them to pawn shops worldwide and make it look as though there is an entire underground society of Parselmouths with terrible taste."

"To what end?" Pansy asked, amused.

"It would be an invisible congregation," Rigel said, taking Pansy's arm again to resume their walk. "Soon talk of 'The Parselmouths' and 'The Order of Snakes' would spread, until everyone was simmering with curiosity about this group. Who are they? What do they want?"

Pansy laughed. "You could be your own political movement of one. Start an anonymous Parselmouth letter campaign to the Prophet."

"And no one would come out to contradict me, because the only other Speaker in England is—" she choked her sentence before she could complete it, a fission of warning strumming through her magic. She had almost violated the oath she'd taken to keep what she'd learned from the basilisk incident a secret.

Fortunately, the oath didn't care if others drew the correct conclusion, and Pansy already had second-hand knowledge of Riddle's talent. She completed the thought without finding Rigel's discretion unusual. "Him, yes." The amusement was gone again, like a wisp of cloud that refused to stay and provide proper shade from the glaring seriousness of reality.

They had reached the apothecary, and Rigel held the door open for Pansy to enter first, not missing the way the girl's nose wrinkled as she crossed the threshold.

Seeing it from Pansy's eyes, Rigel supposed the apothecary was not the most inviting of shops. It was dimly-lit, the aisles cramped and overcrowded, with labels scribbled in hard-to-read slant on small slates that were never fully cleaned of the previous price's chalk residue. If you didn't understand it, the organization system was a nightmare to navigate and, objectively, probably designed to put customers at a disadvantage.

Still, it put a smile on Rigel's face to pick up a deep wicker basket and thread her way toward the dried herbs. As Pansy fingered a stalk of lavender, Rigel swiftly plucked bundles off the shelves. A customer in the next row sighed loudly, and Rigel felt a brief stir of pity for the no-doubt bewildered citizen before the shockingly low price listed for autumn crocus extract caught her eye.

She tried to remember the prices she'd seen over winter break for the dried flowers in bulk, mentally calculating the labor involved in exploiting the stigmas and wondering how on earth they could afford to sell the distilled extract at such a low rate. Someone coughed as they passed behind her, and Rigel automatically moved closer to the shelf to give them room.

"Rigel…" Pansy said quietly.

She hummed in acknowledgement, most of her attention on profit-per-ounce differentials. A shoulder bumped her from behind and she murmured an apology without looking away from the crocus extract. There had to be something wrong with it, didn't there? An expired batch, maybe?

"Rigel," Pansy said, putting a hand on her arm and tugging insistently.

She broke away from peering at the vial's smudged label with a frown. "What is it?" Pansy was starting intently over Rigel's shoulder, so Rigel followed her gaze to the customer sharing their aisle. The tall young man, who was wearing an exceedingly large trench coat over his robes, must have been the one who'd bumped into her. His brimmed hat was pulled low over his eyes. He coughed loudly into his fist again.

Rigel looked back at Pansy and asked, "Do you think he's sick?"

Pansy shook her head with an exasperated expression. "Rigel, that's Sousa."

The bloke turned fully to face them, a look of exaggerated shock on his face, and Rigel finally recognized him. "Ah! I am so surprised to see you, Rigel Black, here in this store."

"Matheus?" Rigel shook her head, confused. "What are you doing in Scotland still?" She hadn't expected to ever see the Brazilian wizard again.

"Nothing." Sousa said, straight-faced. "It is not related with the fifth task."

"I didn't say it was." Rigel frowned at him. "Shouldn't you be back at school?"

That got a grin from him. "My school would rather I not." He made a show of looking both ways up and down the aisle and then leaned closer to say, "You should pretend you do not see me."

Pansy let out a strangled groan from beside her. Rigel tilted her head, considering Sousa. Snape still hadn't been approached about brewing anything for the next task, but they were certain there would be a potion of some sort involved. "Matheus, did one of the tournament organizers ask you to help by brewing a potion for the next task, by chance?"

The dark-haired boy smiled, sly and slow, but didn't answer. Rigel felt her stomach sink a little at that ominous reaction. She remembered all too well what Matheus did to himself in the first task. What was he going to do to them? Finally realizing he was there to give her a heads up on the next task, she said quietly, "Thank you."

"No thanks. I am only here for ingredients." He winked at her as he added, "I have no more of your 'super-sage.'" When she didn't laugh, his face shifted into something more earnest. "Be careful. It will be…bad." Sousa nodded to himself, turned, and skulked into a different aisle.

Pansy sighed. "It's a good thing you make friends easily, Rigel, because your situational awareness could use some work."

"What does that mean?" Rigel asked, still staring after the Castelobruxo wizard. She knew what she would classify as 'bad,' but how bad was bad when someone else said it?

"He was standing there for five minutes. He bumped into you."

"People spend a lot of time browsing in apothecaries, and the aisles are narrow," Rigel said weakly. Recalling her earlier fascination, she added, "Besides, just look at this price listed for autumn crocus—there's no way, right?"

Pansy stared at her for a beat, then said, "I'm going to wait outside. Please be more sensitive to shady characters seeking clandestine meetings while I'm gone."

Rigel felt that was a bit unfair. Who walked around life just waiting for dramatic things to happen to them? That was asking for trouble. Rigel simply wanted to mind her own business and get to the bottom of this saffron pricing mystery.

She was distracted for the rest of her shopping and suspected she overpaid slightly for a jar of bat spleens. By the time she joined Pansy outside, she had determined one thing, however: she couldn't mind her own business any longer. With Matheus' example fresh in her mind, she realized there was someone she needed to see.

"I realized what I need help with, Pan. I need to talk to Delacour," she said. "Can you help me find her?" She and Millie had been keeping tabs on the competitors, so it was a fair guess that Pansy would know exactly where the French girl was staying.

Pansy nodded slowly. "I can take you to her current apartment. It changes regularly," she added in answer to Rigel's curious look. "The girl has a prodigious number of admirers—more even than you, I daresay."

Rigel snorted. "Impossible," she said with a snooty lift to her nose. "The great Rigel Black is unrivaled."

"If you keep calling yourself that, I'll have it engraved on your dormitory door."

"As long as Draco's name is in smaller print," Rigel agreed.

They kept up a light banter through town, until Pansy turned down a small street and led her to the very end. "Up those stairs, number two," Pansy said. "I'll go and join the others. Meet us for lunch at the Three Broomsticks?"

She agreed, and Pansy gave her one long, parting look before adding, "Don't do anything Gryffindor."

Rigel looked up the wrought iron staircase and sighed, hoping she wasn't about to go knocking on trouble's door. She climbed steadily, each step echoing like the beat of her heart. The Vow was shivering in her veins, trying to discern her intentions. Would helping a competitor set it off? Not as long as there's an advantage in it for me, she told herself firmly. Anyway, who would I be if I didn't try? This is the right thing to do.

She rapped on the plain door to number two, but there was no answer. Rigel didn't hear anything inside the apartment, but a hunch made her flare her magical awareness through the door. A very still pocket of energy gave off a return too large to be anything but a magical being. "Delacour, I know you're in there," she called. "It's Rigel Black. We need to talk."

Low French curses accompanied the sound of a bolt being drawn back, and Rigel felt the faint shudder of protective wards falling before the door unsealed slightly. Fleur peered out at her, eyes darting in narrow appraisal about the walkway. Once satisfied that Rigel was alone, Delacour jerked open the door and pinned Rigel in place with her wand.

"To prove you are not lying: 'oo was ze first champion you met in ze tournament?"

Rigel cast her mind back to Halloween, when the preliminary candidates had met for a brief socializing event before the official announcement. Seafoam eyes flashed beneath a blunt red haircut and she remembered. "Antiope. Then you."

The lovely French witch lowered her wand and backed away from the door. Rigel stepped into the small apartment and sneezed. Every surface overflowed with flowers—vases crowded the tables, bouquets languished on chairs, and a pile of what appeared to be rose petals littered one corner.

Delacour began to reset the wards, and Rigel felt her stomach clench. "Would you mind leaving them down for now?" she asked.

The older girl tossed her silver hair. "Zey scramble ze locating charms. Ozerwise, more of zis will come." She gestured to the stockpile of cut flowers.

"You could just vanish them," Rigel suggested hopefully. "I'm sorry, but wards make me uncomfortable."

"You live under ze most powerful wards in Europe," Delacour reminded her, tapping her wand restlessly on her leg. She didn't respond to the suggestion that she vanish her admirers' gifts, and Rigel wondered if she didn't really mind them as much as she claimed to. Then again, there was a real paranoia in the way the other champion had answered the door.

"Are you all right?" Rigel asked, concerned by the girl's nervous demeanor. Fleur Delacour clung to her composure with pride; it would take more than flowers to ruffle her to this extent. "Has someone been bothering you?" It wasn't hard to imagine that a young woman as charming as Delacour could attract admirers that took their appreciation too far.

Fleur avoided her eyes as she cleared a space on the sofa. "Zere are some 'oo feel zat one such as I ought not to win zis tournament. Flowers are not all zat comes."

Rigel felt a flare of indignation on her behalf. "Anyone who thinks that is stupid. You should reverse the tracking spell and send their nastiness right back to them."

Delacour's eyebrows rose as she sat down and gestured for Rigel to do the same. "You do not 'ave experience wiz hate, I zink. Engaging zese people will only encourage zeir madness."

She made a face, unable to refute that observation. "Let someone know if you need any help, then," she said as she sank into the sofa.

"Ze 'Ogwarts staff has been very 'elpful," the girl said stiffly. "Zey set up ze wards and find me new accommodation when eet is needed. Now. Why are you 'ere?"

Recalled to her original purpose, Rigel asked, "Did they tell you that one of the items we recovered in the lake was a clue for the fifth task?"

Her lips twisted. "Zey did."

"Was one of your items a silver diadem—a circlet?" Rigel asked.

Fleur's eyes lit with suspicion. "Why would I tell you?"

She shrugged. "You don't have to. It was only a guess. Mine was a replica of Salazar Slytherin's locket. I think Owens had Hufflepuff's Chalice of Truth, too. I don't know whether the founders themselves are part of the clue or merely symbolic, but I do think that the function of the items is a clue for what is going to be tested in the next task."

The older girl frowned, shaking her head in a way that caused her star-lit hair to slide like water over her shoulders. "Why have you come to tell me zis? You should not be helping me. Perhaps you are here to trick me, instead." At the last, she barred her perfect teeth in a fierce smile.

Rigel paused to reassess how best to explain. "I…want to win the tournament. I don't expect you to believe that it is for reasons other than personal glory, but it is. That said, I don't like the way the tournament is being run. I think the tasks are too brutal, too cruel. They ask too much of us, and I think if they keep pushing this way, one of us is going to get seriously injured or die."

Surprise flittered through Fleur's eyes briefly, but almost at once, it settled into grim agreement. "Yes. I 'ave also seen zis."

Relieved that this, at least, they could agree on, Rigel pressed on. "Today, I saw Matheus Sousa in the apothecary."

Delacour reared back, true astonishment on her face. "Ze Amazonian wizard? 'e ees still 'ere?"

"He came to warn me. The tournament organizers recruited him to brew a potion for the fifth task. He seemed reluctant to say too much, but he told me it's bad."

"Bad? What ees bad?"

"I don't know exactly, but I also have the clue from the lake. I want to give it to you, so that you can properly prepare." Rigel held Fleur's gaze so the other witch could read her honest concern. "I think it's going to be very dangerous, and I'm afraid of what will happen if you walk into it blind."

"Zen tell me," Fleur demanded, eyes flashing a challenge.

Rigel paused delicately. "I want to. I also want to win. You understand?"

"You want an alliance. Or…a deal?" Delacour held her chin firm. "I do not want to owe you anyzing. But tell me: 'ave you offered Owens ze same?"

"I haven't, actually," Rigel said quietly. "There's—I don't know why, but I don't entirely trust him."

"Good. 'e eez a snake. No offense meant," Fleur offered after glancing at the crest on Rigel's scarf.

Rigel narrowed her eyes curiously. "You don't like him either?"

"Non. 'e sends ze ugliest flowers to mock me." Fleur gestured to a bouquet discarded on an end table. The plants inside looked more like a collection of thick, green tubers than flowers. There were no visible petals, almost as though the stems had been cut before they could bloom. She tried to recall what type of flower had such thick stalks. There were three of them, wrinkly and twisted, with a bulb-like thickening at the tip. "Also, I zink 'e means you ill. Sometimes, when you are not zere, he says ze most—"

"Delacour, how long have you had these?" Rigel interrupted, her eyes riveted on the ugly bouquet. She recognized the plant now: Amorphophallus. It brought the tremor of disgust back to her stomach. Rigel hoped Fleur was unaware of how the plant got its name, and the vulgar implications therein.

Fleur broke off and thought for a moment. "I zink two days, no more. I was going to give zem back when I saw 'im next. Zey are 'ideous."

Rigel stood and circled around to peer closer at the offending bouquet. There was a tightly coiled root ball at the base, wrapped in damp sackcloth. To keep it alive, she guessed, her irritation with Owens growing stronger. "This is Snake Lily, did you know? Looks ready to bloom."

Delacour's eyebrows rose, unimpressed. "A snake. 'ow fitting. Zen it will 'ave flowers?"

"Enormous ones," Rigel confirmed. With a wrinkled nose, she added, "They'll smell like a corpse."

With a screech, Fleur sprung to her feet and vanished the flowers. "Zat boy ees a—" She broke into French too fast for Rigel to completely follow, though she got the gist. "A pox on zis tournament." Her hair hovered almost menacingly about her face, and Rigel thought she could see a bit of orange burning deep in the girl's striking eyes. "Tell me what you want for ze information. I am not dying for zis."

She had understood the threat, then, in the flower. Rigel felt ambiguous about accepting help even tangentially from Owens, but if it pressed Delacour into helping them both by accepting her deal, then she wouldn't complain.

"I will tell you everything I know and help you come up with a strategy for surviving the next task. In return, I'm asking for a promise: if it comes down to you or me, in the end, you'll let me win." Rigel held her breath as Fleur silently considered it. She knew it was an extraordinary demand—the tournament was what they were both there for, after all. She also knew that Fleur had no clue as to what the next task would entail.

"A verbal agreement?" Fleur clarified slowly. "On my 'onor, wiz no magic to enforce it?"

Rigel examined what she knew of Fleur. The older girl was not above fighting dirty, but she was also proud. "That's right," she agreed after a moment. "I'm not asking you to throw the tasks, either. If you outperform me to a clear victory, I won't stand in your way. If, however, the outcome is close enough to question…"

"Zen I will defer," Fleur said, voice flat. "I understand."

Rigel got out a sheet of parchment and began to copy down the clue from her memory, explaining as she went. At the end of their discussion, Fleur had three book titles on filtering poison from the body, and a written introduction to Madam Pomfrey, for rudimentary Healing lessons.

"The equinox is next week, so you have three weeks until the task," Rigel concluded. "If you need help with any aspect of this, please don't hesitate to ask."

Fleur fingered the piece of parchment with the clue stanzas scribbled down it and muttered, "I did not sign up for zis. I 'ope you do win, Black. I want to go 'ome and never see zese people again."

So did Rigel, though she was already in too deep to back out now. She left Delacour's apartment feeling more drained than satisfied. It wasn't blackmail, she told herself. The Vow wouldn't let her help for nothing, and they were direct competitors—not like how it was with Hermione in the preliminaries. She could have died walking into the next task blind. It was the right thing to do. Right?

She had chalk on her hands, in her hair, and across her nose, but she grinned in triumph when the last rune was etched into the array.

"I think my hand at Chinese runes has really improved," she said, pleased with the gracefulness of her lines.

"Shall we see whether that increases the efficiency of the transmutation?" Dumbledore smiled genially down at her work, all the while perfectly aware that handwriting, no matter how neat, would effect no such change.

"I'd rather see this 'interesting effect' you mentioned," Rigel said, her eyes running over the patterns again, curious. It was a moderately tricky array, designed to turn sand to glass through the pairing of two slightly tangential signifying runes, rather than the use of a single, clear signifying rune.

Dumbledore gestured magnanimously for her to activate the array, and Rigel touched her finger to the input circle. Usually, when she imbued an array with magic, she could feel it building steadily in potential energy, like a pitcher being filled with water. This time, however, the magic she poured into the array began to…shiver, almost. It trembled, as though that same pitcher was in the midst of a localized earthquake. With a glance at the Headmaster's serene expression, Rigel persevered, forcing the magic to stabilize with an effort of will and continuing to imbue until the activation threshold had been met.

The normal flash of light occurred, but with it came a physical tremor in the worktable. Chalk rolled onto the floor and Rigel took a quick step backwards, instinctively throwing up a shield as the array shuddered. For a few moments, she felt it attempting to do its work, to follow the patterns as they were laid down, but there was something unquestionably wrong. After an agonizing, jarring struggle, the array went dark. She dropped the shield and examined the materials left. Part of the sand was twisted and half-melted, while the rest of it remained untouched. Black marks ran raggedly through her carefully chalked runes—they would not be able to try it again without erasing and redrawing the entire thing.

"What did I do wrong?" she asked, familiar enough with Dumbledore's style of teaching to wait for the other shoe to drop.

"Nothing," Dumbledore said, a bit too cheerful at the results of the choked array. "Or perhaps it is better to say nothing that you could have done otherwise."

Rigel parsed through that sentence for a moment. "So it was something intrinsic to me that caused this?"

"Your magic, to be precise," Dumbledore revealed.

Rigel flinched, but sense caught up with her a moment later. "It—it does not act out of my control anymore."

The old wizard inclined his head apologetically. "Forgive my alacrity. It was not your magic's boisterous nature, but rather its natural affinity that reacted negatively with the array."

Rigel's eyes widened with understanding. "This is a signature-sensitive array?" She had read about them, but they had yet to have a practical lesson with one. "It is Light-aligned, then?"

"Neutral, actually," Dumbledore corrected her.

She frowned. "My magic is mostly Neutral, though." Most halfbloods had a mix of Neutral wild magic from their muggleborn ancestor and either Dark or Light depending on their magical family history. Hers was a little too wild to be considered truly Light, despite the Potter influence, so she described it as 'mostly Neutral' when pressed. It was not too far a stretch for the scion of a Dark family to have wound up with recessive magic that produced mixed results, and Archie's magic truly was a Neutral-Dark mix that owed something to Diana's family, she thought.

"The strict balance in this array is maintained only delicately. Any slight shift on the affinity scale from exact Neutral will upset it."

Rigel's eyebrows rose. "That would narrow the potential users significantly. Why design an array this way?"

Dumbledore chuckled. "It is said to have been developed by scholars of an ancient order who specialized in the aligning of individual affinities. Admittedly, that may be mere legend, but I find there is often more truth in old stories than contemporary minds would credence." He fell into a thoughtful silence for a moment, then came back to himself to add, "How it came about isn't the purpose of the lesson, however. I wanted to show you the effects of a misaligned array, so that you may recognize one if you come across it in your future studies."

"I'd rather know how to recognize such an array before it scars my worktable," Rigel said dryly.

"We can never eliminate all the unexpected occurrences from the world," Dumbledore advised.

"So there isn't a way to recognize a signature-sensitive array before it explodes?"

"I did not say that." A smile twitched under his long beard. "Consider the array clockwise, beginning with the rune of lowest numeric value."

She scanned the runes. "There are two in the sequence that stand for 'one' in Numerology," she pointed out.

"Use the northmost one to start," Dumbledore said.

Rigel pointed to the simple roman numeral I, which was often used in sequences to represent magic, looking as it did like a wizard's wand. "The wizard is the first card in the Tarot deck." She moved her finger clockwise to the next symbol in the array. "Then fehu, the initiating rune, is first in the Nordic system. Next is kun, the receptacle of the initiating force, defining the field of the array. Kun is the second hexagram, so that would be a two in Numerology." She looked up at Dumbledore questioningly, and he nodded encouragingly. She continued in a puzzled tone, "The next one is the Egyptian hieroglyph for grains of sand. It doesn't really have a number associated—oh, there are three grains of sand! One, one, two, three…wait, but the next two break the sequence."

"Those two are paired," Dumbledore reminded her.

"Ah. I can add them. Thurisaz is the third Norse rune, and it's been paired with huo for fire." Together, Thor's rune and fire were supposed to signify lightning. Rigel thought it was a rather clumsy expression, as there were other, better runes for lightning. Still, Dumbledore never taught her anything that wasn't important, even if she couldn't always see it right away. "Huo is the…second element in the Wu Elemental system, so if it's paired with three it makes five. Then lemniscate to cycle the energy back through the array—it is a Fibonacci sequence!" Rigel grinned with satisfied intellectual pride.

"And never forget that circular arrays can always be considered a 'zero' as well," Dumbledore said. "Well done, Rigel. Have you ever seen a perfect Fibonacci sequence in a circular array before?"

She shook her head. "I don't think so, although I'm not sure I would have noticed if I didn't look at the numeric associations in sequence."

"You would have noticed when the array didn't work for you," Dumbledore told her. "Fibonacci arrays are always perfectly Neutral—in this way, they mimic exactly the natural, wild magic of the world."

"So if I notice that an array follows the Fibonacci sequence, then it must be signature-sensitive," she concluded. "But that's only for perfectly Neutral arrays. There are other arrays that are sensitive in different ways, aren't there?"

"Quite so," Dumbledore agreed. "You'll find that the next chapter of your self-paced reading will describe common patterns found in such arrays. It is not exhaustive, of course, as there are a great many arrays and rituals in the world, not all of which conform to typical forms. Still, I hope you find it useful enough to be worth the effort of memorizing. I have certainly found it to be so."

Rigel nodded. It would definitely be helpful if she ever wanted to try a new array unsupervised. She had a question that had been building in the back of her mind since the array had malfunctioned, however. "You mentioned that some think this array was designed by wizards who specialized in 'aligning their affinities' with nature. Does that mean that it may be possible to alter your own magical signature to be more or less Dark or Light over time?"

Dumbledore's wizened face took on a troubled expression. "Our signatures do not reflect any intrinsic quality in ourselves, only in the magic we happen to be blessed with."

She blinked. "I understand, Sir. I'm not interested in the moral implications, but the practical ones. If I could change my magical signature to be more Neutral, for instance, I could use this array."

"Ah, yes. In theory, that is."

"Aside from that, though: if the input signature needs to be Neutral, there should be a way of making that happen without having to change the signature of the one imbuing the array," Rigel said, her mind leaping from one stone to the next easily. "It's just like in Potions, when you have to alter the reactivity of a brew before you add certain ingredients. Sometimes the base needs to be more acidic, other times more basic, and it can move back and forth along the scale depending on what you add to it regardless of how acidic or basic the original ingredients were."

Dumbledore peered at her with a curious expression. "Can you expand on that analogy? How would you apply it to Alchemy?"

Rigel's train of thought moved from Potions to Shaped Imbuing to the ways in which magic could lose its natural signature. "If the magic that goes into the array needs to be at a certain place on the affinity scale, then maybe it needs to be severed from the direct influence of the wizard whose affinity isn't Neutral. When you cast a spell, your magic usually loses its own natural signature as it takes on the shape imposed by the spell. What if it were possible to sort of filter the signature from the magic before it encountered the array?"

"I believe that once his magic is changed sufficiently, a wizard can no longer direct it," Dumbledore said idly.

"That's true," Rigel said, nodding quickly, "but it can be directed externally, can't it? By runes, in the case of Alchemy. Perhaps a separate array could be added before the magic encountered the main array that you wanted it to enact—a sort of pre-array component that would, using runic equations dedicated to the conversion, adjust the signature of the magic that was imbued before it reached the second array, which is signature-sensitive?"

A surprised noise was startled from Dumbledore's throat. He cleared it and said, "My boy, I think you are on to something. The idea is sound, yes, quite elegant. The execution…it bears looking into."

Rigel beamed. "Of course, it would be difficult. Reactions in Alchemy happen so much faster than in Potions. Everything would have to be drawn out and defined ahead of time."

"Not to mention discovering the language necessary to describe precise differences in magical signatures. I'm not certain the same expressions could be used for adjusting the affinity of a Light wizard as were appropriate for a Dark wizard, for instance." Dumbledore gestured to the air and it produced an oversized peacock quill and parchment for him. Under her astonished stare, he jotted something down and slipped the piece of parchment into his pocket. Never, in all of their sessions together, had she ever seen Albus Dumbledore make a note. "If you don't mind, Rigel, I would like to pose your question to my old friend, Nicholas."

Her eyes widened. "I don't mind at all, Sir. I'd be very interested in what he has to say." Another thought occurred to her and she added, "You may consider reaching out to my aunt, too."

"Lady Potter?" Dumbledore smiled. "I have not had the pleasure of her conversation in several months. I would be delighted to write her on any pretext, but do you think she will have a particular insight into this matter?"

She nodded, reaching into her sweater to pull out the necklace she wore underneath. "Aunt Lily gave me this pendant when I started the tournament. She calls it a Dark Defense Disk. There are sequences embedded in it so long I had to consult another, more gifted student to decipher it even in part. Aunt Lily says they describe Dark magic, though, as the disk is specifically designed to defend against Dark Arts and not Light. If there is a good way to express magical affinity with runes, Aunt Lily can help."

Dumbledore bent closer to the obsidian disk. "May I?" he inquired politely. At her nod, the Headmaster cast a wordless revealing charm and hummed with interest as the block of runes materialized in the air between them. He read the sequences with a practiced eye, nodding here and there with a particularly pleased noise. "It seems I am suddenly behind the curve in magical advancements," he said, looking happier than the utterance suggested. "Lily Potter has just thrust the field of Defense Against the Dark Arts into uncharted waters. I daresay these expressions will soon be under patent, if they are not already," he added seriously. "I thank you for allowing an old man to slate his intellectual curiosity, but you might be more protective of the mechanics of your disk in the future."

Rigel flushed. "Yes, Sir. I will be." She supposed she ought to ask Blaise whether he'd kept a copy of the runes he'd transposed for her. He probably had—Blaise liked nothing so much as to know things no one else did. She was certain he would honor a request that he keep the information proprietary, if she asked. "I have another question," she ventured after a few minutes of uninterrupted thought.

Dumbledore raised his eyebrows. "I'm not sure the academic world can withstand two questions from Rigel Black in a day. Shall we find out?"

She laughed. "It's just—I've been researching magical transference on my own, you know, and when Hermione Granger came to Hogwarts for the tournament last term, she shared her research concerning the Fade."

"Yes, Madam Pince mentioned the young American girl with rather ferocious reading habits."

"Hermione swallows books whole before they can fight back," Rigel confirmed. "In dovetailing our research, we noticed that attempts to transfer magic of an adult wizard to an infant suffering from the Fade are not successful in stopping the illness from draining the child of life. The magic doesn't stick in that way to an infant's core, and I wondered if that was because the magical signature of the parent wasn't close enough to the infant's natural signature to mesh properly. My question is: if it were possible to alter a magical signature, even temporarily, to match another's, could that altered magic fuse with the core of the one it was given to?"

Dumbledore let out a long breath. "I don't know the answer to that. It depends on a deep understanding of the way our magical cores create and store magic, which, I am sorry to say, currently escapes even our brightest minds. Have you looked into the case of ritual transference we discussed last term?"

"I have," Rigel said. "My conclusion is that it demonstrates that magic sometimes retains its magical signature when it is transferred and remains mixed with but independent from the magic of the recipient's core, causing the resonance described. This is the unusual instance, however, as most magic does not retain its own signature long after it has been severed from the original core." This she had confirmed with extensive research after Millicent and Blaise pointed out the strange case of her own Medi-minis persisting for so long. "For most people, the same ritual would result in a temporary resonance that dissipated over time entirely, as the donated magic eventually rejoined the wild magic of the world." She paused to gather her thoughts before adding firmly, "I don't think that such shallow transference ever actually gives magic to the recipient. The recipient holds it for a time, provided their core has room, but the magic isn't theirs. Either it dissipates eventually, or it sits there, unable to be used by them because it doesn't match their own signature."

"That would mean that any ritual claiming to confer magical power upon the recipient is false," Dumbledore pointed out. Rather than disagreeing, he seemed to patiently await her judgement on the matter.

"I think most of them are," Rigel said slowly. "The ones that really have been demonstrated to transfer power—the conference of a magical gift, for instance—all involve more than mere magic being donated. It isn't as easy as moving a bit of magic from here to there, the way the lady in our example tried to. Real transference rituals require an exchange of blood, and after the ritual, accounts always describe the recipient's magic as significantly altered. A Neutral wizard is suddenly Light-natured, or a fire core becomes an earth core. There is a fundamental change, almost as though the core itself has been transplanted. At that point, it's not a question of assimilating foreign magic into a core, but of altering the core itself so that it can receive the foreign magic." She shuddered. "There's a reason those rituals are considered in most cases Dark or at least intensely intrusive. I don't think it provides a good solution for the Fade. Forcing an infant's core to mutate to become exactly like the parent's…that sort of thing would stifle all variation in a bloodline, not to mention it seems a perversion of the baby's natural expression of magic."

"It is a distasteful solution, but not as pitiable as an infant perishing," Dumbledore put forth.

Rigel grimaced. "Hermione said the same thing when she suggested amputating the infant's core before the baby could become dependent on magic. It would stop the Fade, if it could be done, but the cost…I don't see many parents agreeing to it. I want to find a better way. There's just so much we don't understand about how magical cores really work." She sighed. "I suppose it was a far-fetched question. The research just isn't there yet."

"More research does need to be done on the subject," Dumbledore mused. "Have you considered doing it yourself?"

"Doing…the research? I'm nowhere near qualified—I'm not even halfway through the Healing program here, much less at the level of a Master trusted to engage in human research." Rigel was astonished that he'd suggested it—even she wasn't audacious enough to attempt experiments on anyone other than herself, and she'd already established that her own magic was not a good benchmark for 'normal.'

"And yet you possess an ability that none of those qualified Masters can boast," Dumbledore said. "Even Mind Healers cannot go into the magical cores of their patients. You, Rigel, can walk right through them."

She gaped at him. "I…I could see for myself what was happening in the core," she repeated dumbly. Why hadn't she thought of that before? She'd spent most of the last three years pretending she didn't have a unique and strange ability instead of considering what she might learn from it. Resolve solidified in her stomach, like a rock that she'd held up for too long dropping to the earth at last. "That's what I need to do, then. That's my contribution."

Dumbledore clapped his hands together, the sound bringing her out of her reverie. "Wonderful. It is so inspiring to see today's youth collaborating across international borders to tackle the pressing challenges of the moment. Reminds me a bit of myself, if it is not too brash to say."

Rigel gave a wry smile. "Perhaps some good will come from this tournament after all. If nothing else, it brought Hermione Granger to England."

The Headmaster chortled appreciatively. "Your greatest strength will always be the friends you make, Rigel. One day, you will certainly appreciate the connections you have forged in so many corners of the globe."

She genuinely hoped that one day she would look back with such equanimity on the year. At the moment, it was a very thin silver lining on a thundercloud of trouble.

"Speaking of making friends," the Headmaster said, seemingly unaware of the entirely obvious nature of his segue. "There is a little soiree I throw every spring, and this year, a number of people have asked whether you would be amenable to attending."

Thrown for a loop, Rigel prevaricated. "Isn't it during the school year?" She had heard of Dumbledore's Soiree, of course—it was as emblematic of Light Society as the Malfoys' Garden Party was of the Dark. It was held around Easter, usually, though she hadn't cause to pay it much mind before.

"Over the long weekend holiday," Dumbledore assured her. Sensing her hesitation, he added, "Some of your current friends, including Mr. Weasley and Mr. Longbottom, will be in attendance. In the current political climate, it never hurts to make a few more."

"That's true," she said slowly. The last thing she wanted to do was be paraded at another event as the Hogwarts champion, but Dumbledore had a point. She was in a political position, and if she attended a prominent Light gathering and made nice… perhaps she could create a little more leverage against Riddle's legislation. She had promised herself she would try, at least, with what little notoriety was now afforded to her. "All right. I'll be glad to attend; thank you."

Dumbledore led her back through the 'secret' passage to his office with a cheerful twinkle. "Not at all, Rigel. With you in attendance, it will be the talk of the town."

For once, she hoped that was true.

That evening, she managed to find Blaise at his own table in the common room. Rigel took a seat across from him, intending to ask him to be careful with the runic sequence he'd copied from her mother's Dark Detection Disk. Before she could say anything, however, the boy held up a slim hand to forestall her and said, "One moment. I'm in the middle of a calculation."

Ever-respectful of the titanic grip of true academic pensée, Rigel waited patiently for him to bring his train of thought to its intended station. When he had put down his quill, she smiled politely. "Is that the same project you've been working on all term?"

He nodded ruefully. "It's a little above my current abilities, but Mother wanted to challenge me."

"Is it just an exercise or will it have a real-world application?" she asked, distracted from her original purpose.

Blaise shrugged. "I don't know. Probably it's a variation on something she's already working on; every now and then she gets an interesting commission and lets me try my hand at it for practice."

"Could I see?" Rigel peered interestedly at the sheaf of parchment splayed out before him. Blaise hesitated palpably, a reserved expression concealing his emotions. Rigel raised an eyebrow, surprised at his reticence. "I won't steal the design or tell anyone," she said gently. "I showed you Aunt Lily's work, remember?" It felt cheap to invoke the principle of reciprocity, but trust was a two-way street, at least in Slytherin House.

Acknowledgement flickered in his serious gaze as he inclined his head. "That's true. I trust you will be as discrete with this as I will be with your Aunt's sequences."

Pleased that they had reached an understanding so easily, Rigel bent her attention to the parchment Blaise pushed across the table. At once, she could tell it was a ward of some kind. Her interest in wards had taken a sharp dip after the previous year, though she had devoured several tomes on breaking them, which in retrospect had probably been a bit compulsive. At least they aren't goblin runes, she thought as she traced the general structure with her finger.

Blaise appeared to be almost finished with the project. The sequences were elegant and balanced, mostly in the western systems of runes, so that they worked together with a synergy that was hard to replicate when you mixed too many different systems. Catching on an inverted barrier rune, Rigel's eyes narrowed.

"This is a cage," she said flatly.

Blaise winced. "It isn't, actually."

"I think I know a containment ward when I see one," she said sharply. "What is it for?"

"Rigel, take a breath," Blaise said firmly. When she had visibly deflated from the defensiveness that gripped her, he continued calmly. "It is an enclosure, but it's cast from the inside, see? It will keep things inside from leaving, but its primary purpose is to keep those outside from entering. It's designed to be taken down from the inside, too—see the inverted cornerstone?"

She nodded slowly, but still had to know. "What will it be used for?"

"Dueling wards, I think," he said carefully. "I can't confirm it, but I believe Mother already has a buyer in mind. Likely Regulus Black, as he is often involved in large event wards, and these would work well for something like the tournament or the World Cup, don't you think?"

She studied them for a few more minutes, inwardly relieved that the purpose was so innocuous. She could even confirm that Regulus had used something similar to facilitate the Lower Alley tournament. Rigel had thought Regulus designed his own wards, but perhaps the extra business he'd been getting lately had saturated his time. "So if the caster would be inside with the event participants, he would have to access all four cornerstones at once to put the ward up," she said slowly. "It seems as though you'd need more than one caster, if the ward was really big enough to encompass a whole dueling arena."

"That's right," Blaise said with a nod. "Four casters are needed from the inside, but only one is necessary to take it down. This chain of runes will destabilize it from any of the cornerstones."

Rigel smiled weakly. "That's good. In case one of the casters is incapacitated when it needs to come down."

Blaise returned the smile, albeit grimly. "It's a lesson learned from the World Cup. It took too many people working in tandem to get the wards down once they were set. These wards will fall all at once, as long as at least one person can get to a cornerstone."

She thought of her father and said, "That means extra security around the cornerstones, but it's probably worth it to have a quicker exit strategy. That's an impressive addition, Blaise. Did you come up with it?"

He flushed slightly. "I did. The only trouble is, the simple chain holding them together makes the wards a little too weak. I'm trying to figure out how to keep them easy to disassemble from the inside while making it harder for the ward to be penetrated from without. At the moment, this ward is no stronger than your average house wards. A group of determined wizards could probably take them down by force."

Rigel saw what he meant. More runes added to stabilizing the ward against attack would inevitably complicate the sequence needed to take it down from within. "You need more power without using more runes," she said.

Blaise gaped at her for a moment. "That's…exactly what Mother said when I asked her for a hint. She didn't elaborate, though. How do I increase the power without adding any more runes? I can't add more casters without adding more cornerstones, and the structure is already at optimum stability with four."

"Perhaps a source of power that isn't the casters themselves?" Rigel suggested.

He smacked the table with sudden elation. "A ley line. Rigel, you're a genius." He grabbed the parchment back from her hands and began to scribble in the margins excitedly.

"You're the one who came up with the answer," she said, amused to see Blaise so worked up over something. He was so rarely ruffled in any way. "Are you going to add an amplification chain so it can be set up on a ley line to boost the power, then?"

"Just going to work in general tie points so it's optional," he muttered distractedly, still writing. "Then whoever casts it can tie the ward to whatever is closest—ley line, other wards, it won't matter. It can borrow that power to support itself, while staying simple enough to be unraveled by a single wizard." With a grin, Blaise cast sand over his notes and sat up straight once more. "I'll send it off to Mother for grading this week, but I think this is the answer, Rigel. Thanks for your help. It's been driving me spare."

She shook her head. "I think you just needed to talk it out with someone. I make a lot of breakthroughs when I voice my problem out loud."

"Still, I—"

"There you nerds are!" Theo slammed his Transfiguration book onto the table. He was echoed a moment later by the thuds of Pansy's, Millicent's, and Draco's books joining the spread. "We were waiting like idiots at our usual table by the fire, only to find you bookworms have started without us."

Blaise extracted his designs from beneath the corner of Theo's heavy book with a long-suffering expression. "Rigel and I had some real thinking to do before our more passive academic peers distracted us with the monotony of their prescribed homework assignments."

"Oi! You're the one who asked me to explain the difference between British and European Gobbledegook dialects tonight," Theo shot back.

"I'm sure Millicent or Draco could do just as well," Blaise drawled, deliberately provoking the other boy.

"Somehow I doubt goblins are included in International Relations," Theo sneered.

"Pansy, then."

Pansy shot him a reproachful look. "Goblins aren't covered in Care of Magical Creatures; they're beings, Blaise. You of all people shouldn't make a joke like that."

He shrugged one shoulder, his face blank. "These days, who knows what's considered a being?"

Pansy's face softened. "Is your Mother still annoyed with Riddle about the tournament definitions of blood purity? We missed her at the Yule Ball."

"She declined her invitation," Blaise confirmed. With a sigh, he added, "Honestly, none of those in the shifter community are pleased."

Millicent muttered, "This tournament has been a disaster for magical relations on a number of fronts. The Centaurs are still upset about the first task, and the Merfolk didn't exactly enjoy being cast as the villains during the fourth."

"Wonder which group of magical beings we'll manage to piss off in the fifth task," Theo said cheerfully. "Rigel, any guesses?"

She shook her head. "I think we're going to be drugged or something, actually."

Draco whipped his head around to stare at her. "What does that mean? And why are you so calm about it?"

Rigel tilted her head. "Nothing I can do about it, if that's what the task is."

"Should you be telling us this?" Pansy asked, looking casually around the common room.

She realized she hadn't told them about the necklace yet; Pansy must be worried Rigel was admitting to a mysterious source. "We got a clue at the end of the last task," she explained, smiling apologetically at their exasperated faces. "Professor Snape helped me work it out. It basically says we're going to have our clarity clouded and then be asked to do something while in that confused state. Sounds fun." The joke fell flat.

"If you know, can't you just take a bezoar?" Millicent asked.

"I will, if we're allowed to have any items for this one," she said. "Riddle hasn't told us yet. Anyway, bezoars only work against poisons. They might dose us with something that isn't technically poisonous."

"Such as a drug," Pansy repeated, her eyes flashing. She looked as though she wanted to be angry but didn't have anyone present to direct the feeling toward.

Draco patted her shoulder, murmuring, "Only two more tasks," in a low voice that seems to calm the blonde girl somewhat.

"Two more tasks," Rigel agreed. "It'll be over before we know it." She didn't know who she was trying to convince.

In preparation for the fifth task, some of her lessons with Snape had necessitated a rather dubious turn. Snape didn't like it, and Rigel hated to ask it of him, but she needed practice filtering foreign substances from her blood. After considering the potential consequences of miscalculating her ability, she admitted it was safer to do with supervision.

Her Head of House stood with arms crossed in disapproval as she slowly injected herself with concentrated essence of Aconite. She knew what to expect—texts described the dizziness and fluttering heartbeat in laconic terms. She also knew she could begin filtering immediately and stave off the worse effects, but that wasn't the point. Rigel needed to be able to climb out of the worst of it, for Snape suspected she would not be allowed to combat the effects of whatever they imposed on the champions right away.

From her experience dueling Ralph over the summer, Rigel was familiar with the treacherous tingling that crept through her limbs, heralding the coming incapacitation with sweeping softness. Sweat beaded on her forehead, and she struggled to control her breathing until Snape said, "Now." There was a clock ticking away the seconds as she turned her attention inward and attempted to channel her magic without diverting it first to her wand.

This was the second part of their strategy. If Rigel could battle the effects of the substance from within, it would keep her hands—and wand—free to deal with whatever came at her from without. The poison was swift. Her limbs were weak, but she couldn't undo the damage there until she won the battle in her bloodstream. In most danger was her heart, so it was into her veins that Rigel sent her Healing magic first, shaped by the strength of her will alone.

"Thirty seconds."

She heard Snape's voice as though from a tunnel. Her blood was almost clear. The rest was only flushing out the poison from where trace amounts had already been deposited. Rigel swept each system carefully, all the while trying to ignore the strange purple color crawling from the edges of her vision.

"One minute."

"Done." Rigel stretched her neck and stood. She wobbled slightly, but shook it off with impatience.

"You've adequate speed, but it still requires all of your concentration," Snape commented.

She nodded. "It's tricky, because Aconite might actually kill if left unattended. I have to be fast when dealing with it. Whatever they give us in the tournament probably won't be as bad at that. I'll be able to split my attention."

"You don't know that," Snape argued. "You ought to practice with a lower risk substance and attempt to multitask."

"I've done that already," she told him. At his scowl, she smiled. "You don't really want to know where I got the Firewhiskey, do you?" She was kidding, but Snape did not seem to appreciate the jest.

He crossed to the wall and took her apron from its hook, tossing it to her with impatient force. "If you aren't going to take the tournament seriously, you can at least spend the evening improving your brewing."

Rigel brightened. "I had a recipe I wanted to try, actually. The specifics came to me after our last session—remember the deathcaps you had to throw out because the preservation charms had worn off the jars?"

Snape's mouth lifted in a sneer. "I had words with Burke. It won't happen again."

"That's great, but it got me thinking," Rigel said. "Not about ingredients, really, but about the potions themselves. How many do you think people throw out every year because they bought them for emergencies and haven't used them before the expiration date?"

"That necessity keeps us in business," Snape said drolly.

She made a face at him. "As if you don't resent every replacement batch of Pain Relief you brew for the Hospital Wing. What if you could increase the shelf-life of potions like that without having to alter the recipes?"

Snape lifted one eyebrow slowly. "I'm listening."

"It's annoying that most potions can't be exposed to a lot of direct magic without destabilizing, right? It makes preservation charms on potions themselves unreliable at best. I want to create something that is like a stasis charm, which is less reactive than a preservation charm. Stasis spells can't be maintained for more than a few days at most, though, and what I'm thinking would last years if done right." Rigel pulled a piece of scrap parchment from her pocket. "This is just a start, but I think with a little tweaking I can get it to work. It'll be a base—kind of like the neutral base you created for my cousin Harry—but built around raw amber. When it's mixed with other neutral potions—I wouldn't recommend volatile ones, unless we test them specifically—it should act as a sort of liquid medi-mini, encasing and trapping the magic in the existing brew, so it doesn't dissipate as quickly. The hard part is making sure the amber base doesn't interact with the potion itself—I don't want to indiscriminately increase the effectiveness or longevity of the potion once ingested." She imagined a Blood Replenisher that kept producing blood indefinitely and shuddered. "So, what do you think? Will it work?"

"Amber is an inspired choice," Snape said after a long moment of thought. "To ensure it doesn't incorporate with the potion in question, this base must be perfectly balanced. Its ingredients should be bonded and sealed completely to one another before it is added to the recipient brew."

She nodded, understanding the danger if one or more ingredients from the amber base separated and reacted with ingredients in the potion it was meant to preserve. "I was also thinking it should be more oil than liquid base, you know? That way, you could just coat a bottle with the amber base before adding the potion you want to preserve."

Her professor nodded once. "Sound theory. Let's see it."

Rigel grinned. "Thanks, Professor. I really want to get this finished in time for the twins' birthday."

He stiffened. "I forbid you to supply the Weasley terrorists."

She widened her eyes earnestly. "Please, Professor. I don't often ask for favors, do I?"

"I will not be party to it."

"They've been really good friends to me," she argued. "They saved my life in the first task by giving me those fireworks." As Snape's jaw clenched, she pressed home the point. "They've also single-handedly run a public relations campaign for me."

"A prank campaign."

"Which worked."

They stared at one another, both stubbornly refusing to blink.

"Don't you think it's a creative application of Zygmunt Budge's principle of amplification without interaction—"

"Do not insult me."

Rigel groped for another argument and settled on, "It's important that I not be in anyone's debt, isn't it?"

Snape scowled fiercely. Even he could not argue with one of the tenants of Salazar Slytherin, however. "Do what you will, then."

Rigel resisted the urge to hug him. "Thank you! Uh, if it works, would you also be able to submit it to the Guild for testing? Nothing extensive, just to make sure it's safe for human consumption."

"Don't push your luck."

"That's okay, I can have Harry submit it," she said. Master Thompson would help, though he would grumble almost as much as Snape.

"You will not give her credit for your invention," Snape snapped. "I will take care of it. Just get to the cauldron and brew."

Rigel grinned and did as she was told.

She was grinning again a week later, when she sidled up to the Gryffindor table and edged through the throng of admirers around where the twins were holding court.

"Puppy! You came!"

"How honored we are to have the Hogwarts Champion, Romantic Rigel himself, at our birthday celebration!"

"I eat breakfast here every morning, same as the rest of the school," Rigel said.

They pulled her onto the bench between them. "As long as you're here, you can watch us open presents," Fred suggested cheerfully.

She applauded politely through three boxes of Bertie Bots and a bag of hastily hidden stink bombs. As the pile of gifts dwindled, the crowd around the twins diminished, until finally it was just their usual friends left at the table. Rigel couldn't contain her impatience any longer. "Don't you want to know what I got you?"

The twins froze and exchanged a skeptical look over her head.

"The last time Puppy got us a gift, we melted into piles of glittery goo," George said.

"This time, I can't remember what we've done to annoy him," Fred added, looking vaguely worried.

"On my honor as a trickster, it isn't a prank," Rigel said, laughing. She pulled out two plainly wrapped boxes, each no bigger than her palm. "Happy Birthday!"

They waited a beat, as though to be sure the boxes wouldn't reach out and bite them, before apparently deciding she was sincere. Rigel supposed it was difficult to know who to trust when your birthday was April 1st and you were a pair of notorious pranksters.

George opened his first. They had learned something from last time, then. He plucked a grey, unpolished stone from within and turned it over in his hand. "Pretty?" he said, questioning.

Fred leaned across Rigel to peer at it. His eyes widened. "George, look at the aura."

George narrowed his eyes in concentration and a moment later yelped and nearly dropped it. "Rigel, what—"

"Read the card," she prompted helpfully.

He dove into the box and came up with a square card and a small roll of parchment. Upon scanning the short message in the card, his eyes widened and his face lost a little color, making his freckles stand out in alarm. "Rigel, this is…"

He passed the card to Fred, who read it quickly. "No kidding…" His voice sounded faint and a little awestruck.

Rigel frowned at their reactions. "It's just a little magic," she huffed. "For your experiments. I know sometimes all an inventor needs is a little extra stabilizing power." Extra magic could make the experimental process safer and smoother, and thus faster, too. "Anyway, that's only half the gift. The scroll is a recipe. I think you'll find it useful when you start stockpiling an inventory for your shop."

George was still staring at the stone. "Rigel, how do we even use this?"

She made a noise of understanding. "Ah, I forgot to explain. The runes in gold are reversible, see?" She pointed to a line of golden runes etched between dozens of lines of red. "Red means don't adjust, okay? I used an attractant array so the stone would suck in the magic I imbued and keep it as long as the array is active—you'll know if it starts to fail, because the runes will flicker. When you reverse these runes, it becomes a repellant array, instead, and the magic will start to leak out."

"And this equation?" Fred said weakly, pointing to the alchemic expression she'd included in the card.

"That describes the relationship between the number of seconds the stone leaks and the associated decrease in the coefficient of whatever brew, ritual, or array you're trying to imbue," Rigel said, pretty proud of the calculations. "You just plop the stone into the potion or field of magic for whatever you're working on, count the seconds you need, then levitate it back out and reverse the runes again. It can be used an indefinite number of times, until the magic inside is spent. Cool, huh?"

"Rigel…" George let out a strangled laugh. "Yeah, this is cool. Maybe the coolest thing anyone's ever given us," he added lowly.

"I'm a little afraid to ask what the recipe is for, but I also really want to know," Fred said. A wide smile was winning out over the earlier surprise. "Is it for a prank?"

She shook her head. "I'll leave that sort of invention to you two. It's a little boring, but very practical," she said. "Professor Snape helped me come up with it." She ignored the twin choking noises that statement produced. "He'll probably deny it if you ask."

"This has to be a prank," Fred muttered, opening his own box to dig out his copy of the recipe from under the matching stone within and unroll it. "It's…a preservation oil?"

"Exactly! For when you start making big batches of product to sell one day. If you coat a container in this before adding the potion you'll store in it, the oil will help extend the shelf life of the potion. I haven't done exhaustive calculations, yet, but I think for an average potion it'll be between two and three times the shelf life." She could hear herself rambling, but she couldn't help it. The recipe had been an immensely satisfying short-term project. "Professor Snape was the one who suggested the color-change component. When the oil turns brown, it's lost the magic that sustains it. At that point, the potion inside will only have its normal shelf-life remaining."

"Professor Snape gave us birthday presents," George whispered, horror in his tone.

She elbowed him. "Don't let him hear you say that. He helped with the recipe out of academic interest only."

"This is most surreal, Rigel," Fred confided, rolling up the recipe. "Somehow, your shockingly unique gifts feel like their own sort of prank. We're grateful! Thank you, I mean, but…"

"Yes, thank you!" George exclaimed from her other side. They both appeared overwhelmed.

"It's the least I could do," she said quietly. "I haven't forgotten all the things you've done for me over the years. From splinting my wrist in first year to literally saving my skin with your handy firework display. You went so far above and beyond casual friendship when you helped me recover from the unfortunate blood magic incident in the third task." She looked between the two of them and shrugged a bit helplessly. "I'm not the best at expressing gratitude on a regular basis, but I wanted to help you both with your ambitions, the way you've helped me with mine."

She thought she saw tears welling in Fred's eyes, but before she could be sure, Rigel was enveloped in twin hugs that pinned her to the bench. She held very still, careful not to breathe too deeply, until Fred and George gathered themselves and pulled back with matching sighs.

"Rigel, I don't know what we'll do with this yet," George said as he clutched the stone in his palm. "I do know that one day there will be a truly epic prank product named in your honor."

"What more could I ask for?" Rigel said, a glad grin stretched across her face.

"Seriously, thank you," Fred said fervently. "This recipe—it's gold, Rigel. You could patent it and sell it to manufacturing companies for—I don't even know. What in Godric's name you're giving it to us for, I don't know either, but we're sure as spit going to use it."

"Use it well," Rigel said, still smiling. She stood, waving farewell to the other Gryffindor sixth years, who gaped at her in silent reproach.

"Sure, arm the agents of chaos and walk away," Angelina Johnson muttered.

Rigel resisted the urge to cackle maniacally, but it was a near thing.

In such a good mood, she decided to try again at a task that had been frustrating her for months. Animagus transformation, she had found, was unlike any other form of magic she'd studied before. Her own magic was apparently next to useless until she discovered the 'inner enlightenment' that would solidify her connection to the raven.

She settled into her lab to meditate, struggling to find the animal within her even as the animal in her care slithered from his rock to her lap and coiled in peaceful repose. Dom, on the other hand, was less than helpful. He had finally finished filtering Riddle's magic out of her core and now had decidedly too much free time on his hands. That he spent that extra time blowing raspberries at random intervals in her mind should not have surprised her.

Brrrrrt!

Rigel broke her meditation with a huff, not giving the construct the satisfaction of an admonition, and hissed an apology to Treeslider for disturbing him as she stretched her legs. She'd been at it several hours, and when she checked the time, she realized Archie would be waking up soon. Feeling mildly vindictive after her own peaceful moment was interrupted, Rigel dug out the mirror and shouted into it. "Harry! Haaaaarrryyyy—"

"Damn it all, cousin, what?" Archie's face appeared in the surface of the mirror, his eyes bleary with sleep.

"Morning, cuz," she chirped, good humor restored at the sight of his disgruntlement. She wondered vaguely whether her emotions were a zero-sum game, but shrugged off the suspicion in favor of watching Archie yawn.

"If you tell me you didn't wake me on purpose, I won't believe you," he grumbled. The view shifted as her cousin sat up in bed and shook his head back and forth sharply. His hair was getting long, she noted. She supposed he'd been shrinking it up with his Metamorphmagus ability rather than bothering to actually cut it.

"Early bird gets the worm," she said.

"You'd know." He yawned again.

"Actually, that's sort of the problem," she admitted, stroking Treeslider absently. "I can't get this Animagus thing to work, so I thought I'd commiserate with you to make myself feel better."

Archie's expression perked visibly. "Well, I hate to disappoint you," he said slyly.

She gaped at him. "You…already?"

Her cousin moved the mirror against something solid and let go of it. A moment later, there was a handsome red fox perched atop his rumpled bedcovers.

Treeslider hissed at the image. "Interloper! Ssseize it, Ssspeaker."

Rigel moaned in defeat as Archie turned back into himself, startling her snake into another fit of hissing. As Treeslider slid off her lap and left the lab in a disgruntled snit, her cousin laughed at her. "Pretty impressive, huh? Start to finish in a year, no less. Dad'll be plussed when I tell him."

"How did you do it?" she begged. "I'm getting nowhere, no matter how long I meditate on the 'qualities of the raven.'"

Archie scratched his chin, where the faintest hint of stubble was visible, and said, "It wasn't about defining the qualities of my fox so much as it was admitting to myself that those were my qualities, too."

"That's what Tahiil said. I still don't really understand."

Archie was quiet for a long moment, but then he began to explain. "I didn't get it either at first. I had to admit, really accept, that the fox is me. I am cunning and sneaky. I am also loyal and protective. It's okay to be all those things." His voice dropped lower as he went on. "It was more than just the Animagus thing that clicked when I accepted that, you know? I actually feel much better about the ruse, now, too. It's been weighing on me—well, I've told you some of it. I thought I was turning into a bad person, with all the lying and trickery, but I've reached a sort of rapport with that now. I accept who I am. As long as I am sneaky for a reason I agree with, then I haven't lost myself at all. In fact, the fox enhances me and my goals. It reminded me that it was because of loyalty to my family that I wanted to be a Healer in the first place. Because of Mum. And it was that same familial protectiveness that drove me to agree to the ruse. It was for your dreams, too."

"Archie…" She didn't know what to say, but her heart ached with his.

"I can also admit I'm not fully happy with the way things have turned out," he said, speaking over her gently. "It asked more of me than I knew. Going forward, I'm going to try to be truer to myself, until we find a path through all of this. And Harry—I just want you to know that whatever the raven represents to you, whatever you're scared to admit to yourself, that's okay, too. When you accept that part of yourself, you'll be more at peace. It won't happen meditating or combing through arcane magic, either," he added with a self-deprecating smile. "I figured it out in the middle of a tuna sandwich. Just be patient, and when the voice inside you tells you things you don't want to hear…try listening."

I think I like this kid.

She shoved Dom back to the recesses of her mind. He is not talking about you!

"Thanks, Arch. I know things haven't turned out the way we planned." She ran a hand through her fringe, feeling helpless to comfort him so far away. It was obvious he was going through something profound, and she hated that she couldn't be there in person to help. "I know I've been distant this year, too. Busy. After this tournament, it won't be so crazy."

Archie smiled, but it didn't have his usual shine. "I know. I don't blame you. I'm all right, anyway. Coming to terms with some things, but that's part of growing up. Don't worry about me, okay? Just come home safe. We'll sort it all out this summer."

"Okay." She swallowed the rest of her apologies and offered, "How's Hermione?"

His expression sharpened. "That's right! She's been asking me if you read through her notes. The woman is obsessed with the Fade, Harry. She's not even doing extra credit assignments for her classes anymore." His wide eyes told her that this was, indeed, a large deviation from character.

"I did read them," Rigel said. "Twice. I'm not sure I completely understand her conclusions; she thinks the common understanding of the way cores produce magic is flawed? She postulates that there is little evidence other than assumption supporting the idea that magic is created by a wizard's core alone, from scratch. While I agree the process isn't well-understood, I'm not sure there's no evidence. Then there are notes about a potential experiment to test her theory, but they aren't complete."

Archie nodded. "She's having a hard time coming up with a way to control all the variables she wants to. I hope you figure out what she's talking about and explain it to me before this summer, because she's expecting to meet up with 'Rigel' at some point to discuss the experiment face to face."

"I'll write her back after the next task," she promised. "Knowing Hermione, she's probably onto something shocking."

"Maybe you two can talk it over using the mirror," Archie suggested. "Letters take forever, and I don't mind letting her borrow it whenever." Rigel agreed to set a date when the fifth task was finished. Her cousin caught her gaze in the mirror and said, "Good luck in the next task, cuz. If you need anything, ask."

"I will. Thanks, Arch."

They disconnected the mirrors, and Rigel found herself alone in her lab with restless energy coursing through her. The next task couldn't come fast enough. The sooner this tournament was done with, the sooner life could get back to normal.

They could see it being constructed for a week before the task. Oliver Wood was frequently caught staring toward the Quidditch pitch, misty-eyed and solemn. Rigel tried not to look, but the monstrosity was hard to miss. It grew in twisting spirals, like Jack's proverbial beanstalk, only instead of green life stretching high into the clouds, it was metal, black and silver, cobbled together with only the barest allowance made for structural integrity.

From the base of the stadium gates, some of the more curious students said, you could see the top swaying in the wind. No one was allowed close enough to study the structure in detail, but Rigel could sometimes hear the ghostly voice from the locket mocking her.

"A fortnight past the equinox, three heroes will ascend."

The tower seemed to follow her for days, just visible through the open doors of the Entrance Hall, hovering over her shoulder during their morning runs. Rigel had taken to averting her face when she passed a window, which was probably why she ran smack into Auror Dawlish on her way up a set of stairs on the third floor.

He righted her with perfunctory efficiency, then adjusted his own olive trench coat. "Black. You appear distracted." Disapproval was heavily implied.

"What's your excuse, Professor?" she quipped. At his unimpressed look, she quelled. "Sorry for running into you. I have a lot on my mind."

"That much has never been in question." His sharp eyes took in the slump in her shoulders, the bags under her eyes. "Why don't you join me for a counseling session in my office?"

"I have a…" she trailed off, aware that she couldn't exactly explain she was on her way to a dueling club that didn't exist. "Never mind. Sure, Professor."

She'd apologize to Draco, but she honestly didn't think he'd mind too much. The club tended to run smoother when she wasn't there to distract the others, who inevitably had questions about some trick she'd pulled in the tournament.

Dawlish left the door to his office propped open but set up a silencing ward so that their conversation couldn't carry. He snapped his fingers twice and a set of steaming teacups appeared on the otherwise empty surface. Rigel took a cup with murmured thanks, looking around the office with muted curiosity. It looked like the space of a man who didn't intend to stay long.

"Your uncle is worried about you," Dawlish said bluntly. "He thinks the tournament is too much strain." The blank expression on his face suggested he didn't care either way, but was obliged to ask.

"Tell him I'm fine."

"I don't lie to my boss."

She straightened in her seat and scowled over her teacup. "Then tell him I will be when this is all over."

Dawlish tapped a finger on the desk next to his untouched tea. "You've been holding back in class."

Rigel blinked at the non sequitur. "I get a lot of Defense practice outside of lessons," she said dryly. "I don't think my peers would appreciate my treating the classroom the way I treat a dueling arena, Sir."

"It isn't just my class." Dawlish's gaze seemed to pierce right through her. "The other professors talk about you, did you know?"

She shook her head, eyes widening in mild alarm.

The Auror ticked them off his fingers. "From what he's seen in the tournament, Flitwick suspects you know every Charm in the textbook for at least two grades above your own. Sprout says she ran out of things to teach you about plants in third year. Potions doesn't need to be touched upon, as you already know where you stand with Snape, but McGonagall… she thinks you might be a prodigy." Even as Rigel continued to shake her head slowly, Dawlish inclined his own. "Yes, she says you continuously imply an understanding of topics not covered until well into NEWT-level Transfigurations, and that's without adding in the Alchemic principles you dovetail into her field from the Headmaster's personal tutelage."

"I just study ahead. I'm not some kind of genius."

Ignoring her, Dawlish went on, "Now for my part, the Defense class as it currently exists seems to be a complete waste of your time. Barring a slight improvement in your reflexes, I cannot claim to have effected any significant improvement in you through my instruction. Don't deny it," he added sternly. "I watched the first four tasks, same as anyone. Your demonstrative ability in handling dangerous magical creatures, spell-defense, and high-stakes dueling is beyond contestation. I'd give you an NEWT right now, if that was in my power. It's not. Don't be surprised if your post fills up with pamphlets from the Auror Corps in a few years, though."

She grimaced. "No offense to Uncle James, but I'm not interested in being an Auror. I'm going to be a Healer."

He stared at her, blinked long and hard, then barked out a laugh. "A Healer? Magic does love her little jokes. A Healer. Boy, you could be the most lethal thing to come out of the Auror's Officer in a decade. Moody is itching to get his hands on you. A Healer." He laughed again, shaking his head.

Rigel sighed. "Sorry to disappoint, but I wasn't trying to get recruited for anything. I'm just trying to survive this tournament and get back to my studies." Reminded of something, she reached into her bookbag and pulled out the worn copy of the Auror's Field Guide he'd given her the previous term. "Here. It was very helpful, but I've finished with it."

"It's your uncle's," Dawlish told her.

"I figured. I'm sure you'll see him before I do," she said, shrugging. "Thank you for the tea, Professor, and the information. Was there anything else?"

He shook his head, but belied that by adding, "You can't play dumb forever."

"I'd have to be pretty stupid to think I could," she muttered, standing. As she turned to go, she heard the Auror take up the book and flip it open. A bark of laughter cut off as she stepped through the silencing wards. Her mouth lifted in a small smile. The notes in the margins had been intended for James, but perhaps Dawlish would appreciate the suggestions, too.

Putting on what she had mentally dubbed her 'tournament uniform' for the fifth time was almost anti-climactic. Risking her life for the sport of others had, impossibly, become almost routine. She moved through the familiar scenes easily: accepting jubilant well-wishes from her housemates, giving solemn assurances to her friends, avoiding the worried gazes of her professors in the Great Hall. Rigel even had her standard 'last meal' down to an art—just enough that she would be energized without risking lethargy or nausea.

She had to be down at the pitch earlier than usual, at least half an hour before the advertised starting time for the fifth task. Draco and Pansy walked her down to the champion's tent, neither saying much. She knew they, too, were worn thin by the constant string of tasks, the never-ending cycle of preparation and recovery. Rigel felt even more awkward than usual, naked as she was without her potions kit, but Riddle had finally told them they weren't allowed any items except their wands this time. Despite this, she summoned a smile for them at the entrance to the champion's tent and said, "I'll be okay. This time, I have a good idea of what to expect going in."

That what she expected was going to be decidedly unpleasant went unvoiced.

She ducked into the tent and paused for a moment to get her bearings. Rather than the usual open space with scattered chairs, there were three cots set up around the center pole. Owens was stretched out in one as though he were only there to take a nap, and Delacour sat primly on another. Rigel climbed onto the third and said, "Any idea what they're dosing us with yet?"

"Sousa was 'ere already," Delacour said, her face set in an unhappy scowl. "'e went to find ze official 'oo was to 'old ze substance."

"So you both figured it out, too?" Owens said, sounding surprised. "This'll be fun, then. I was worried about you, Delacour."

"Not worried enough to tell me ze clue," the French girl spat.

"Hey, I sent flowers," Owens protested, a mean grin on his face.

"Corpse flowers," Delacour muttered, eyes flashing orange for a moment. "Pray our wands do not cross before zis eez over."

Owens appeared more amused at the threat than intimidated. Before he could goad her further, Matheus came back into the tent, three vials in hand.

"Good. You all are here." He held up the vials with a grin that was just a little too strained to be truly believable. "This is your task—most of it. The hard part. The rest is climbing."

"Now, Mr. Sousa, don't give away too much just yet," Bagman admonished jovially as he pushed his way into the tent ahead of Crouch and the other organizers.

Riddle swept them with his gaze as he entered, Lucius Malfoy and Crouch Jr. at his heels. The sight of the twitchy man put Rigel's hackles up, but Riddle caught her gaze briefly and sternly, and she supposed she was meant to interpret Barty Crouch's continued presence of evidence that Riddle had handled the situation. Lucius gave her a slow nod when she flicked her gaze to him, and Rigel sent him a small smile. He didn't return it. There was a warning in his eyes that sent a bare chill down her spine.

"This test will not be like the others," Riddle told them after a moment of quiet expectation circled the room. "In some of the tasks you have been limited on the items you bring or the actions you take, but in this task, you will be limited in the faculties you can bring to bear on the challenge ahead. In many ancient wizarding cultures around the globe, the youth were set to similar trials—sent to face the unknown in an altered frame of mind—and they returned enlightened and vindicated, adults in the eyes of the world."

Rigel thought that was putting a rather thick layer of icing on a cake that was, at best, mildly culturally appropriative and, at worst, objectively offensive to those very cultures, many of whom still practiced a variation of such coming-of-age rights. She glanced around to see if anyone else was embarrassed to be party to this particular aesthetic choice, but most of those in the tent hung on Riddle's words as though he might accidentally utter the secrets of magic at any moment. In exceptions, there were only two—Delacour and Owens. Her fellow champions were more interested in what exactly they'd have to do than the symbolic reasons behind it.

"Matheus Sousa has generously agreed to collaborate with the committee on this task." Riddle put a hand on the young Brazilian boy's shoulder. "His unique talents have been applied in preparing the draught that each of you will drink before attempting the main portion of the task."

"The draught has, of course, been screened by several Mediwizards," Bagman hastened to add. "Not to worry. It's designed to make the task difficult, but not impossible."

"Will we each be given an equal dose?" Rigel asked, cognizant of the fact that Owens was bigger than both her and Delacour.

Matheus shot her a dramatic pout. "I am insulted. Of course, I calibrate the correct dose for each."

Crouch nodded sharply. "Indeed. Your heights, weights, and genders have been taken into account when considering the optimum dose. Not to worry, Mr. Black. Each champion will receive a dose suited to his or her own biological limits."

She felt herself blanch, but put on a polite smile and nodded as though relieved. Inwardly, she cursed her luck. If the brew was metabolized differently according to sex, then she would be getting a dose suited for a boy of her size. Rigel hoped the practice she put in with Snape would pay dividends—it would certainly be problematic to be knocked unconscious by a dose of a drug she ought to have been able to handle.

"After ingestion, you will be monitored for twenty minutes. During that time, no circumvention or mitigation via physical or magical means is permitted." Bagman clapped his hands together as though this were an exciting twist. Certainly, Rigel could feel something twisting in her stomach. Twenty minutes? Their systems would be completely saturated by the time they were allowed to fight it off.

"Once the twenty minutes is up, the task begins," Crouch continued. He looked at them one after another with a stern eye. "You will all attempt the task at the same time. It is a race to the top of the tower that has been built in the arena. Unlike the other tasks, there are no subjective scoring categories. The first to the top will receive top score. Understood?"

Rigel nodded with the other two, at once amazed by the straightforward nature of the task and disgusted by its convolutions. To force them to attempt such a thing while mentally and physically compromised was—well, she had expected it, but that somehow didn't make it any more palatable.

"Will zere be safeguards in place around ze tower?" Delacour asked softly. "In case we fall."

Riddle's lip curled in what he probably meant to be a reassuring smile. It looked more like a sneer. "I would advise against falling, Miss Delacour, if you wish to complete the task. In the event that it becomes unavoidable… you won't physically perish."

He managed to convey clearly that any such embarrassing display was discouraged and would result in a very different perishment—that of their chances in the tournament. Rigel sneered back at him. Did he think anyone was planning to fall on purpose?

Owens fell back onto the pillow. "Let's get this going, then. I want to know what the fuss is all about." He offered his arm toward Sousa, tapping his vein with a teasing wink.

Matheus smiled slowly. "You must drink it. It is not delicious."

That was an understatement. Rigel got a waft of the brew as Sousa passed her the vial with her name on it. Even held at arm's length, it was enough to cause her stomach to clamp down in protest.

Bagman fished a headband out from his robe pocket and put it on, giving them a thumbs up to indicate it was transmitting before saying, "Welcome, one and all, to the New Triwizard Tournament fifth task! If you haven't taken your seats yet, not to worry; this is only being broadcast for transparency. The task will start in twenty minutes, but at this very moment our three remaining competitors have been given…a Draught of Delirium! They will drink it, and in twenty minutes, take up the challenge of the tower under the auspices of one of the most potent combinations of mind- and magic-altering substances known to the Wizarding World!" Bagman paused, presumably for the cheers he imagined would follow his pronouncement. He gestured urgently from beyond the viewpoint of the transmitting headband, and the three of them clenched their vials tighter. "Now, the champions will imbibe their potions!"

Rigel held her breath and downed her vial in one go. She did not release her breath until she was certain the liquid had made it all the way into her stomach, and even then, the smell of what was left in the vial almost brought it back up.

Delacour covered her mouth with a hand, eyes wide in disgust, and Owens choked and spluttered for an agonizing moment before deciding to keep the brew down.

Bagman let out a staged chuckle, though his eyes winced in sympathy for them. "There you have it! Get comfortable, folks. In twenty minutes exactly, the fifth task will begin!" He took off the headband and added, "You lot all right there?"

"It's disgusting," Owens gritted out.

Delacour nodded, tears in the corners of her eyes.

They both looked at Rigel, who grimaced. "I've actually had worse."

Madam Pomfrey bustled into the tent with flared nostrils and a glare that could keel over a hippogriff. "I should have been here from the moment they took it. Why did no one summon me?"

Crouch lifted a placating arm. "The tournament organizers are going to monitor—"

"Like hell they will." Pomfrey brandished her wand at Delacour. "Lay down this instant. I need to check your blood pressure. You're going to feel the effects first, I'm afraid. Black, you'd best lay down as well. Try not to move."

She did as she was told, rather grateful to have the strong-willed Mediwitch there as the poison began coursing through her veins. It would be doubly uncomfortable to slowly lose her senses in a space without anyone she could count on to have her back.

"The rest of you can go, unless you take some amusement from the slow torture of three helpless young people," Madam Pomfrey added with a sniff.

"Torture? No, Poppy, don't be so dramatic," Bagman said, looking uncomfortable. "It's only part of the task."

"Vertigo, dizziness, shortness of breath, sweating, vomiting, palpitations, paranoia, confusion, fear, loss of muscle control, involuntary stimulus to the visual cortex—shall I go on? Does this not sound torturous to you, Ludo?" Pomfrey's sarcastic indignation seemed hot enough to burn down the entire stadium with the right spark. "Or perhaps you'd like to take a vial for your own entertainment? I'm sure Mr. Sousa can scrounge up another dose."

Bagman was not quite foolish enough to press the witch any further. "Well, perhaps it is for the best that a trained professional take over the monitoring." He checked his watch. "Right then. Bring them to the pitch in fifteen minutes, if you please. Gentlemen? We'd best get up to the Judges' Box."

All eyes moved to Riddle, who inclined his head gracefully. "Best of luck to you three. Do make the most of your last chance for advantage before the finals."

The men left—all except Sousa, who hovered uncertainly by the entrance. When it was clear no one was going to come back in, he slouched closer to their beds and said, "I try to dial it down. Riddle has no mercy."

"What's in it?" Rigel asked. She couldn't feel it yet, but wanted to plan what she would do while her head was still clear.

"Yohimbe bark and Ayahuasca, mostly," he said quietly.

Delacour frowned. "Are you allowed to tell us zis?"

Matheus shrugged. "No one is here to stop me."

He glanced at the Mediwitch, who very pointedly did not say anything other than, "I disagreed with the concept of this task from the start. They didn't listen when I told them that twenty minutes was too long to wait in counteracting this sort of concoction—at least if they want you to be able to move your limbs."

Owens half-rose in alarm. "Is it that strong? What the f— is Yohimbe bark?"

Matheus glanced at Rigel, who answered, "It's an alkaloid commonly taken as a stimulant. It's not meant to be mixed with Ayahuasca, however, which is a brew that combines DMT with a monoamine oxidase inhibitor."

"What language are you speaking, Black? I thought this was going to be like LSD or some crap." Owens ran his fingers up and down his arm restlessly.

"This is faster and longer," Matheus said helpfully.

"The MAOI stops your digestive track from metabolizing the drug as it normally would. Instead, it will cross the blood-brain barrier and severely impair many primary functions for several hours," Madam Pomfrey added with a sniff.

"When will it start?" Delacour asked.

"Soon. Expect severe nausea, tremors, and dizziness first," Madam Pomfrey said gently. "Then it will move into unpredictable visual and audio stimulus, loss of motor control, confusion, and fear. You may think about purging prematurely if possible."

The French girl frowned. "I zought we are not allowed."

The Mediwitch raised her eyebrows and looked pointedly around the tent. She conjured a bucket and set it on the floor beside the girl before moving to the entrance to 'check the weather.'

The moment Pomfrey had ducked out of the tent, Fleur dove for the bucket. Rigel looked away as the girl held back her own hair and turned her wand on her throat. Retching noises followed, coupled with a quick vanishing charm. Rigel glanced over at Owens, curious to know whether he would say anything about the deviation from tournament rules, and caught him sliding a slim vial back into his sleeve. The pained look on his face as he averted his eyes from the sunlight coming through the slits in the tent told her what he'd taken: Sobering Draught.

She was impressed by his sneakiness, but doubted a brew designed to tackle the effects of alcohol would be very effective against the powerful psychedelic created by the vines of the Amazon basin.

Delacour performed a breath-freshening charm wordlessly and offered Rigel the bucket. She declined. "I'm all right, thank you." She'd been monitoring the draught internally, and knew that it had been absorbed too quickly for regurgitation to help much at this point. She could feel real nausea setting in, and cold sweat on her forehead.

Madam Pomfrey came back in and moved to Rigel's bedside. "I'm going to perform a basic diagnostic—"

"No, thank you. I refuse," Rigel said calmly, swallowing against her churning stomach.

Madam Pomfrey scowled at her. In a low voice, the woman said, "I'm not allowed to heal you. They'll be checking my wand, no doubt, but I can tell you what I see."

She smiled in gratitude, but shook her head. "I can diagnose myself. It is already in my bloodstream and beginning to permeate my general nervous system. I'll do what I can," she promised, already having begun directing her magic toward metabolizing the poison one area at a time.

The nurse gave her an unhappy nod and moved to Owens' bed.

"Five minutes," Matheus said.

Vertigo was beginning to set in. Rigel focused her magic toward her digestive system first, clearing the rest of the draught from her stomach and intestines before it could be absorbed further. After that, the long, slow process of sweeping her other systems began. "The heart is the most vulnerable," she said out loud, in case the others were wondering where to start. "Once we begin physical exertion, the palpitations will be dangerous."

She heard Owens curse and Delacour murmur, "Zank you." Rigel hoped the girl had managed enough practice filtering blood in the last two weeks to at least spare her heart long-term damage. This task was really too much.

Barty Crouch came in to collect them when it was time. "Figured you may need an extra pair of hands to get them out there," he said with a rather nasty smirk.

Delacour tried to stand and immediately buckled on trembling knees. She caught herself on her cot and snapped, "Do not touch me," when it seemed as though Barty would attempt to lend her his support.

Madam Pomfrey stepped in, letting the French girl lean on her as they slowly made their way out of the tent. Owens put a hand out to Matheus impatiently and said, "A little help, man? This is your fault, anyway. Least you could do, really."

Sousa sighed, but obligingly swung Owens' arm over his shoulder. He glanced at Rigel and Crouch Jr., clearly not willing to leave them. Rigel forced magic into her limbs to stabilize them and slowly swung her feet over the edge of the cot. Her vision swam away from her for a moment and she swayed, but regained her balance before toppling, at least. With a sharp jerk of her head, she said, "Let's go."

Barty crossed his arms as Rigel slowly made her way toward the entrance under her own power. "You're faring well, Black." He leaned closer and she had to suppress the urge to flinch as his tongue darted out to lick his lips. "Almost as though you didn't get a full dose."

She raised an eyebrow at him, not sure what he was trying to imply. She'd drunk the full vial, in front of the whole world, no less. "I've swallowed a lot of poison in my life," she said sweetly. "I guess it doesn't bother me so much anymore."

They moved slowly, more like a string of wounded soldiers limping toward a casualty camp than three young heroes marching into battle.

Rigel could feel her pulse in her stomach and see it in her elbow when she pulled back her green jersey sleeve. She was sweeping her cardiovascular and respiratory systems as quickly as she could, trying to target the areas that kept her body alive first and worry about what it was doing in her mind second. Her magic was slower to respond than usual, though. It wasn't like fighting off a poison such as Aconite, which affected only her body. As the draught began to affect her mind more keenly, the connection between her will and her magic felt strangely dampened, clogged like a gunk-filled pipe.

Every step was an exercise in complete concentration, and she had no idea how she was supposed to complete a task in that state. Delacour could barely stand upright, and Owens had begun to mutter quietly to himself, eyes darting here and there uneasily.

They finally reached the pitch, the din of applause and stamping cheers enough to cause Owens, still suffering the after-effects of his Sobering Draught, to double over and purge violently. Barty Crouch led Rigel to her starting point at the base of the metal tower.

"Look up, boy," he said conversationally. "See the top?" She squinted up the steep incline, her eyes crossing briefly without her impetus. The tip of the spire doubled and swayed in her confused vision, and she shut her eyes with a low groan. "There are no traps along the way," Barty went on brightly. "Not a single curse or beastie to stop you until you get to the very end. All you have to do is climb. You can even use magic—whatever magic you want. If you can, that is." He slapped the black metal of the tower fondly and laughed. "You're in for it this time, Black."

Rigel knew she was having trouble parsing through his words. Her brain felt heavy and slow in a way it hadn't since those feverish days in Pettigrew's pit. She hated it, but found it difficult to sustain the energy required to be angry. Bagman was shouting something, his magnified voice ringing all around the stadium, going on and on and on and—

Kid, what's going on!?

Dom? Disoriented, Rigel tried to concentrate. "Dom, what are you doing out here?" she murmured, looking around the pitch.

I'm still in here, idiot! You need to come see this—it's everywhere. It's going to burn down the whole mindscape at this rate—

That jolted something inside her, some residual panic that had been squatting in her chest for a rainy day, perhaps. Rigel took a deep breath and clutched her dizzy head. She reached for her magic to continue filtering the draught from her nervous system—when had she stopped?—but it twisted away, just beyond her grasp. My magic, she thought with deliberate force. My magic…I can't—!

I know. Stop panicking. You're making it worse. He pushed a wave of calm across her mind, and for a moment, there was clarity.

Dom! Rigel thought as fast as she could. It's the fifth task. We were drugged, and I have to climb a… The thought was so close. A tower! I have to climb a tower.

She struggled against the tide of chemicals in her system that just wanted her to lie down and stop moving. After a moment, Dom answered. All right, you can't come in here right now, then. You've got to win that tournament. I will take care of things in here.

Yes. She could have sobbed in relief. The confusion crept back at the edges of her mind. Handle it. Protect my mind. Use whatever magic you need.

The was a short, almost horrified pause. Then Dom's voice came again. When you have control of your magic back, I'll let you know, but until then, you have to keep going on your own.

"Keep going?" She said it slowly, testing the words. Where was she going?

Climb, kid! Climb the tower!

Rigel blinked, noticing the monstrous tower in front of her nose. There were people all around, screaming at her, something…something. Climb! The voice in her head insisted. Rigel reached for the first rung and started to climb. Her limbs were wooden, but they worked to a degree. One step, two. She reached a small platform. It was big enough to stretch out on. Maybe if she—

Climb!

Right. She was climbing. Her hand reached up and found the next handhold.

It was an invasion of burning spores. Dom perceived them as they drifted into the mindscape, accompanied by a sourceless fog, and climbed to his perch atop the mountain to better see. They appeared at first glance to be fireflies, faintly twinkling spots of light that wafted aimlessly in the breeze. Where one landed on the mountain, the flowers caught fire. Dom leapt to stamp it out; his foot was aflame in moments. With a howl of annoyance, he flicked the small amount of magic he had saved from his last 'allowance' at the fire and doused it. As he lifted his head, a sea of burning embers met his gaze, each a fiery snowflake floating gently toward an unsuspecting landscape.

His urgent cry to the girl rang through the mindscape, and her resulting panic sent the spores into a flurry. They landed in his hair, his clothes, and everything they touched turned to ash. Within minutes, it was chaos.

Protect my mind.

The command called to the runic arrays etched into his construct. Protection was the construct's primary directive. Purpose swelled in his breast.

Use whatever magic you need.

A well of bottomless hunger opened up in his gullet. Whatever he needed to protect her mind. A joyful shout bubbled up inside him, even as he swatted a spore away from his face with a whip of sheer magic. Dom folded his way through the mindscape faster than a blink, materializing before the unassuming door to his Mistress' ever-sacred Space Room. The seat of her inner self. She never let him come here unsupervised, but he knew the password well from her many visits. Silly girl; she thought if she only thought the password and didn't say it, he couldn't hear it.

He murmured the phrase with an ironic lift to his voice, and the door opened. Her magic awaited, warm, sweet waves of it that rolled over him. Bliss, pure and welcoming. He didn't have time to bask in it, however. With an outstretched hand, he called to the sun. Her magic resisted at first, wary of him—as it should be—and already trembling under the force of the attack on the girl's mind. Despite her magic being too unsettled to respond readily, the will she had attached to her edict was unshakable, whether she had the attention to enforce it at the moment or not.

Use whatever magic you need.

The truth of it was undeniable, and the magic acquiesced with a shudder. He drank it in until he was swollen with power. Not all of it—not even most. Just enough to send these impudent, infidelic spores back into oblivion.

He barred the door to the Space Room with a wall of fire and swept through the corridors like an ancient plague, sucking the life from every spore, crashing up into the study on a tidal wave of power. The scrolls with carefully constructed decoy memories were on fire, and the carpet that concealed the trapdoor was nothing but ash. None of that worried him—mental objects could be recreated on a whim. What drew his immediate notice was the open cabinet door swinging freely from its broken hinge.

That man's magic was loose. Whether the spores had somehow damaged the lock or the foreign magic had sensed the inattention of its keeper, it was gone from its prison, only an empty vial remaining.

With a roar, Dom vaporized the spores in view and went hunting. The little vial of collected magic lacked true autonomy, so removed from its owner—it could not have gone far. He stepped out of the mountain and drew on the fresh magic in his stomach. On a great breath, his form stretched and grew, until he more resembled a colossal cheetah, claws like knifes and teeth enough to rip through anything in his path. In a skin befitting his magnificence, Dom tore across the mountainscape in a streak of menace, consuming the spores in his way. The whole world was fire, but his was the hotter flame.

Time was ephemeral, but he had spent nearly all the magic he'd taken by the time the last of the spores had been snuffed. Dom regained his humanoid form with a faint scowl. He had not found the foreign magic.

With the immediate enemy defeated, Dom closed his eyes and took stock of the whole of his domain, one piece at a time, soothing the worst of the damage, until he found it. With a smirk, he stepped from the mountainside to the pyramid. The ball of magic had managed to shift between the layers in the girl's mind. It struggled and squirmed, caught in the claw of a curious Sphinx. Dom shook a finger at it. "Naughty, naughty. You shouldn't wander. Thank you, lovely." He gave the lion-bodied guard a measured stroke and relieved her of her prize.

He transported them back to the mountain layer in a flash, a frown of contemplation on his face. What to do with the enterprising little ball of snot? His host had enough to worry about without wondering if her enemy's magic was gamboling about whenever his back was turned.

Dom sat heavily in his chair by the fire, patting his belly, full for the first time in ages, with regret. He shuddered, clenched his construct's muscles, and let the magic go. It climbed out of his throat, scalding as it went, and scurried back to join with its larger part in the Space Room. Dom watched it flee, breathing heavily. When the warmth of the sun had faded from his system, he turned his gaze to the magic captive in his fist. It was better not to risk re-mixing them, he knew, but it didn't make his next meal any more appetizing.

With a decisive lunge, he swallowed it. The magic struggled all the way down, but it, as all magic before it, bent to his will in the end.

"This is not on." Ron's voice was flat with righteous indignation. Neville didn't have to ask what he meant; it was everything. All of it.

They were in the highest section of the Southwest stands, with a clear view of Rigel's side of the tower. As its near-vertical face twisted around the corner, they could barely make out Owens' form, too. Delacour wasn't visible, but they could see her progress on the large mirrors, which transitioned smoothly between transmission runes set at various angles around the tower and stadium.

"He's halfway through," Neville said quietly. It was cold reassurance, and they both knew it. This task had seemed cruel from the start; now, it was beginning to look impossible. Rigel had stopped again, shaking his head slowly back and forth, a confused frown on his sweaty face whenever the mirrors reflected it up close. This was the dozenth or so time he'd stopped, and each time it took longer before the Slytherin started moving again.

"Owens is catching up."

Neville wasn't sure which of the Gryffindors around them had said it, but they were quickly shushed. He eyed Owens' jerky progress in relation to Rigel's. The American wizard kept twitching to look behind him, and there was a wild, unsteady look in his eyes that the mirror magnified a hundredfold. Whatever they'd had to drink, it had almost completely compromised their higher thought processes.

Rigel started to move again, but it was slow—so slow it was painful to watch. The boy's head suddenly whipped around in confusion, and a moment later, Neville heard what had caught his attention—a scream. The mirror flashed over to Fleur, who lay crumpled in a heap, her foot twisted at an unnatural angle.

"Bloody hell," Ron croaked. "I think she fell to a lower platform."

The French witch's limbs trembled visibly in the mirror and tears fell freely down to her chin, where they caught for a moment before dripping to the metal plate under her hands. Neville looked to the Mediwizards standing below on the pitch, but none of them moved to rescue the girl. One of them appeared to be physically restraining Madam Pomfrey, whose shouts were carried away by the wind.

His voice caught in his chest a little as he said, "They aren't going to help her."

Ron cursed colorfully, his face beginning to turn red. Neville understood his frustration. This wasn't entertainment; it was pure, unbridled torture. What were they supposed to be proving—how much absolute misery they could handle before giving up?

"How long do you think it would take to prank Riddle?"

Neville craned his neck around to see Fred and George in the row behind them, red heads bent together. George had his eyes fixed on Rigel's slowly climbing form, but Fred's gaze was lasered in on the Top Box.

"At least a year," George answered. When Neville realized they were serious, he winced. The twins were scary when they dropped the joker act.

"Lotta surveillance, probably," Fred agreed. "Might have to turn someone on the inside."

"I reckon we could—"

Ron sucked in a breath and Neville whirled back around to face the pitch. Rigel's foot had slipped, the only thing keeping him from a nasty fall the fingers of his left hand, which were stuck fast to the metal rung. "Thank Godric for those gloves of his," Ron said with a sigh of relief. "Blimey, this is gonna give me grey hairs"

Neville watched Rigel shake his head sharply and haul himself up to the next rung. He was high enough now that the wind buffeted him violently, his hair and jersey in constant motion. Neville felt his stomach turn over as the mirror zoomed in on Rigel's scared, confused features one more. It didn't seem right that a nice bloke like Rigel should have to go through this. Neville had watched the first task in sheer terror, but comforted himself with the thought that Rigel had probably known what he was getting into. The second and third tasks had been rough, but his friend got through them well enough. He hadn't known what to make of the fourth task—it seemed as though someone had been trying to make a point, but he wasn't sure what it was. This, though…it was just mean. Whoever reached the top first wouldn't be the best wizard. They'd just be the one who fumbled their way to the finish with the least accidents.

Rigel groped for the next rung. George whispered from over Neville's shoulder. "Come on, Pup."

"Keep going, Rigel." Ron stared at the boy as though the fervency of his gaze alone could sustain him.

Neville added his own murmur to the hundreds of others that were no doubt going up around the stadium. "You can do it, Rigel. Don't give up."

It was hard to believe it helped. With a series of cringe-worthy lurches, Rigel finally topped the last of the platforms. Neville's knees felt weak with relief and he watched the boy approach the flag that represented the finish line. His heart rose—then froze, as Rigel's hand came up against an invisible barrier.

"No…"

"That's cheap!" Ron's snarl of outrage drowned out his own weak protest.

It wasn't fair. It wasn't—he made it to the top. What kind of sick game were they playing? Rigel beat against the barrier weakly, the most pathetic look of hopeless denial on his face.

"What do they expect him to do in that state?" Ron snapped. "He's barely upright."

"It's not enough to get to the end of the task. He's got to beat the draught, too." George said it with a resigned sort of realization. "This won't end until one of them fully fights through the drug."

Neville felt his shoulders slump. Who knew how long that would take? Delacour hadn't moved from where she landed, all the fight seeming to have gone out of her. Owens had his wand out and his back against the tower. He brandished the stick wildly in every direction, seeming to see something no one else could. And Rigel—Rigel was staring dumbly at the invisible barrier, a frozen denial on his face.

The sky tilted on its axis, spilling blue all over, and the sun rolled above her. She shut her eyes and rested her head on a wall that wasn't there. She was so tired. So lost. How did she get here?

Climb.

That voice had been echoing for what felt like hours, but there was nowhere left to climb. A sob bubbled up in her chest. Where was she supposed to go now?

Behind her eyelids, people and places swam together in a sea of sound and color that had been swirled all out of order. She could smell fish and goat cheese and taste fairy wine. There was a trick there…somewhere. Archie was whispering her name—why was Archie there? He pressed a knife into her hand. She didn't understand. There was a trick here. Somewhere.

Kid, what are you doing?

Her ears pricked, she tried to decide whether the words were real. She opened her eyes but didn't see anyone beside her. "I don't know," she told the voice, just in case.

Did you finish?

"I finished…climbing," she decided, looking around the barren platform. "No more—nowhere left."

That doesn't…never mind. I got things under control in here. You should be able to use your magic again.

Magic. She liked her magic. She opened and closed her hands, then frowned. That wasn't right. How to reach—there. It was inside her, warm and comforting. Strangely, it made her want to cry. She was so tired.

That's it, girl. Use the magic. I can help, but you've got to be the one deciding. You want to flush the confusion out, don't you?

She nodded slowly. She wanted the fog to blow away. Then she could see the trick.

Will it. I'll guide it to start—just wish as hard as you can.

She closed her eyes and put a hand to her heart. Please, please, please, take the confusion away. Wash it off, blow it out, scrape it, squash it, please, please.

Got it. Hang in there.

The warm magic was wrestled gently from her grasp, and she almost cried out, but immediately she felt the trembling confusion recede the tiniest of bits. This was good. She wanted this. Strand by strand, she felt the tapestry of her conscious mind delicately woven back into place. When she remembered what she was supposed to be doing, she stiffened and her eyes snapped open.

The tournament. The task. The tower.

The stands were just above her—she was at the top. Students screamed down at her, some pointing. Rigel shook her head, her vision swimming as she caught a glimpse of the ground, so far below her.

She felt the shimmering magic of an active ward a few inches from her nose—could recognize it now, and Rigel realized there was something else she had to do before she could rest. Dom was making swift work of the chemicals in her nervous system. She could feel motor control returning to her muscles, along with an ache as they protested their recent treatment. Rigel didn't want to think about how she had no clear memory of climbing the tower at all.

She flexed her control, grasped the reigns of her magic and pushed Dom firmly aside with a mental wave of gratitude. It had been his voice, she knew now, urging her over and over to keep climbing. She knew she didn't have time to completely flush her system of the draught, but she could mitigate its effects on her mind with sheer magic for a relatively short period of time, the same way she'd forced her limbs to cooperate with magic until they were properly under her control again.

Rigel held her faculties as steady as she could, determined to finish this task quickly. First, she had to know what kind of ward she was dealing with. She flared her magical awareness and flinched—there was a core right behind her. She spun on her knees to see Owens towering over her, his footing unsteady and his eyes wide. There was something wild in his gaze, something glazed that told her he wasn't seeing her in that moment.

"Owens…" she said, her voice croaking. She held up a placating hand, even as the other one groped for her wand. "We don't have to fight. We'll both get top marks if we get through together."

"You're not…supposed to be here," he snarled between deep, unsteady breaths. "I left you…there. I left you."

"The draught is making you see things, Owens—Jacob," she pleaded as he lurched forward a step. "Listen to me. Do you understand?"

He swayed in the wind, trying to step toward her. "I understand everything. You don't under—"

He tripped, and Rigel stunned him. The bolt of light was weak and wobbling as it left her wand, but Owens was in no condition to dodge. She caught him, lowering the boy to the precarious platform with trembling arms, and panted for a moment to regain her strength.

The ward. She had to take down the ward. The drug pulsed against her magic, so many compromised synapses firing out of turn. Archie. The knife. What—

Focus, kid.

With a heave of mental effort, she put her train of thought back on track and flared her magic at the ward again. Rigel whimpered as she recognized it—a blood ward. A bloody blood ward.

Whose blood did she need? Her brain was in physical pain from the strain of forcing it to fire along the pathways she needed it to. They didn't have her blood. It shouldn't matter… Rigel eyed Owens for a long moment. She could use his…a tiny cut, just a baby one, an Addy little…

She shook her head sharply. Tested the ward again. Groaned. "Willing, has to be willing." Okay. That was fine. Why was it fine? She had a… trick! There was a trick. It was hers.

Quickly, Rigel took off her fingerless gauntlet and glove, feeling the skin on her left wrist as it pulsed with the force of her blood pressure. Her fingers grasped for the smallest of edges… there. Visibly concealed, but perceivable with a careful touch, was evidence of the skin graft performed months ago.

Willing… yes, Archie had been willing to give it.

Her wand, sharpened with a shaky whisper, sliced carefully through the graft to the flat pouch of blood behind it. The barest of trickles as liquid was released, her wrist against the barrier, and she was falling forward. She caught herself raggedly on the flagpole and buried her face in the white folds for a long moment. The noise in the stadium was unbearably loud. Someone was shouting something—Bagman, she thought—but her energy was flagging rapidly.

She couldn't keep control of the magic any longer. As the bulwark fell, the tide of chemicals advanced once more, and she felt her consciousness falter, flicker, and sink.

She was floating, rocking, cradled by the soft hands of magic herself. Content to drift, she let the gentle motion take her deeper, pulling her under like a riptide until its abrupt cessation startled her awake once more.

Madam Pomfrey stood above her. Rigel was back in the tent, staring up from her cot, and for a long, suspended moment, she wondered if the entire thing had been a dream. The thought that she might not have even started the fifth task yet was so upsetting she forced herself upright, straining against gravity to sit up and stare about her.

"Lie down this instant, Mr. Black. You have been through quite an ordeal and I must heal you—"

"No." The word was torn from her lips at once. "No, I will heal myself."

She was not quite as bad off as she had been before. Some things were still confusing—how had she gotten back to the tent? How long ago had the task ended?—but others Rigel was perfectly clear on. No one would treat her. She and Dom would work through it in their own time.

"The others," she said through dry lips.

"They are here," Pomfrey assured her, gesturing to the other cots.

Rigel blinked. So they were. Had she missed them coming in? Owens was unconscious—her doing, she dimly recalled. Fleur was awake, but wracked with convulsions, her eyes straining up toward the ceiling. Two Mediwizards stood over her, wands out, murmuring diagnostic spells.

"See to Owens," Rigel insisted, laying back down slowly. "I can handle the rest of it." She hoped she could, at least.

As Pomfrey moved over to Owens' cot, or maybe much later—it was difficult to know—Sousa ducked into the tent. His expressive eyes went to Delacour, still trembling, now unconscious, and he said, "I come to apologize. It should not… the dose should not have done this."

One of the Mediwizards looked over with a dark scowl. "The amount in her system is out of order. She could have died."

Matheus shook his head helplessly. "I calculate it right. I don't know… the dose must be tampered with." The boy ran a hand through his beautiful hair. "But if they are switched, one of you should be only weakly affected." As Owens was still unconscious, he turned to Rigel. "Were you pretending?"

She blinked at him, having only followed most of the conversation.

He sighed. "No, I see. These British ingredients are unreliable, or her creature blood messed up the dose." He apologized again, eyes lingering on the pale French witch, before retreating from the tent.

Rigel drifted in and out of the world, and slowly her mind turned the problem over. She wondered about the doses. If the wrong dose almost killed Delacour, then a double dose should have killed Rigel. If it didn't, then she couldn't have taken a double dose. Which meant… she grasped at the answer for a long time. Finally, it solidified in her stomach. The doses were switched. If she drank Fleur's, and Fleur drank Rigel's…then Rigel had only had the regular dose intended for a female, and Delacour had been double-dosed.

The conclusion satisfied her, until the implications crept up over her shoulder. Someone had switched the doses. To make sure Fleur lost… or, more likely, to make sure Rigel won. Not knowing she was a girl, someone must have assumed she'd perform significantly better under what should have been a half-dose for a boy.

"Bastard," she muttered to no one in particular.

One moment, she was glaring at the tent ceiling, the next, someone was nudging her awake. Rigel jerked violently and blinked her vision back into a single picture. It was Owens, standing over her again, only this time, his eyes were sane.

"Just checking to see if you're still alive," he said casually.

The American looked as though he'd never drank the Delirium Draught, and Rigel thought enviously that she could be as put together, too, if she allowed Madam Pomfrey to heal her. The temptation was brief; there were far too many reasons why that was a bad idea. She had never wanted someone else combing through her mind less.

With a groan of annoyance, she waved the boy away, rolling over to put her back to him pointedly. Rigel would deal with him later, if she had to deal with him at all.

Owens laughed softly and said, "Suit yourself. Sousa says this stuff might wear off on its own in another hour or two."

The thought was a bleak one, but it kindled her resolve. She had to stay awake. Had to start flushing the toxins in earnest, again. Her rest was over.

When she heard Owens' voice again, her first thought was that he hadn't left, after all. When she rolled back over, she realized he had left the tent, but was standing just to the side of the entrance, speaking low—but not lowly enough that she couldn't hear him.

"Don't bother. He's still out of it."

"I thought you were going to—"

"I did. It's not my fault the draught knocked him on his ass."

"You speak as though you fared any better." Rigel knew that voice. She cursed the confused neurons in her brain. She knew she knew it.

Owens let out a hiss of annoyance. "What's so special about him, anyway? You've held his hand through this entire tournament. Every task was geared toward him or fixed for him. Every clue. Every test. I should be your apprentice, not some half-reluctant, hostile little—"

"That. Is. Enough. Now is not the time or place to brandish your insecurities."

Her mind produced images without context: The Chamber of Secrets, Tom the teenager, insecurities fresh on the surface, the locket from the lake, the article about Morfin and Marvolo—Riddle! She held tight to the understanding. Riddle's voice had been the one she recognized, though there was something weird about it, soft and subtle…

Rigel shook herself back to reality and looked around. Owens was gone. She didn't see or hear either him or Riddle. She looked over to the lone Mediwizard who was still standing over Fleur's bed, a troubled frown on his face.

"Did you hear that?" she asked.

He looked over at her, surprised to see her awake, perhaps. "Hear what?"

"That conversation…"

The Mediwizard gave her a pitying look. "You're going to hear things and see things that aren't real until the drugs wear off."

Rigel nodded, slumping back to her cot once more. Everything was so confusing. She just wanted to sleep. Before she could summon the willpower to either fight through the rest of the draught or let herself slip back into unconsciousness, the decision was made for her.

"Rigel! Thank Merlin."

Pansy's arms were around her shoulders; Draco's palm was on her head.

"Pomfrey says you won't let them heal you, so we're taking you back to the common room," he said.

Rigel looked between them, not entirely sure whether they were real or whether her mind had conjured the most comforting image it could come up with. "Really?" she asked, hope threading her voice. "Are you really here?"

"Oh, Rigel." Pansy squeezed her gently and stood. "Nothing could keep us from you."

"Nothing and no one," Draco confirmed. "If we have to carry you, levitate you, or smuggle you transfigured as a rock, we're getting you out of here one way or another."

"We're taking you home."

Chapter 13

It was hard to accept congratulations for the fifth task when she didn't remember most of it. Everyone in the castle seemed supremely confident that she would win the tournament outright. Hadn't she outperformed the challengers at every turn? Wasn't she looking forward to carrying the champion cup into the Great Hall at the end of year feast?

Rigel tried to avoid the well-wishers, and when she couldn't, her friends ran interference. Rigel has to prepare for the final task. You can congratulate him when it's over.

Under the weight of such eyes everywhere she went, she found her head often bowed and the breath heavy in her chest. When Dumbledore stopped by the Slytherin table with a formal invitation to his soiree, she grasped it with both hands.

"What is that?" The flat tone told her Draco already knew. Rigel admitted to herself that she probably had forgotten to mention she was attending.

"Dumbledore invited me to the spring soiree this year."

"That is highly inappropriate," Pansy protested. "He's your headmaster. He shouldn't be steering you politically."

"But it's okay for everyone else to?" she said dryly. "I'm not the only student who will be there."

"The Weasleys, Bones, and Longbottoms attend every year," Millicent allowed. "But they are all Light-aligned."

"Are you sure I'm not?"

There was general spluttering at that. "You go to the SOW gala every year," Draco said. "And my parents' summer garden party."

"And I still will. I'm Neutral," she said firmly.

"You're the Triwizard champion," Theo said with exasperation. "Don't you know what it looks like, you going to this thing?"

"Yes, I do."

Theo gaped at her. "So, you're throwing your support behind the Light? You can't do that and claim neutrality. I knew there were some things about our platform you didn't agree with fully, but I thought…"

"You thought I would support a platform I didn't believe in? One that actively works against the interests of people I love? Why?"

"Ambition," he muttered. "Thought you and Snape were birds of a feather."

Rigel felt her gaze go cold. "I don't think you understand Professor Snape or me at all."

Pansy put a hand on hers and said, "Let's not argue over breakfast. Rigel, you can support whatever platform you like. Just be careful. Some of the Light sect won't be able to look past your connections to the other side."

She pulled her hand from beneath Pansy's and looked her square in the eye. "They told me the same thing about your sect, and they were right. There are uncompromising people on both sides." She could still remember the way her schoolmates had stood very still and quiet the first time she encountered Caelum Lestrange at a Party function. "I won't apologize for not being one of them."

"No one is asking you to apologize," Blaise said. He sounded tired. "If you want people to understand you, you just have to explain yourself every once and a while."

Rigel deflated. Now she wanted to apologize, but for what she wasn't sure. Her friends were never the ones she wanted to push away.

"Go and schmooze with the Gryffindors, then," Draco said, dismissive pride in every syllable. "Just don't forget who was with you at the start."

"I haven't." The start was further back than he imagined, though. Draco and Pansy and the others got to know her as Heir Black, but before that Harriet Potter had a start of her own. It was to that beginning that she owed allegiance. It was for the Harrys of the world that she would go to Dumbledore's soiree.

It sounded noble in her head, but she felt like a villain as she put on her dress robes at the end of the week. Draco and Theo ignored her when she said, "See you later," on her way out of the dorm. Blaise at least looked up from his periodical to nod.

Pansy met her at the common room door. She looked down at Rigel's boots and said, "No." A transfiguration that Pansy promised would wear off by the end of the day, two straightening charms for the wrinkles, and a smoothing spell for her hair later, Pansy put her wand away. "I suppose you'll do," she said, attempting a smile.

"Thanks, Pan. I'm hopeless without you." Rigel shifted in her altered shoes. "Also, I'm sorry for what I said the other day. You've been nothing but welcoming."

"I know it wasn't aimed at me." Pansy's smile was stronger, though, when she bid Rigel farewell.

She resisted the urge to jog across the sweeping lawn in her dress robes, though something about the field of new spring grass made her want to run. Her heart lifted just a little at the thought. What would it be like to start running and never stop, never look back? Rigel squashed the urge ruthlessly until her pulse was calm and steady again. There was no room for regrets on her path.

As she approached the group of students at the gate, she heard a voice say loudly, "What is he doing here?"

The cluster shifted as people turned to look her way, and she saw all four Weasleys, Neville, and a number of other Gryffindors and Hufflepuffs she knew.

"Albright, wasn't it? Nice to see you again," she addressed the shorter boy who'd called her out.

He scowled in her general direction without looking at her. "Someone tell Black this is a Light event."

"Get over yourself, Eric," Fred said lightly. George grinned in a less-than-friendly way.

"Yeah, Rigel is a cool Slytherin," Ron put in fiercely. He looked over at her uncertainly. "What, ah, are you doing here, though? You never come to the soiree."

"I haven't been invited before."

"Your folks come every year," Neville said softly. "Not that we aren't glad to have you now."

"Rigel doesn't do politics until he does." Ginny had her arm looped through the elbow of a girl with long, wispy blonde hair and a Ravenclaw tie. "Have you met our neighbor, Luna? Luna, this is Rigel."

The girl blinked large eyes at her and tilted her head in a way that bounced a radish-shaped earring against her cheek. "Daddy did a segment about you in his newspaper," she said, her voice a little breathy. "We both think it was terribly inhumane to set those nargles on you in the fifth task."

Rigel glanced at Ginny, whose sharp smile was vaguely threatening, and said, "Thank you, Luna. It's nice to meet you."

"Meeting people is nice, isn't it?"

"The portkey is warming up," Cedric Diggory called. They pressed into a tighter cluster around a long rope that had begun to glow faintly.

Ron passed a loop into Rigel's hand and she gripped the rough length of it tightly in her fist. The glow became a flash and her guts tried to move through space without her before the rest of her body caught up like a rubber band snapping back into place. She landed hard on the ground, sprawled beside the others, and grasped dazedly at the first hand in her face.

Diggory pulled her to her feet with a grin. "Portkeys are endless fun, eh Black? I wonder what wizard first taught the universe to chew people up and spit them back out."

"I'm sure the universe has always known how to do that. Some cheeky witch probably just condensed the experience down to a single instant." She straightened her robes just in time for Ron to slap her on the back and rumple them again.

"Good one, Rigel. It's always the witches. Come on, then; you remember the Burrow, I hope?"

She shook her head as she took in the Leaning Tower of Weasley presiding over an entire field of festivities. Enormous white pavilions dominated the yard, their panels secured by colored ribbons to golden poles. Food sprawled in piles on every surface and refreshments bubbled out of fountains interspersed between the pavilions. Each tent was guarded by an ice sculpture as big as a man, which ranged from lions, badgers, and ravens to phoenixes, dragons, and sphynxes. "I think I'd remember if you lived at the circus, Ron."

"Mum's really outdone herself this year," he agreed. "The ice animals were probably Dumbledore's doing, though."

"You'll notice there aren't any snakes," Albright hissed from behind them.

She eyed him as he passed. "Could have fooled me."

"Don't let him get to you," Ron advised. "The Albrights are a bunch of self-righteous types."

"Twats, you mean." Ginny bumped her other arm companionably. "Rigel knows well enough how to handle those—got a whole house full of them, don't you?"

"I hope you're referring to my school house and not my family."

Ginny affected an alarmed look. "Would I insult your beloved Harriet?"

"You have repeatedly done so to her face."

"That's how I show affection."

"That explains so much, little sis." Fed pounced on the girl like an oversized cat. She yowled fiercely but was unable to escape the hair-mussing that followed.

"All this time we thought you hated us, when really you were crying out for affection." George encapsulated the girl and his twin in a rather violent embrace.

"I yield," Ginny spluttered from the eye of the hurricane. "I take it back. Get off me!"

Her words only encouraged the twins, until Ron said mildly, "Mum'll be torched if Gin's dress robes are wrinkled."

Fred and George sprang back like guilty children. George coughed a quick straightening charm under his breath as Fred looked around for any sign of Molly bearing down on them. There was a Weasley headed their way, but it was Bill.

"Oi, the party is over here, you lot." Bill eyed his younger siblings with wry amusement. "Your straightening charm needs work, George."

"No straightening charm in the world can un-bend Gin," Fred said with a sly smile.

Gin elbowed him in the gut and stomped on a foot for good measure. "Anything else you'd like to say in polite company?"

"Just a general warning to all against little sisters," he muttered through a grimace.

"It's a special bond you have," Luna said suddenly. "I used to pretend you were my older brothers, too, when Ginny let me play here."

The Weasleys exchanged uncomfortable glances, and Rigel marveled at the Ravenclaw's ability to disarm all five of them simultaneously.

"Well, I came to wrangle the four of you before you scatter to the winds," Bill said when the awkward moment had passed.

George nodded seriously. "The general wants a word?"

"You guessed it."

"Better go make our reports, then. Rigel, want to say hi to our mum?"

"Not if you're looking for a human shield."

"Puppy, puppy, would we admit it if we were?"

"Please, Rigel," Ron wheedled. "She's much nicer to us around strangers."

Ginny tossed her hair and struck her brothers with a scathing glance. "Cowards, all of you. Come, Luna." She strode toward the house, the dainty Ravenclaw on her arm.

"Witches." Ron shook his head like a dog shedding water. He peered at Rigel hopefully. "Sure you don't want to come with?"

She looked over at Neville, who was hovering uncertainly. The pale boy shrugged his shoulders. "If you come with me, you'll have to say hi to Gran…"

"Are you all afraid of your female relatives?"

"You aren't?" Ron seemed genuinely bewildered.

"'Course he is." Fred sounded sure. "Have you forgot he's literally related to Bellatrix Lestrange?"

"Lady Malfoy, too," George said, ticking off his fingers. "Plus Andromeda Tonks, Nymphadora-don't-ever-call-me-that-again-or-I'll-eat-your-bollocks-Tonks, and the late but still horrifying in rumor Walburga Black."

A sudden chill passed a shudder between them.

"You forgot Aunt Lily," Rigel pointed out.

"Lady Potter? But she's so nice," Neville protested.

Rigel laughed. "Nice doesn't eat the Dark Arts for breakfast. Aunt Lily is terrifying."

There was a pause as the boys considered this.

"Maybe we should just stay here and not talk to anyone."

"Come off it, Ron." Fred shook his head.

George nodded. "It'll hurt worse if they have to hunt us down."

"To our doom, then?" Rigel suggested lightly.

Bill raised a hand to his heart. "Your sacrifice won't be forgotten."

"Where will you be, then?"

"Avoiding Mum, obviously." Bill slunk in the opposite direction, shoulders slouched and chin tucked as though his mother wouldn't be able to pick his distinctive shade of hair out of a crowd in milliseconds.

"That turncoat. I bet Mum never even wanted a word with us." Ron looked after his older brother with disgust. "Where's the top cover? The brotherly loyalty? He just wanted to throw us in her path as a distraction."

"Still, I should probably pay my respects to the hostess," Rigel said, somewhat apologetically.

Ron groaned. "And the first thing she'll say is 'where's Ron?'"

"You can do this," Rigel assured him with a bracing pat on the shoulder.

"Easy for you to say. You faced down a dragon, Rigel."

"Same basic principles," she offered weakly.

"Sure, just keep your wand at the ready—"

"—apply fire-free liberally—"

"—and don't ever turn your back on it!"

Fred and George dissolved into guffaws, but Neville straightened, a serious glint in his eyes. "There's no other choice, is there?"

Rigel grinned. "Exactly, Neville. When you realize the hard way is the only path forward, hesitation and fear become meaningless."

"Meaningless," he repeated, unconvinced.

"You'll still feel the curdling in your stomach, but it can't stop your feet if you really want them to move." She took a large step toward the party in the distance. "You try."

With a wry smile, he mirrored her movement. Fred and George hollered a war cry and made running leaps, and even Ron took an exaggerated stride. All solemnity dissolved, they made an ungainly series of leaps and jumps toward the square-pointed tents. As they squeezed between two pavilions, Fred and George traded off in single-file leaps over one another, finally spilling in a tumble of limbs and grins at their mother's feet.

"Oh, for Godric's sake, boys. Could you not last five minutes without working each other into a state of hysterical—Rigel! How good to see you, dear. What on earth are they feeding you up at that school? Come, get a plate; the pork hash is just come out."

"Thank you so much for having me, Mrs. Weasley," she said, bowing at the waist.

"So polite." Molly sighed and shifted narrowed eyes toward her brood.

Ginny held up her hands at once. "Now, now, Mum. Remember, Rigel likes me rude."

The fiery-haired woman looked between Rigel and her daughter with exasperation, but turned her attention to Ron instead. "Grown again, have you?"

Ron looked down at his pant leg, which came an inch or two above his ankle, and grimaced. "Bill was looking for you," he lied.

"I saw him ducking me earlier." Molly clucked her tongue. "Come to Dumbledore's soirée looking like a pirate—he should be afraid. Speaking of which." Her eyes cut to Neville, where they thawed. "Madam Longbottom is by the ice punch."

Neville slumped. "Probably looking to find something wrong with it."

"I dare her to try." Molly lifted her chin. "Rigel, you ought to say hello as well. She personally requested your presence this year."

That was news to Rigel. She turned curious eyes on Neville, who shrugged. "Not like she explains herself to me," the boy said.

The twins gave her wide-eyed looked of betrayal as she bowed again to excuse herself.

Neville blew out a breath when they were out of earshot. "I like Ron's family, but in pieces."

"Their cumulative presence is more than the sum of their parts," she agreed. "Did you really not know your gran asked Dumbledore to invite me?"

The Gryffindor slid a nervous glance her way. "She's asked me about you. Nothing personal; political stances and views, mostly. I think she's hoping you'll come over to our side."

Rigel frowned. "I've always agreed with Light politics. No one has to convince me."

Neville shot her a surprised look. "Thought you wanted to stay Neutral."

"I thought I did, too." She took a long breath. "I tried to. Used to think if I didn't bother anyone, didn't draw attention to myself, the world would leave me to my cauldrons. Now I find myself on the opposite side from what I would have chosen, simply because I didn't choose until it was too late."

"I don't think it's ever too late," Neville said slowly.

She smiled thinly. "I hope you're right."

They approached a towering fountain of pale blue punch that fell from the upper tiers in sparkling crystals like snow. Augusta Longbottom, formidably attired in stiff brocade with a stuffed vulture in pride of place on her wide-brimmed hat, held a wide-lipped glass before her eyes.

"Am I meant to wait until the drink melts or lap at it like a child with an ice cone?"

Alice Longbottom held her own glass beneath the gentle snowfall and watched the blue crystals collect with a smile. "I think it's fun."

"Fun. Good. That's why we gather the most prominent forces for the Light here in the wilds of Ottery St. Catchpole each year. For fun."

"Neville!" Frank Longbottom caught sight of his son cutting through the crowd and raised a hand to wave. Alice whirled and a smile beamed across the distance.

Neville shot Rigel an embarrassed look, but strode forward more quickly to embrace his parents nonetheless. "Hi, Mum. Dad."

"Sweetums, we've missed you. How is your second term going?"

"Made much progress on that Potions mark?" Augusta asked sharply.

Neville's ears turned red. "A little, grandmother."

Madam Longbottom appraised him sternly for a long moment, then set her drink on the rim of the fountain and opened her arms. "Well, come greet me properly, Heir."

Neville ducked his head to hide a grin and embraced the old woman gently.

"That's enough of that." Augusta reclaimed the delicate glass and prodded Neville upright. "Going to introduce us to your friend?"

"We've met before, Madam Longbottom," Rigel said, stepping closer when the family created space in their midst. At least, Sirius claimed they had. She had no memory of it, but they'd apparently been taken to Dumbledore's soiree as small children until they were too old to be carried in their mothers' arms.

"I doubt you recall it, young man. You introduced me to your invisible griffin who ate whole sticks of butter."

Rigel closed her eyes in embarrassment for Archie. "Finny ate raisins, too," she said with a wry smile.

"I believe it was you who ate the raisins, Heir Black."

She bowed with a flourish. "Raisin-eater and griffin-tamer at your service, Madam Longbottom."

Alice laughed. "How like Sirius you are. Is he here today?"

"Probably, but I haven't seen him yet," she admitted.

"Making the rounds before greeting your own family?" Augusta did not look impressed.

"Rigel came through on the portkey with us," Neville put in on her behalf. "He went to pay respects to Mrs. Weasley first, and she directed him to speak with you, grandma."

"As well she should. Do you know why you are here, Heir Black?"

"It would be foolish to guess if you are about to tell me," she said carefully.

"You are here to make an account of yourself to the Light."

"Mother, please." Frank turned a long-suffering face her direction. "He's fourteen."

"Do you suppose the Dark cares how old he is?" Augusta drew herself up to full height and glared down the slope of her nose. "Heir Black, you are the Triwizard Champion."

"The last task decides—"

"Don't interrupt. It is plain to all watching that you are the wizard who will emerge victorious. What is not plain is which side you will stand with when that happens."

Rigel waited a moment to be sure Augusta was finished speaking. "I stand with my family, as always."

"Well said," Frank muttered.

"I will be having words with Lord Black as well today," Augusta declared. "Left us in quite the lurch, turning Neutral all of a sudden. I understand he did it to keep a closer eye on you as you gambol about Dark society with your school friends."

Rigel could not refute that, so she inclined her head.

"I admit I wrote you off when you were sorted. Despite good influences, I assumed the Black genes had reasserted themselves."

"Mother…" Frank winced.

"However," she said with a sharp jerk of her chin. "My grandson tells me otherwise. Now I would like to hear it from you. Have you reconsidered your allegiances?"

"I have never declared them," she said.

"You did in deed if not word."

Rigel held her chin steady. "By attending my friend's birthday party, you mean?"

"By accepting blood ties to the Malfoys."

"A Life Debt is sacred, Mother. I am very sorry, Heir Black," Frank said firmly.

"I take no offense. I have learned that to be in the public eye is to face scrutiny for private relationships. I am a friend to the Malfoys. I am also a friend to the Potters, the Weasleys, and, if it pleases you, the Longbottoms." She sent a small smile to Neville, who returned it uncertainly. "I keep diverse company, and part of that is the nature of the house I was sorted into, and part of it is my own upbringing and preference. Those relationships don't dictate my politics, Madam. I…I support the Light."

There, she had declared it.

"And what does that mean to you?" Augusta pushed. "Good over evil? Truth against villainy?"

She wrinkled her nose. "Light politics, Madam, not fairy tales. It means I support the rights of muggleborns and halfbloods to equal protection under the law in all aspects of society. I believe in the humane treatment of all magical creatures and in fair dealings with our fellow magical beings. I oppose discrimination on the basis of blood or gender or magical ability. I oppose the doctrine of Magic is Might. I oppose political structures that benefit the few at the expense of the many. I oppose, in general, the concept of lineage as an argument for social superiority at all—and that includes the title I hold as Heir to the House of Black. Most of all, I oppose any system which puts children into moral or social categories before they learn how to hold a wand straight."

The Longbottoms, to a one, stared at her, until Augusta said, "It seems I was mistaken, then. I might have guessed, of course; your father declared his path late in life as well. Mind you don't do something so dramatic as running away on a flying motorcar."

"I'll strive to refrain from such a scene," she said dryly.

"Do."

"Mother…"

"Do what?" Sirius stole up behind her and clapped a hand down on Rigel's shoulder. "Frank, Alice, it's been a while. And young Neville, you are the spitting image of Frank in school, if you don't mind me saying. Madam Longbottom—but no, you haven't aged a day. Be honest—have you phoenixes in your ancestry?" He eyed the vulture on her hat with a devilish glint.

Augusta sneered. "Only the Blacks have what it takes to conceive of such unnatural things."

"Well, that is the Black family motto—'whatever it takes to conceive!'"

Rigel groaned. "Ugh, Dad, gross. Can we change that or something?"

"I'm afraid you need a supermajority of Blacks to change the motto, and Reggie won't be budged."

She lifted an eyebrow. "I bet I could get Aunt Cissy on my side."

"She doesn't count. You'll have to produce sons until you outnumber us." Sirius seemed to relish the horrified look on her face as he added, "Why do you think the motto never changes? It's a Catch-22."

"You haven't read that book."

"Lily explained it to me ad nauseum."

"Where is Aunt Lily?" Rigel shot back. "I can't imagine she let you off your leash so soon."

"I outwitted her."

"Unlikely. You recruited Uncle James to distract her, right?"

He barked out a laugh. "Close. I charmed Addy's hair to look like tiny snakes and ran away while she was figuring out how to fix it."

Rigel made a show of checking her pocket watch. "So you've got, what, sixty seconds until she bears down on you with the wrath of nesting dragon?"

"You'd know more about dragons than me," Sirius said, inspecting his fingernails unconcernedly.

"I hope you at least planted a false trail."

"I mentioned hours ago how eager I was to catch up with Gideon and Fabian."

She nodded in approval. "I'm impressed, Dad. The plan almost certainly hinged on her ally, Remus, being home after the moon, but still. You don't usually think it through that far."

"Lately, the future has weighed on me a bit. What is my legacy? What do I strive for? Why, I even have a vague inkling as to what I'll eat for dinner tonight." He sighed. "Must be getting old. Not as old as Augusta, mind you, but—"

"Enough! You Blacks are nothing if not tiresome." Augusta poured her glass of blue snow back into the fountain and set the empty container pointedly on its rim. "If you wish to disarm us, words are not enough. No amount of antics will make us forget who you call kin. I need deeds, Sirius, and your slide backwards into Neutrality is not reassuring to witness."

Sirius let the ready smile fall from his face. "Can't choose our kin, Madam."

"You can choose the Light."

"I have," he said quietly. "My public stance doesn't change that."

"You cannot be so naïve." The venerable woman fairly shook with the vehemence with which she spoke. "Public perception is everything to this campaign. All the world watches as the Black Heir proves the concept of blood purity and his father steps firmly back from his progressive platforms. Next thing I hear you're to organize a joint charity venture with Lucius Malfoy. Do you want Riddle to cash in every chip he's wagered for the past decade? Will you be satisfied when—"

"That will do, Mother." Frank's mouth had set into an unhappy line. "I'm sure you've given our friends plenty to think about."

"The time for thinking is almost over. Only actions matter now."

Augusta Longbottom drew her brocade overskirt back from her feet and left their company. Frank started to apologize, but Sirius held up a hand.

"She's right to be frustrated. I have made things difficult."

"You did it for me," Rigel said, nudging him gently. Guilty waves lapped at her heart. "Dad, you know…I mean, I never planned to make friends in Slytherin. It just happened. And then, I—I certainly never thought you'd have to sacrifice anything over it." When Sirius declared Neutral, it hadn't made the ruse any easier, but there had been a certain easing in tension between him and Archie. Perhaps it hadn't been worth it.

"Don't be such a martyring Gryffindor," Sirius said, a bit of his usual cheer threading into his tone. "I've made my choices and my peace with them."

"I would do anything for Neville," Alice said suddenly. She curled a protective hand around her son's arm. "I'd walk any path, if it led to his happiness. Augusta is set in her ways like most of the old guard, but we understand you, Sirius, and the complexities of the situation. Please don't think you've lost any friends over a label."

Sirius' smile was one she'd never seen before: fragile and uncertain, like it was built on air. "Thank you, Alice. Frank. Sorry to have spoiled the mood."

Frank waved his apology away. "The soiree is always more politics than party. We've come to expect a few dramatic moments—wouldn't be worth getting dressed up if no one made shocking declarations or mortally offended an Albright."

"Now, there's a goal I can get behind," Sirius said, making a show of looking around. "Where is old Ulrich Albright?"

"Probably inspecting the alloy ratios in the flatware," Alice said with a sly grin. As her eyes glinted with mischief, Rigel could suddenly see how she and Lily became friends.

"Want to watch your old man bully an even older man?" Sirius looked hopeful, but Rigel shook her head.

"Riveting as that would be, I'm going to find James and Lily." As his eyes flew wide in pronounced fear, she smiled. "I won't tell Lily I've seen you."

"This is why you're my favorite son."

"Where are you hiding the others, anyway?"

"Somewhere safe, in case you step out of line."

Neville coughed to cover a sudden laugh, and Sirius sent him a wicked grin. "Glad you were born Light, eh kid?"

"More and more, Lord Black," Neville muttered into his collar.

Rigel wandered through the various tents, looking for her mother's distinctive coloring. She finally found her near the apparition point at the outskirts of the party, glaring up at two men with matching cinnamon manes.

"—swear we haven't seen him," one of the men was saying, all the earnestness of a veteran player in his voice.

"Looking for Sirius, Aunt Lily?" Rigel called.

Lily spun, pure predation in her eyes as she clutched Addy's snake-free head to her chest. "Archie. Where is the wretch?"

"Gone to annoy Aldermaster Albright," she said. "He feels no repentance and will likely avoid you for the rest of the party."

One of Lily's victims edged away with a wide grin that revealed his genetic connection to Fred and George. "You see, Lily, might as well enjoy the soiree now—"

"—and punish Sirius at your leisure later," his brother finished.

Lily blew a lock of hair back from her face and readjusted Addy in her arms. "I suppose it's foolish to try tracking him all over Molly's garden."

"Well then—"

"—If that's settled."

The men executed a tactical attack in the opposite direction, and Lily scowled after them. "Those two…" She fumbled a moment as Addy made to dive from her arms. "Ah, yes, darling, you can go to Archie."

Rigel caught the free-diving toddler with an alarmed lurch in her stomach. "Hi, Addy," she said, a bit breathless as her sister gazed up at her with wide eyes.

"Hawee," Addy said, batting her hand against Rigel's mouth insistently.

Rigel craned her neck away from the sticky appendage. "No, Addy, it's Archie. Ar-chie."

"Hawee!" Addy shouted, her voice a little bursting crack.

Lily smiled at her apologetically. "You really do look very alike, Archie."

She sighed. "I know. Where's Uncle James?"

"I sent him to hunt down Sirius in case Fabian and Gideon were decoys."

"They're probably having drinks together right now," Rigel surmised.

"Dink?" Addy opened and closed her mouth like a fish out of water.

"You know that one, huh?" She grinned down at the copper-headed toddler. "Want to see a drink fountain that makes blue snow?"

"Dink."

With solemn approval from the goddler, Rigel led the way. As they wove through ribbon-wrapped tent poles, Lily said quietly, "How are you doing, Archie? We've heard…disturbing things about the fifth task."

"It was disturbing," she agreed, her face twisting. Addy smacked her clenched jaw and surprised a smile out of her. "Ow, Addy."

"Oh."

"Ouch."

"Ooch."

"I think she's making fun of me."

"This one is going to have some strange ideas about social norms," Lily said ruefully. She caught Rigel's eyes. "You didn't answer my question."

"I'm doing as well as can be expected," she said, aware that it was not entirely reassuring. "I just…I'm tired, Aunt Lily."

"Sirius has been beside himself with worry," Lily told her, a careful lack of reproof in her voice. "I think it's harder for him to hear about the tasks than it would be to witness them for himself."

She winced. "I didn't mean to make it harder on you all." She caught Addy's hand before it could smack her in the lip again and examined the tiny fingernails. Without looking at Lily, she added, "I feel like a different person in these tasks. Part of me doesn't want you to see that."

Lily wrapped her in a hug that gracefully encompassed Addy, too. "We would never think differently of you, Archie. These tasks are dangerous. Do what you must to survive with your mind and body intact. I understand how your decisions might be clearer when you don't have to worry what we'll think. I just want you to know that it won't matter to us either way. We just want you home."

Rigel bit back the moisture in her eyes with ruthless willpower. "I love you," she whispered. "I don't say it enough."

"We know, sweetheart." Lily held her until Addy squealed a protest at being squished between them.

She took a deep breath to clear the urge to break into shuddering sobs from her lungs. When she thought she could speak without croaking, she said, "It's fine if you all want to come to the last task. It's only right that you should be there at the end."

It was only one more task. The excitement of the tournament finale and their worry for Archie would likely forestall any questions her performance stirred.

The Longbottoms had wandered elsewhere, but there were a pair of familiar wizards inspecting the extravagant fountain when they approached.

"Lady Potter! The lioness herself appears." Raoul Goldentower swept a courtly bow, his husband a beat behind him.

"Lords Goldentower." Lily curtsied with the flare of a dancer. "I'm sure I don't have to remind you that I was not a Gryffindor."

"And yet, you are everything the fair house was built to emulate," Gareth declared. "Where is James? We've been meaning to duel him for your hand."

"As I am Lord Potter's champion, you'd be dueling me, I'm afraid," Lily said with a grin.

"Damned clever of him, making the task insurmountable," Raoul mused.

"Have you met my nephew, Archie?"

"At the Yule Ball, we had the pleasure," Raoul confirmed. "Mr. Black, how are you holding up?"

She shrugged, bouncing Addy into giggles in the process. "Well enough, Lord Goldentower. The finish line is fast approaching."

"And you seem poised to cross it first," Raoul said frankly. His partner snorted into his glass of ice punch. "It's not favoritism, Gary, only cold truth. I don't see the other two overtaking you in the last task."

"Do you know what the final task is?" Lily asked, unmasked concern in her gaze.

"It's no secret," Raoul confirmed. "They've begun growing the maze already."

Had they? That was news to Rigel, but then, she wasn't the most plugged into the happenings at Hogwarts.

"A maze? That seems…"

"Suspiciously wholesome after the last few?" Gareth gave a dark chuckle. "I wouldn't trust it."

"What do you think, Mr. Black?" Raoul's dark eyes glinted like whetstones.

Rigel grimaced. "I've no doubt in the organizers' ability to overwhelm us with their creativity."

"Keep that cynicism, boy. In the position you now hold, it'll serve you well," Raoul suggested.

Lily looked at her with significantly less approval. She knew it was not something Archie would have said—at least, not the Archie their family knew.

Gareth, perhaps sensing the solemn moment, changed the subject abruptly. "I'll be looking forward to Miss Potter's coursework when it comes in again this summer. After our last meeting, I read a few of her essays—damned insightful, if I do say so myself."

"You have, repeatedly," Raoul put in dryly.

Some of Lily's worry for Archie was swept away by surprise. "The correspondence course, you mean? Is she still doing that?"

"You didn't know?"

"I remember her asking for the tuition the first year, but then…I suppose I forgot." She glanced at Addy almost guiltily.

"Harry uses her earnings from brewing to pay for the courses," she explained quietly.

"She sells potions? At, what, fourteen?" Gareth shook his head in amazement. "Well, that explains the rigor of her assignments in that category."

"Who does she contract with?" Raoul asked.

"A couple of apothecaries in Diagon Alley," she said carefully. "Horace Burke has her on the hook for Blood Replenishers and a few others, as well."

"Burke? The devil never mentioned anything so interesting." Raoul seemed affronted at having been left in the dark on gossip of any kind.

"I'm sure Harry appreciates his discretion," she murmured.

"And I'm sure it was more self-serving than not. There's some who wouldn't trust a fourteen-year-old's brews, no matter her brilliance," Raoul said shrewdly.

"She must have been brewing younger than that, if she's been paying her tuition for two years with it," Gareth added. His confusion was polite, but marked.

Lily looked uncomfortably confused as well.

"Harry's always been practically minded," she said, trying to sound upbeat. "Combine that with Aunt Lily's brains, Uncle James' entrepreneurial instincts, Remus' organizational abilities, and Sirius' bad influence, and…"

The adults laughed. "Quite the pair of heirs you lot raised," Raoul complained. "Leave something of the world for the rest of ours, won't you?"

"How is Gilmyn?"

Raoul raised a hand to his lips and an ear-splitting whistle rang out. He gazed about imperiously, and Rigel supposed it must be nice occasionally to be head and shoulders above the crowd. "Ah. Here he comes."

"He's not a dog, Raoul," Gareth muttered.

"You're the one who objected to the leash charm."

"This is equally demeaning."

A curly-haired three-or-four-year-old shot around the fountain and nearly barreled into Raoul's feet. "Dad. Pa. I found you!"

"That you did, sport." Raoul hefted the child onto one shoulder and grinned proudly. "This here's my heir, Gilmyn. Gilmyn, say hello to Lady Lilian Potter, Miss Adriana Potter, and Mr. Arcturus Black."

At the sound of Archie's name, the boy's jaw dropped.

"Awe you lying, Dad?" He had the rounded speech of a boy who was not confident in his 'r's yet.

Gareth snorted, but Raoul ignored him. "Ask him yourself!"

Gilmyn stared down at her with something approaching awe and whispered, "Awe you weally A'cturus Black?"

She secured Addy to her hip and gave a proper bow. "At your service, Heir Gilmyn. Did you get my note?"

The boy nodded, eyes wide. The moment was broken by Addy's open hand slapping against Rigel's cheek with a resounding smack. She flinched. "Ouch, Addy." Addy giggled, and so did Gilmyn. Rigel smiled ruefully. "Fiercer than a dragon, this one."

"Awe you scawed of dwagons? I am." Gilmyn blurted.

She nodded. "Very scared. Dragons are super dangerous and they do not like wizards."

"But you fought one!"

"I was scared the whole time," she said seriously.

"Oh. That's okay. Papa says e'erybody gets scawed."

"He's right."

"And he says even G'yffindors do."

"That's true as well."

"And he says Daddy is the scawiest of all."

She hid a smile as Raoul's ears turned pink. "I can't speak to that one, but your Papa sounds very wise."

"Oh. I like you."

"I like you, too."

Raoul cleared his throat. "All right, little parrot. Where's your minder?"

"Aunt Buwi is with Aunt Thayet."

"Well, we can't trust those two together for long, can we? Better go find them, sprout."

Gilmyn laughed into his fist as he scampered away. Lily gazed after him with a wistful smile. "They grow so fast."

"Faster, if they have Goldentower genes," Gareth said, pointedly glancing at Raoul's long legs.

"We can't all be part giant."

She turned at the sound of James' voice, and took in the sight of him. Her father clasped hands with Raoul and took a clap on the back from Gareth before tossing a grin her way, "All right there, Arch?"

"All right, Uncle James."

"Did you find Sirius?" Lily asked pointedly.

James swept his immediate surroundings for escape almost automatically before manfully clearing his throat and saying, "Nope."

"Aren't you paid to find people, Uncle James?" Rigel affected polite confusion.

"Not anymore," he said defensively. "Now I'm paid to manage the people who find people."

"Like my wayward apprentice?" Auror Moody, as grizzled in person as he was in rumor, stalked into their midst with all the social grace of a hungry tiger. He wore robes that were not technically Auror garb, but mimicked it perfectly in cut and style. "She's supposed to be running perimeter."

"As this is not an official Ministry event, I am not technically responsible for its security," James said weakly.

"It's Dumbledore's soiree," Raoul said, rolling his neck unconcernedly. "You'd be mad to try and crash it."

"Dark wizards are not known for their rational, goal-oriented approaches." Moody glared around the loose circle with his piercing blue eyes as though one of them might be a Dark wizard in disguise. The sharp gaze landed on Rigel. "You."

"Yes, sir." The response came without conscious fashioning.

"Good lesson you taught my recruits in the fourth task."

"I didn't know I wasn't supposed to fight them…"

"Like I say—good lesson for them. Constant vigilance." He shouted more than said it, and James winced.

"If we see Tonks, we'll point her your way," James assured the old Auror.

Moody would not be hurried along. His eyes still fixed on Rigel, he said slowly, "You're a damned good duelist, Black. Your daddy didn't teach you all those fancy moves."

"Uncle Remus taught me dueling, actually."

"Bull."

"Remus did tutor him this summer," Lily confirmed. "Sirius and I did, too. He was progressing well."

"What I saw was more than 'progressing,' Closer to professional." Moody did not hide his annoyance with that fact. "So what's this nonsense I hear from Dawlish about healing?"

Rigel blinked. "As I told Auror Dawlish, I won't be joining the Auror corps." James whipped his head around in surprise, and she smiled reassuringly around Addy's hair. "I intend to become a healer."

"Give it up." Moody jerked his head in a dismissive toss. "I saw the way you dealt with Owens. You don't like innocents being hurt."

She dropped her eyes to Addy's sweet face, which was scrunched in a yawn. "That's why I want to heal people," she explained patiently as the toddler nestled into her shoulder.

"Bah. Help me bring Dark wizards to task—unless…you sympathize with them."

"That's enough, Moody. Archie's always wanted to be a healer." James put a hand on her shoulder firmly. "I think it's noble."

"It's a bloody waste," the senior Auror muttered. "Now, more than ever, we need people in the fight."

"Let's not talk shop—" James tried.

"Nonsense. People ought to know their cozy peace has an expiration date."

The Lords Goldentower exchanged frowns, and Gareth said slowly, "Auror Moody, we all know it's your job to prepare for worst-case scenarios. What's so different about these recent attacks that sets them apart from dozens of other isolated events over the past few decades?"

Moody inflated his chest like an overgrown bird. "Everything. They're organized. They're connected. There's messaging."

"Some of that rational, goal-orientedness, you mean?" Raoul drawled.

"Laugh while you can," Moody groused. "I've got sources from all the bad places that say there's something worse come into the shadows of late. Targeting traditionally violent groups. Recruiting. Orchestrating. And you think it's a coincidence extreme bigotry is being aired for all the world to see? No. I don't think so."

Rigel wondered if one of his sources was her anonymous tip. She wouldn't be surprised to hear that Bill Weasley was funneling information to the Light, too. He had invaluable access to the underworld of the alleys, for all that the thief's code would stop him short of giving specific names.

"I think you're right, Auror Moody," she offered, shifting a dozing Addy carefully to her other arm and shaking out the one that had gone numb. "It's not a coincidence."

"Certainly, the tournament has emboldened a few fringe groups, but that doesn't imply a direct connection between the two." James sounded as though he'd had this argument with his old mentor before.

There was a direct connection—Riddle, in two horrifying manifestations—but she couldn't say as much.

"There's Andromeda," Lily said suddenly. "Perhaps she knows where Nymphadora has gone."

Moody's head swiveled, a hound after a scent. Doubtfully, he grumbled, "If 'Dromeda had dragged her spawn here, she wouldn't be late."

"Only one way to be sure," Lily cajoled.

With a final, hard look around the circle, Moody went to hound Andromeda Tonks.

"Old Moody only has one track," Raoul said.

James nodded, though a frown pinched his brow. "He's been wrong before…but more often, he's right."

"When your hypothesis is 'Dark wizards are evil,' it's hard to be wrong."

Rigel didn't recognize the forceful voice, but she caught a grimace on both her parents' faces before they hid them behind polite smiles.

"Ulrich, impeccable timing, as usual," Raoul said, face blank.

"I was loath to interrupt such a serious conversation," the man said, striding into their midst with his shoulders rolled back and chin tilted up.

"And yet," James muttered.

The newcomer did not appear to hear him. He was a head shorter than the other Lords, and even Rigel had an inch or two advantage, but he made up for it in solid stockiness. Ash blonde hair bristled thickly on his round head and curled in a neat beard from broad cheekbones.

"Raoul, Gary. Potters. And…" He peered at Rigel for a moment before it clicked. "Ah. Heir Black. Your father mentioned you were about while he was making a nuisance of himself earlier."

"That's his general equilibrium," she said with a small smile. "Pleased to meet you, Aldermaster Albright. Your heir and I are classmates, of a sort."

"He's mentioned no such thing," Albright said with narrowed eyes. "Aren't you a fourth-year?"

"I'm in Dumbledore's Alchemy class," she explained. "We don't have class together, but as we are the only two students—"

"Alchemy is a Light art."

Rigel held back a sigh. She could see where Eric Albright had absorbed his rather skewed opinions.

"It was designed initially around Light runes, and the transition to the Neutral art we study today is fascinating," Lily said forcefully. "Did you know it was a Lady Black in the twelfth century who first applied Arithmancy to the calculation of material coefficients? Well, of course you did." She laughed and toasted Ulrich Albright with a glass of blue snow. "You are the Aldermaster of the Alchemy Guild."

"Indeed." Ulrich wrinkled his short nose, but didn't argue further. "And your heiress, Potters? I hear she's started down the guild route herself. Malcolm never shuts up about her," he added with a slight sneer.

"Harry is doing well, thank you for asking," James said through stiff lips.

"Not as well as thing one, though, eh?" Ulrich pinned her with storm-grey eyes. "Pureblood champion. It's thanks to you we've called in every political favor on our books this session."

"Now, Ulrich—" Raoul protested.

"He knows it, I'm sure," Albright drawled. "Slytherin, isn't he? Baptized in politics from the cradle."

"I was once baptized in the Dark Arts by our family House Elf," Rigel said blandly.

James snorted before he caught himself in a cough. "Ah, that House Elf was mad, Archie."

"Still, I was in a cradle," she said earnestly.

The Goldentowers laughed, but Albright's disapproving smile never faltered. "You're aware as well, I suppose, that if you win, public support will swing irreparably in favor of the S.O.W. Party and they'll pass the biggest packet of legislation since the 1989 Split?"

"Here, now," James began, fierce protectiveness on his face.

Rigel frowned. "It's all right, Uncle James." She met Albright's gaze. "I am aware of that, Aldermaster Albright. I wasn't when I started this tournament, but it makes little difference what my intentions were. I'll be judged by the results."

"As are we all," Gareth said with a pointed stare at Albright.

The Aldermaster seemed immune to peer censure. "What will you do about it, then?"

She pretended to misunderstand. "I'm not sure what I can do at this stage beyond surviving the last task."

Albright let out a hollow laugh. "Certainly don't die. Last thing we need is a pureblood martyr. A second-place finish wouldn't hurt, though, particularly if that Owens boy comes first."

"Are you suggesting my nephew throw an international tournament?" James had an Auror's warning in his voice.

Albright shrugged. "Not suggesting anything. Just noting the results of a hypothetical outcome out loud."

Rigel kept her face blank against the grimace that wanted to form. Of course, the one thing likely to help combat the legislation was the one thing the Unbreakable Vow prevented her from doing. "Is there no way to block the legislation regardless of public sentiment?"

The Aldermaster snorted and cut his eyes challengingly to Lord Goldentower. "Well, Raoul? You're the resident expert on the Wizengamot."

Raoul rolled a shoulder uncomfortably. "We're focused on swaying the Neutral members with a preponderance of seats. Unfortunately, the most principled of the Neutral sect see it as their duty to vote in accordance with the electorate's wishes. On this highly-publicized issue, it means public favor counts more than it might for more obscure legislation."

She ran the issue through her mind, the gears shifting and realigning with uncomfortable friction. Her free hand came up to cradle the back of Addy's head, as though she could shield her little sister from the dark turn of her thoughts. "I could become the villain," she said slowly. The adults around her went still. She looked at them uncertainly. "I could…do something terrible. Be caught in a scandal, or perform some barely-legal dark magic in the last task. If people were ashamed to support me, perhaps it would extend some unpopularity to the legislation I've become the symbol for."

There was silence for a moment. Lily and James stared at her in mild horror, but she could see their minds racing. Would it work? Would it be worth it?

Albright was the first to speak. "It's too late for that. You underestimate your base if you think they wouldn't rather deny your deeds than admit their mistake in believing in you."

She winced. That was perhaps the most cynical thing she'd ever heard.

James nodded, his face set in harsh lines. "You're better off untarnished, Archie. It sounds callous, but if the legislation goes through, we may need your pureblood credentials to soften the impact."

Raoul made a noise of unhappy agreement. "You make a good role model right now. What you do, other purebloods and even halfbloods may emulate. Don't throw that away."

Rigel wasn't sure if she should feel relief or frustration. On the one hand, she didn't want to bring shame to Archie's good name. On the other, she didn't relish the idea of playing the moderate pureblood for social politics.

"It seems I have found the gloomiest group in the garden." Dumbledore smiled genially as the circle opened for him. "Don't tell me you aren't enjoying your first soiree, Mr. Black; however will I convince you to come back next year?"

She hitched her mouth up for the older wizard's benefit. "On the contrary, Sir. It's just the diversion I needed."

He fixed her with a penetrating stare. "While I do believe you're in need of an escape, dear child, my suspicious old brain doubts you have found any relief from the pressures of the tournament here." Dumbledore shifted his gaze to the others in the circle, who, one by one, dropped or averted theirs.

Rigel hid a real smile. "We were just discussing the merits and pitfalls of popularity, Headmaster. Nothing too serious."

"Ah. Well, as someone who has experienced both unaccountable popularity and incontestable villainization, I would say public opinion is rather overrated." His eyes twinkled and he smiled with the serenity of a man who had long risen above the cares of his fellows. "My advice, for whatever small measure of the human experience it represents, is to seek truth, be faithful to your principles, do the best you can in every situation, and learn from your mistakes while forgiving others theirs."

She felt her heart sink a little. "And should we forgive ourselves for our mistakes?" she asked quietly, flexing the hand in Addy's curls. The pile of regrets in the back of her mind throbbed, like a tooth compulsively prodded.

Dumbledore's eyes stopped twinkling. "He who learns to do that may be the wisest of us all."

In the silence that followed, James took a deep breath. "Well, Archie, you've managed to depress even Dumbledore. You're officially the wet blanket of the party."

She snorted. "I am the common denominator, aren't I?"

"I know you don't want to hear it, Lily, but this situation requires Sirius intervention," he added.

Lily rolled her eyes. "A Weasley would do just as well, and you know it."

Rigel nodded. "One ought never convene a circle without a Weasley. Only solemnity can follow."

"There are certainly enough of them to go around," Gareth muttered.

James's face was animated as he gathered steam. "They ought to start a public utility company—get your Weasley! Instant levity to any moment!"

"Take a set of twins, double your money," Lily suggested.

Rigel gave a wry grin. "Discounts on the acrimonious she-Weasley. One-of-a-kind!"

Dumbledore hummed doubtfully. "Miss Weasley would be unlikely to participate in such a venture."

"She'd shave her head first," Rigel agreed.

"When I'm pressed to explain the unlikely friendship between the Potters and Blacks, I reference these nonsensical interludes." Raoul looked between Rigel and her parents with pure bemusement on his face.

James shrugged and Lily frowned thoughtfully. "I wonder if we learned it from Sirius or Sirius from us?"

"I'm convinced our families share a particularly mad gene somewhere in—"

They were cut short by a cry of rage that had been magnified tenfold on the wings of a Sonorous Charm. Addy woke at once and screeched for her mother, but Lily had drawn her wand. She held up a hand toward Rigel and said, "Keep her." Rigel clutched Addy tightly, despite the toddler's attempts at diving toward her primary caregiver.

"Was that—?" James looked to Dumbledore.

"Alastor." Dumbledore gestured to the ground beneath him, and it obligingly rose in a wave of earth that sent the rest of them stumbling backwards. The mound carried the wizard up a dozen feet, where he swept the horizon with a terrifyingly calm stare. "The apparition point."

James set off at a run. Lily took one step after him, but checked herself with a glance at Rigel and Addy.

"We'll be fine here," she started to say.

Dumbledore interrupted as he descended from his vantage point. The earth smoothed out beneath him like a blanket under the hand of an experienced maid. "There's no immediate danger." His blue eyes caught Rigel's. "Your services may be required, Mr. Black."

He made for the apparition point in long strides that reminded Rigel how tall the Headmaster was. Rigel relinquished Addy to Lily's bewildered arms and started after him.

"You've got your pendent?" Lily called after her.

She touched it and nodded, unworried. Dumbledore wouldn't lead one of his students into danger.

They approached the apparition point and found James and Moody bent over a prone figure in the shadow of the tree line. Molly and Arthur reached them at the same time, wands at the ready and a ghostly pallor in their cheeks.

"Not Andy's girl," Molly moaned, one hand coming up to her lips as she got a look at the crumpled body.

Arthur's grip on his wand was white-knuckled as he stared into the trees. "Attackers?"

"Dumped her here and left," Moody growled. He had fingers on his trainee's pulse and murder in his eyes. "Bled her first, but she's hanging on."

Rigel hurried forward and dropped to her knees beside the young woman, trying not to notice how her hair had reverted to its natural brown color. Her chest barely moved, and up close she realized Moody wasn't taking her pulse—he was holding her neck together.

She swept her magic out and took over the staunching while assessing the extent of the damage. Pulse not palpable, punctured trachea, hematoma over the anterior aspect of the neck, plus the neck laceration.

"Roll her over. I'm going to stabilize the cervical spine."

She wasn't fully aware of Moody following her instruction; most of her attention was on knitting the girl's airways back together while keeping the bleeding in check. When the trachea had fused, she immediately set her magic to the manual circulation of airflow through the lungs while the rest of her focus shifted to repairing the carotid artery.

"You can let go, now," she murmured.

Moody released his pressure on the young woman's neck, and blood immediately oozed out of the skin lesion. He went to put his hand back, but she stopped him.

"It's fine. Her blood vessels are healed—see how there's no pressure to the leak? That's just the hematoma draining."

She inspected the esophagus, double-checked the spine and the delicate vocal cords, and cleared residual blood from the site before closing the surface wound. She withdrew her magic carefully, waiting until the patient's system had taken over completely before switching to diagnostics.

Rigel dug into her pocket for a Blood-Replenisher. Moody caught her arm as she moved it toward his trainee and growled, "You just happen to have that on you, do you?"

"It's one of several emergency potions I always carry with me," she said. "I also have Pain Reliever, Modified Weightless Draught, Fever Reducer, Nutrient Potion, and a bezoar." James stared at her. She shrugged. "Harry insists."

Her father nodded. "That checks out, Moody. Harry carries an entire library of potions when she goes anywhere. I can't say it hasn't proved useful."

When Moody continued to glare suspiciously at her, she reminded him, "She's lost at least a couple pints. Her blood pressure won't recover until there's more in her veins."

He took the vial and held it up to the sun, swirling it. He inspected the cork seal, popped it open, and let a drop fall into his palm. Once satisfied, he handed it back with a scowl.

Rigel spelled the contents into the woman's stomach, then sat back on her heels. "Give that a minute, then it's safe to wake her."

Molly bustled the two of them out of the way. "There's still time to get that stain out," she said with a hiccup. Her lips trembled, but her wand was steady as she siphoned the blood from Tonks' clothing. "She'll want to be presentable when she wakes," Molly murmured, more to herself, it seemed. "Andy won't want to see all the…the…" She took a deep breath and met Arthur's pained gaze. "On our own land, Arthur. How could this have happened?"

"They got her somewhere else," James said. "Dumbledore would have noticed at once if someone uninvited crossed the wards."

"She didn't apparate herself here in that state," Arthur said slowly.

Moody brushed Molly's hovering hands away and searching Tonks' pockets efficiently. He pulled out a scrap of paper and a growl escaped him. "How many times have I told her to memorize the bloody coordinates?" He crumpled the parchment in a fist. "Someone side-alonged her here on purpose. It's a message, Dumbledore. Our people aren't safe."

Dumbledore's eyes were focused on something far-away, and his voice was heavy with consideration for a dozen variables Rigel would probably never understand. "Nymphadora is yet to be inducted. There is no more reason to target her than any other child of the Light. Less, as her Auror training presents a harder defense than the average witch or wizard."

"Perhaps she was in the wrong place at the wrong time," James said quietly.

"There are no coincidences in this world," Moody spat.

"Evil does not discriminate," Molly murmured.

"Humans do, though." Moody glared at Rigel. "Wake her."

Rigel roused the young woman with a gentle Rennervate. Tonks came to like a fish leaping from the water; with a gasp, her hand shot to her neck and she sat up so fast she almost head-butted Rigel.

"Vampire," was the first word from her lips. Her eyes caught Moody, and her entire demeanor calmed at once. "Sir. I was accosted en route to the apparition point near my apartment. Two men in rough garb. One in his late teens, dark skin and long hair. The other was six foot, but wore a cloth mask that obscured his face. I had my wand out, facing them, when something faster than my eye could track got me from behind. It moved like a vampire, and I thought it bit me, but…" she felt along the ridge of her newly-patched neck, and shivered.

"That was a knife wound, not a bite," Rigel said.

Tonks absorbed the information soberly. "Did you patch me up, little cousin?"

"Sorry I couldn't fix your face, too," Rigel offered with a lopsided grin.

Tonks turned her nose into a pig's snout and snorted at her.

"Focus," Moody snarled.

Tonks let her face relax into its true shape and frowned. "They didn't ask me any questions. Didn't even spout propaganda or insults at me. Just…" Tonks touched her neck again. "So suddenly," she murmured.

Rigel pressed her lips together even as her heart shook with a memory. A shadowed alley. A blue vest. Death was always a surprise.

"How did I get here?" Tonks asked suddenly.

"They apparated you here with the coordinates in your pocket," Moody said gruffly.

Tonks blanched. "Is everyone—did they try anything? Sweet Merlin, I put you all in danger."

"They'd be mad to move directly against Dumbledore," Arthur said firmly.

"Everyone is fine, dear," Molly added soothingly. "Your mother is—"

"Here."

Andromeda Tonks bore down on them with a storm in her eyes. In that moment, she really did look astonishingly like Bellatrix.

"Mum!" Tonks glanced down at her robes, but Molly had gotten most of the blood off already.

"Are you quite finished interrogating my child, Moody?" Andromeda moved the man away from her daughter with the sheer force of her gaze.

"I'm fine, Mum," Tonks croaked.

"You are fine only thanks to your cousin's magic," Andromeda snapped. She turned a challenging stare to Dumbledore. "I am taking my daughter home." With a withering glance at Moody, she added quietly, "She's not a soldier yet." She set her hand firmly on Tonks' shoulder and Disapparated them both with a twisting pop.

Dumbledore appeared pained, his head bowed slightly. To Arthur and Molly, he said, "I think it wise for the rest of us to follow suit." His gaze shifted to Rigel. "Brilliant application of Madam Pomfrey's teachings, Mr. Black. If we were on school grounds, I would award Slytherin two hundred house points."

She felt her mouth hitch. "It's for the best, then. Professor Snape would have been hospitalized for shock."

James choked on a laugh he stifled too late.

Rigel turned to give him a long hug. "I'm going to round up the other students. Say goodbye to Dad for me?"

James squeezed her hard and promised he would. "Good work, Archie. Really, really, well done. It seems I'm constantly thanking Godric for your interest in Healing."

"It's only because of Mum," she murmured quietly into his chest. "I never wanted to be the one watching someone die again."

James' voice was thick. "Diana would be so proud of you. We all are. You're gonna be better than all of us."

They broke apart, both composing themselves as the Weasleys and Dumbledore pretended not to notice. Moody just scowled at them. "Are you ready to work now, Head Auror?"

James put on his hard face and took out his wand. "I'll trace the last dozen coordinates. If they apparated her somewhere else before coming here, we might find a connection to them."

Rigel accompanied Dumbledore to the other side of the lawn, picking up Hogwarts students as they went. He fashioned them a new portkey with calm efficiency, using a conjured length of rope to anchor the magic, which Rigel hadn't known was even possible.

Before the sick feeling of dread in her stomach was overtaken by the literal nausea of the activated portkey, Rigel met Dumbledore's eyes and understood the regret that nested there. She summoned a rueful smile, realizing it had been foolish to seek some kind of respite at the soirée. There was no escape from their cold reality.

A letter of heavy vellum landed on Rigel's plate with a dull thump that drew the attention of her year mates at once.

Millicent actually leaned around Pansy to admire the smooth texture. "Is that vintage calfskin?"

Pansy plucked it from Rigel's hand so she could see it better. "With Moonglass ink, no less."

Millie raised her eyebrows. "Are you corresponding with a duke, Rigel? The vizier of a small kingdom, perhaps?"

"Someone French?" Pansy guessed.

Rigel took the letter back and gently untied the soft black ribbon. As she opened it to reveal ornate calligraphy in shimmering moonstone grey, the girls sighed in appreciation.

"Who is it from?" Millicent wheedled.

"And where do they shop?" Pansy added with a grin.

She skipped down to the signature and smiled. "Just an old-fashioned colleague."

"From the Potions Guild?"

Rigel tilted her head. "He's not technically a member, I suppose. More of an…enthusiast."

"How old is he?" Draco eyed the letter with a hard-to-read look.

"Ancient," Rigel said, amused.

After a few more appreciative comments about the smoothness of the vellum and fluid, uninterrupted lines of script, her friends went back to their breakfast. She pushed her plate to the side and dove into the letter's content properly.

Esteemed Friend,

In response to your query regarding our coven's well-being, we are not well at all. My laboratory was spared the conflagration, but several of my animals perished of smoke inhalation. Grandfather is most irate. The loss of his lieutenant is a foul blow. He is not technically perished; rather, lost in the literal sense. Since discovering his empty sickbed, Irvina stalks the alleys, bereft. I suspect she will not find him. Sometimes, when one of our kind senses the end is near, he will abandon his mate so she does not have to witness the passing.

I am ignorant to the nature of what evil poison affected Gavril so. Grandfather did not permit me to take his blood for examination. Even still, the most curious effects of mental deceleration, memory loss, and confusion lead me to suspect an unusual neuro-toxin. I mean unusual in the sense that it would be capable of affecting our kind, of course; I trust you know that such effects are not unusual at all in neuro-toxins generally.

I thank you for your concern, and for your munificent offer to assist in replacing lost ingredients, should there have been any. Fear not, for my work continues apace.

Yours in Common Purpose,

Kasten

Vampire. That's what Tonks said. Rigel closed the letter mechanically, worry making her fingers stiff. The Lamia's attack and Gavril's subsequent disappearance, Tonks' superhuman attacker—were they related? It seemed a large coincidence, but perhaps only because she was connected to both situations.

Moody's voice echoed ominously in her memory. There are no coincidences in this world.

"Bad news?" Draco asked, catching the frown on her face.

Rigel nodded. "It seems there are grim tidings everywhere these days."

"This will cheer you up, then." Pansy pushed a copy of the Daily Prophet toward her. Rigel looked down, and the headline "Date Set for Landmark Legislation Vote" screamed back at her.

Rigel's heart clenched, but Millicent was quick to reassure her. "It's set to the end of the session, see? Mid-June."

"Dumbledore's faction managed to buy a few extra weeks," Theo grumbled through his sausage. "For what good that will do them."

Her heartbeat slowed. "After the tournament, then."

Relief swept through her, a cool breeze after the sweltering humidity of stress. Rigel smiled. One thing had finally gone in her favor. As long as she won the tournament, Riddle could not directly intervene in the vote. He had carried it this far, but would have to rely on momentum to get it across the finish line. And she would be there waiting with every ally the light could muster standing in its way.

At 3am on Sunday morning, Rigel work to the sound of her cousin calling her name softly from the mirror she kept under her pillow.

"Rigel….pssst, Riiigeeeel."

Groggily, and accompanied by her roommates' annoyed grumbles, she pulled out the mirror and mumbled into it.

"Hang on, Harry."

"Ri—oh, good, you're up."

"Shhhh."

She tucked her toes into slippers and stumbled in her crumpled robes to the common room.

"Is this an emergency?" she asked through a yawn. Her cousin didn't sound frantic, but one never knew with Archie.

"Yes and no…."

"No, then."

The fires were low, but imminently coaxable. She stoked one higher and pulled a silver throw over to a low-backed armchair, settling into the comfortable cushion with a sigh.

"All right, cuz. What is it? I'm in the common room, mind."

"Great, no worries, I've got Hermione here, actually."

She felt her eyebrow twitch. Now he tells her. "Hermione, how are you?"

The curly-haired witch leaned into the mirror next to Archie. "Hi, Rigel! Sorry to wake you. I forgot about the time change in my excitement but—I mean—this is really something. I think."

"It really is," Archie confirmed.

"What is?"

"Well…" Hermione trailed off, unusually tentative. "I don't even know where to start," she said helplessly.

"Topic?" Rigel asked with another yawn.

"The Fade."

Some of her sleepiness vanished. "Right. Give me a moment, actually. Binny?"

"Who?"

"Not you."

Binny popped into the common room with the look of curious expectation common to House Elves when they answered a call on instinct alone. "Young Master Black! You is rarely calling me so late."

Rigel smiled sheepishly. "Sorry, Binny. Could I trouble you for a cup of strong tea?"

Binny's eyes crinkled in pleasure. "Binny is happy to provide!"

A cup of English black tea appeared on the small table beside her armchair, and Rigel thanked the elf before returning to the mirror. Armed with her wits after the first couple of sips, she said, "I'm ready. Tell me everything."

Archie set the mirror on some surface and moved back a bit so she could see them both. Hermione's hair had reached supernova levels of mass, and she had a scab on her lip from where she had nearly chewed it through. Rigel braced herself.

"You know I've been working on an experiment to test my theory of core replenishment," Hermione began.

Rigel nodded. "I didn't understand all of it in your letter."

"I hadn't really grounded it yet, but now I have," Hermione said breathlessly. "You see, I think everything wizards believe about their magic is a lie."

She blinked. "That's…something."

"I know how it sounds—there's no other explanation, though. Oh, I'm doing this all wrong." Hermione took a breath. "Sorry."

"The experiment," Archie prompted gently.

"Yes. I disproved the hypothesis that wizards create their own magic."

Rigel choked on her tea. "You what?"

"It's the most fundamental assumption to all the research, and I just thought—what if we're wrong? So I designed a ward that blocked the flow of ambient magic through the air." Hermione spoke very quickly, as though the explanation has been building inside of her like a river behind a dam. "It was a two-part experiment. I used several classmates with different affinities in both parts. First, I found an obscure spell that measures the density of magic by volume and used it to measure the ambient magic within a set of my magic-impermeable wards. Then, I introduced a subject who had cast several high-powered spells in quick succession, making their core fatigued. After allowing them sufficient time to recover their magical reserves, I measured the ambient magic within the wards again and—it decreased."

Hermione took a deep breath as Rigel opened and closed her mouth soundlessly for a few moments. "You…invented a set of perfectly impermeable wards for this experiment?" Most wards were designed to block active magic—shaped magic, not ambient wild magic. One may as well block the molecules of the air itself. But Hermione had done it. And that wasn't even the most incredible thing she'd said. "And you—wait, so you're saying wizards draw on the magic in the air when we replenish our own stores? That's…"

"I know, I know. But I reverse tested it, too!" Hermione said it forcefully, evidently aware of how completely earth-shattering her theory was. "Part two of the experiment involved placing a magic-fatigued individual inside a ward that had already been depleted of ambient magic. I wanted to see if it would take longer for them to recover without the help of the ambient magic, and—they didn't, though. Every one of the subjects remained core-fatigued until they left the ward. Do you see what that means? Not only do we tap into the wild magic around us whenever we replenish our magic, but we are dependent on it entirely, Rigel!"

The air left her lungs in a whoosh. "Hermione," she croaked. "That's…"

"I know."

"We know," Archie added, sounding a bit shell-shocked himself.

Rigel gulped the rest of her tea and marshaled her thoughts quickly. "We don't produce magic; we absorb it." She tested the words on her tongue, wonderingly. "How does that explain the way the inner core feeds the outer core?" she asked. "For that matter, why do we have affinities at all, instead of purely Neutral magic, if it's all wild magic?"

Hermione shook her head. "I don't know exactly, but I have to theorize that some mechanism in the structure of the inner core alters the magic as it is absorbed. There is energy being used in the process of replenishment—plenty of studies prove that food and rest are key to a fast recovery. But what if the energy we use goes to shaping the magic, adjusting it to match our own personal signatures as it is incorporated into our cores?"

Rigel nodded slowly. "That could be...Hermione, this is terrifying. Brilliant, but really, utterly terrifying, do you realize that?"

"Yes." A slightly-hysterical laugh escaped the girl. "I expect the idea that wizards are just sentient plants photosynthesizing will generate some controversy."

"Controversy? People will riot in the streets," she said faintly. "This turns on its head the very idea that magic belongs to wizards. Merlin, there are people that believe it comes from a wizard's very soul."

Archie grinned. "All along, our greatest arrogance was assuming we own this spectacular thing inside of us at all."

"Exactly!" Hermione burst out. "Magic isn't yours or mine. It belongs to the world."

Magic belongs to the world. Riddle's words in Hermione's mouth. Something fundamental about the universe had surely cracked in two.

"Then—" The implications were dizzying.

"Back to the Fade," Archie reminded Hermione.

"Oh! Yes, so then…babies don't produce their own magic either, don't you see? They absorb it. That's the mechanism that must be broken. Transmitting magic to their cores doesn't help, because they don't know what to do with it." Hermione's eyes were bright through the mirror. "Rigel, if we can isolate the exact way the core alters the wild magic to make it storable, we'll finally have a real cause for the Fade."

"Why the fading, though? Why do the babies waste away…?" Rigel murmured the question out loud, trying to connect all the dots.

"Their bodies are still throwing energy at the problem," Hermione guessed. "It's just not being used correctly. The mother's supply of magic is cut off, and by the time the baby needs to convert wild magic and can't, it's already dependent on magic to survive."

"Explain muggleborns, then, or halfbloods whose mother is non-magic," Rigel challenged.

Hermione grimaced. "I've been wondering about that too. I don't know yet."

Archie ventured a suggestion. "Do you think the initial donation of mother's magic during a magical pregnancy influences the way the infant learns to shape the magic it absorbs?"

"What do you mean?" Hermione demanded.

"Well, it might explain why certain affinities or traits can run in a family, aside from genealogy," Archie said.

"Genetics…" Hermione trailed off as her eyes lost focus. "Yes, maybe there's a faulty gene expression involved."

Rigel frowned. "I'm not really versed in genes, beyond the basic inherited traits theory."

"I'll look into that portion of it," Hermione said, waving a hand dismissively.

"Then I'll try to isolate the mechanism of conversion you're talking about," Rigel offered.

"That's going to be the hardest part," Hermione cautioned. "The core's inner workings are entirely mysterious, which is why no one has proved this theory before."

"I have a way of seeing into a person's core," Rigel said.

Archie made a noise of realization. "That's right! Your core-diving thing."

"Core-diving?" Hermione's eyebrows furrowed.

"It's a freaky unique thing only Rigel can do," Archie said helpfully.

"He's…not wrong." He's…

Hermione seemed skeptical, but said, "All right. I'll leave that part to you, then."

"What can I do?" Archie asked.

"Look into what is known about muggleborn magical development," Rigel suggested. "I think we're missing something there, but most of the literature I've seen treats muggleborns as non-entities until they turn up at school at eleven. Sorry," she added as Hermione winced.

"It's true. We're identified too late. If only there was some way of finding muggleborns at birth…" Hermione's expression was torn for a moment, but cleared with a sharp breath. "My next project, perhaps."

"After you cure the incurable Fade, you mean," Archie said, elbowing her with a grin.

Hermione cracked a smile in return. "One thing at a time, as my father likes to say."

"Or all things simultaneously, as my father likes to say."

"No one should take research advice from your father," Rigel said, shaking her head.

"He comes up with lots of ideas!"

"And never sees them through. Remus has to do all the technical work."

"Because Dad's an artist."

"I'm sure they all bring something to the team," Hermione said. She glanced between Archie and the mirror and added, "Just like us."

"Team Cure!" Archie crowed.

"Team Cure," Rigel repeated.

For the first time, she let herself believe it.

Even halfway through the brewing, she couldn't believe it. Her hands felt as light as soap bubbles, as though the ingredients were adding themselves, and her magic slept peacefully in her core, undisturbed. Her Head of House grew quieter and more still as the minutes dragged near to an hour and not a single. Thing. Happened.

Rigel finished the potion and set down her stirring rod. She turned the fire off with tingling fingers, her eyes searching for something in Snape's face. Approval. Respect. Both were there, but the third thing trapped the breath of relief in her chest. Awe.

"I think it will work," she said.

"I am certain it will." Snape shifted his gaze to the cauldron, where an innocuous alkaline brine glistened, and a crease like a smile folded into his jaw. "You…" He cleared his throat. "I have never seen anyone complete an original free brew without stifling unstable magic even once."

She smoothed a hand down the front of her pristine apron, soothing the glow of pride in her belly. "Perhaps we should end on that auspicious note, then."

Snape inclined his head with a wry tilt. "You've done enough tonight for the annuls of potioneering history."

Rigel bottled the potion and stoppered each dose carefully. She set the bottles on one of the spare work benches, and said, "I've no real use for a dozen vials of homesick-relief. Perhaps you could test them on first-year Hufflepuffs next term."

"A clinical trial would be valuable experience in your medicinal potions education," Snape agreed, sly amusement hidden in a deceptively dry tone.

He wouldn't really use them before the Ministry approved the brew for human consumption, but he also didn't refuse the doses. Knowing that she'd created something good enough for Master Snape to keep around sent another round of warmth through her stomach.

She carried the cauldron to the sink to scrub it clean, and Snape began meticulously re-shelving the leftover ingredients. They worked in companionable silence, until Snape asked, "What were you thinking, while you brewed?"

Rigel slowed the water and spoke over the tinny sound of it hitting the metal cauldron. "I wasn't thinking anything, really. It was as though—have you seen the Acromantula nests in the forest?"

Snape let out a bark of laughter. "You think yourself akin to a spider in its web?"

She scowled at him good-naturedly. "It was like that. My mind was suspended over everything in perfect understanding, but connected to dozens of avenues at once. I could see all the ways it could turn out, without really consciously playing through them."

Her professor considered that for a moment before asking, "Do you play chess?"

Rigel chuckled. "We're more of a checkers family."

"Even the werewolf?"

She frowned at his use of the descriptor, but admitted, "Uncle Remus did try to teach us. I know enough to draw out a game, but I find it frustratingly limited. In real life, the pieces are more flexible."

He raised an eyebrow as he closed the cupboard. "How so?"

Rigel gestured to the castle around them. "If Hogwarts was a piece, do you really think it would only move back and forth in the corner?"

Snape snorted. "Hogwarts would have an entirely invisible dimension in which only it could move."

"Exactly. And the king—he's artificially restrained in chess. In situations that are not battles, which is most situations in the modern world, the king has a much more expansive role."

"Who is the king? The Minister?"

She eyed him with disappointment. "Dumbledore, of course." She returned to rinsing the cauldron and bit out, "Riddle for black, I suppose. The Ministry…is the board they play on, if anything."

"What am I?" Snape asked, a dangerous edge to his voice.

"A knight." She flashed him a grin. "The Weasleys got that one right, sir."

He sneered. "And what are you?"

"I'm not on the board," she said quickly.

"Your denial is fathomless."

"But not unexpected."

He shook his head at that, but let the subject go. She set the cauldron upside down to dry and they wiped down the surfaces together.

"What will my next assignment be?" she asked as she pried the lid off the oil tin.

"What would you like it to be?"

Rigel grinned. "I want to dive deeper into dragon's blood as a signifying ingredient."

"Dangerous and unpredictable—your inner lion is showing."

"No ambition is realized without risk," she teased.

Snape took the oil rag from her fingers with a sniff. "Quoting Salazar won't get you out of everything."

"What about, 'nothing is lost for striving, striving at every turn and striving despite the odds'?"

"Have you swallowed a book of Slytherin sayings?"

"Draco keeps flashcards in his pockets."

Snape snorted. "He does not. How do you know about flashcards?"

"Aunt Lily swears by them. She keeps all her ideas pinned up on a board in the basement…" she trailed off as Snape's expression closed. After a moment's hesitation, she said, "Did Dumbledore mention what she's working on?"

He shook his head sharply. "We do not speak of such things."

"Well, she's invented runic expressions for describing the exact properties of Dark Magic." Rigel took out the amulet and held up the disk. He glanced at it briefly. "Then she created this amulet to detect and counter those specific signatures. I'm sorry if I'm overstepping, but no one else knows what you've done, so no one else can tell you this, sir. Because of Aunt Lily's work in experimental magic—work that you secured for her—the most dangerous Dark Arts are one step closer to being blunted. I'll say it for all the people who can't ever know: thank you."

Snape set the oiled cauldron down and stared hard at her. "That is quite enough."

"It won't ever be enough," she shot back. His eyes flared in warning and she subsided to a calmer tone. "Some things cannot be repaid in thanks alone."

"Some things are not done in anticipation of repayment."

She bowed her head in acknowledgement of that. "I'll pay it forward, then. What you've taught me…potions and all the rest. I'll pass it on one day."

Snape drew his composure around himself like a cape. "If you intend to publish a memoir, you'd best ensure I'm dead in my grave first."

Rigel huffed. "Skeeter will get to you before I do."

He narrowed his eyes. "That may be the most harrowing curse I've ever heard."

"One day, young Slytherins will be quoting me."

"If you think your past statements reflect wisdom, you must not remember any of them."

She affected an offended eyebrow-raise. "I am profound, Professor. Ask anyone."

He crossed his arms. "Shall I choose a few at random?" He put on a guileless tone that was so out of place she choked. "'But Professor, how does a doxy even make eggs if they have no—?'"

Rigel cleared her throat loudly. "No need to spoil the ending." She wrinkled her nose. "Only promise if I die in the next task that won't be on my headstone."

Snape stiffened. "Do not joke about such things. You are not invincible, Rigel."

She sobered. "I know that—I really do. I—" The wand in her pocket buzzed, and she checked the time with a grimace. "Damn. Sorry, sir. I promised Dray I would…" she groped for a moment before offering, "Play Exploding Snap tonight."

Her Head of House tapped his fingers on the counter. "Ah. I suppose that is where Draco, Miss Parkinson, and dozens of other students from all four Houses have been disappearing to on the seventh floor every week. An Exploding Snap league, is it?"

Rigel swallowed soundlessly and nodded, belatedly reinforcing her Occlumency shields.

"How unexpected," he drawled. "I thought for certain it was an underground dueling club."

She forced a laugh, the words plausible deniability pulsing in her brain. "That would be so sneaky and irresponsible, professor. Definitely not something Pansy would be involved in."

"Saying nothing of the others."

"Well…" She closed her mouth.

After a beat of silence, Snape rolled his eyes. "Go make your Exploding Snap appointment, Rigel."

She backed slowly out of the room, her feet pushing across the cushioned floor in soft bounces. "Great. I will, sir." She hung up her protection gear and reclaimed her bag at the door. "About the next assignment…"

"I will speak to Albus about it and we will revisit your ideas after the last task."

"After the task, great. See you later, Professor."

"Mind you don't exhaust yourself with that card game."

She fled before he could make any further insinuations, wondering how she ought to break it to Draco that Snape had known about their illegal dueling club all along.

Draco had the club warming up when she slipped into the Room of Requirement. Rigel jogged over to where Pansy was demonstrating a truly gamine stretching position and took a spot between her friend and a blushing Ravenclaw who was very pointedly not-looking.

"That stretch should come with a warning label," Rigel said, grinning.

"The stretch is the warning label," Pansy retorted, sending the flustered Ravenclaw a wink. She flicked her eyes over Rigel's brewing robes and trusty boots. "You're going to exercise in that?"

Rigel shrugged. "It's already dirty."

Pansy raised an eyebrow. "You don't think we can give you a real challenge."

She winced. "Don't put words in my mouth."

"You're right, though." Pansy bent at the waist and looked up at her with her cheek pressed to her ankle. "You've outgrown this club. Be honest; do you come just to support Draco?"

"Maybe I come for your stretching."

Pansy flipped her hair in Rigel's general direction. "I've reconciled my inability to sway you, Rye. It helps that everyone else has failed, too."

"Thanks?" Rigel shook her head.

"Stretch, Rigel!" Draco called from his place in the center of the room. "Can't have our champion pulling a muscle two days before the last task."

Rigel lifted a hand in mock-salute. "Aye-aye, mon Capitaine."

When everyone was limbered to Draco's satisfaction, he ran the advanced students through a new set of footwork and set up a line of dummies for the younger students to practice Flipendo.

It was achingly normal. Contrary to Pansy's prediction, Rigel worked up a decent sweat getting down the new patterns, and she gratefully accepted a cup of water from the ringleader himself when the session wrapped up for the evening.

"I can't believe you wore your potions getup to practice," Draco said, giving her the same once-over that Pansy had.

"I came straight from the lab," Rigel said between gulps. She wiped her mouth and remembered her conversation with Snape. "And this is in no way my fault, but Snape definitely knows about the—"

"Seriously, Rigel? You can't keep one secret from the man?"

She shook her head quickly. "It wasn't me, Dray. I told him I had to go play Exploding Snap and he said 'oh, I thought you had an illegal club to get to' or something."

"Exploding Snap? That was the best you could come up with?"

"I lost track of time, all right? My alarm went off right in the middle of—"

"Boys, what are we arguing about?" Pansy took the cup from Rigel's hand to refill it from a Room-provided pitcher.

"Rigel told Snape about the club—"

"Draco thinks I can't keep a secret—"

Pansy dumped the water on Rigel's head. While she spluttered and wiped at her eyes, Pansy calmly refilled the glass and tossed it in Draco's face. "You're both ridiculous. Snape is smart enough to have figured it out himself, Draco." As Rigel let out a triumphant sound, Pansy spoke over her. "And Rigel is conspicuous enough in Snape's field of view to have led him straight here."

She set the pitcher down on its table and planted her hands on her hips. "Regardless, you're both wrong. I told Snape." Rigel and Draco gaped at her. She sighed. "Honestly. You think it's a coincidence that all the members' detentions have been conveniently deconflicted? That none of the other teachers have grown suspicious? We needed an ally on staff."

"Snape expressly forbid me from running this club," Draco hissed.

"Yes, Draco. Snape openly and expressly told you not to have a club." Pansy's face clearly said 'do you see it yet?'

Draco opened his mouth, shut it again, and crossed his arms defensively. "Uncle Sev is very convincing."

Rigel patted him on the back. In truth, Draco had no idea how many masks his godfather wore. "Just be glad to have such a powerful piece on our side."

"Uncle Sev's not a piece—he's a player."

"I'm going to delete that sentence from my memory," Fred declared loudly from over Draco's shoulder.

Draco spun around. "That isn't what I meant—"

"Too late. Deleted. Thanks for the subconscious trauma, Captain."

"What are you eavesdropping for anyway?"

George appeared on Draco's other side and leaned a heavy arm on the boy's shoulder before he could escape. "So glad you asked. We were thinking this might be the last chance to catch Rigel before the big to-do."

"Consider me caught," Rigel said, intrigued. "Have you another firework display for me to show off?"

"Firstly, yes." George pressed a dangerously innocuous disk into her palm with a grin that invited her to join him in epic anticipation.

"And speaking of lighting one off, what say we take a trip down to the kitchens for a little pre-accomplishment celebration?" Fred waggled his eyebrows at each of them in turn.

Pansy smiled. "Isn't it bad luck to celebrate before winning?"

"Bad taste, maybe, but luck? Who needs it?" George slung an arm around Rigel's shoulder and turned his best puppy-eyed pout on Pansy. "Doesn't Rigel deserve to unwind a bit?"

"We've noticed a few new grey hairs," Fred added, plucking one from her head without so much as a by-your-leave. He examined the perfectly black hair for a moment before letting it fall, pretending not to notice Rigel wandlessly vanishing it as it hit the floor. "As your friends and advisors, we're concerned for your health."

"And your sanity."

"And your fun-ness, which overall seems much diminished of late."

"Will it appease your disquiet if I go and have cake in the kitchens with you?" Rigel asked on a laugh.

"It's a good start," George said seriously.

Rigel gestured for them to lead the way.

Fred cupped his hand over his mouth and shouted to the entire room, "AFTER PARTY IN THE KITCHENS!"

A general cheer went up, and before Rigel could wonder if she'd let the twins pull her farther from shore than was wise, she was caught in the riptide of students marching gayly down to the basement. If any professors had come across the mixed group of sweaty teens, they'd have strained credulity with any story they could have fabricated.

They burst through the portrait hole amidst numerous exclamations from those in their party who had never traversed the Elves' territory.

Binny met them with crossed arms and a stern expression as her fellows froze in the midst of polishing the dinnerware. "You is bringing the whole school tonight, Mr. and Mr. Weasleys?"

Fred looked over his shoulder in exaggerated surprise while George said, "Us? They're not here with us."

"They is spontaneously finding their way here?" Binny squinted up at them.

Fred snapped his fingers. "By George, I think we were followed!"

"By Fred, I'm certain we were."

Rigel pushed her way to the front of the crowd. "Binny, good evening. Our apologies for the intrusion."

Binny dipped a curtsey. "Mr. Black, you is always welcome." The Elf ignored the twins miming tears as they held one another. "Is you bringing Mr. Draco?"

"It's his illegal club," Ron called from the back.

Binny clapped her hands and two Elves jumped up from the pile of silver. "Tarts. Many and quickly."

Rigel shot her friend a grin as his ears turned pink. "This is why we love you, Binny."

"Binny is loving all of Hogwarts' students," the Elf said solemnly. She leaned close enough for her champagne cork necklace to brush Rigel's knee and added, "But Mr. Black is being extra special."

"She used to say we were special," George mourned.

"Guard your heart, Rigel—that she-Elf is fickle as a boggart," Fred lamented.

"That she hasn't murdered you both in your beds speaks volumes to her steadiness and loyalty," Ron said flatly.

Binny flicked her fingers and one of the long tables cleared itself. At a twitch of her left ear, a sumptuous tablecloth rolled a path from end to end, and with a twirl of her pinky, flagons of pumpkin juice crowded the center. The round of applause that burst from the group set Binny to curtseying again. "Mind you is in bed before curfew," she cautioned.

"Thank you, Binny," Rigel said as her schoolmates crowded the table with empty goblets. The Elves who had jumped-to at Binny's command were already ferrying piles of Raspberry tarts to the table, and the flurry of new activity in the kitchen promised a plethora of treats to follow.

The Elves pretended not to notice when Fred and George spiked one of the flagons, and Rigel pretended not to notice when Draco poured himself a generous helping. She took a sausage-stuffed roll and held her hand over the top of her goblet when George went to top her plain juice off with something stronger.

"It's a celebration, Rigel," he wheedled.

"I'll celebrate properly when it's over," she promised.

"That's the difference between our Houses," George said with a grin. "We celebrate first, because a Gryffindor does not assume he's going to see the end of the fight."

Rigel considered her goblet seriously. Hadn't she said something similar to her Head of House? Perhaps it was foolish to put off gaiety until a time of perfect, uncomplicated peace. With the rate at which she picked up problems, there was a good chance that day would never come.

George grimaced. "It was only a joke, Rigel. I know you'll make it through all—"

"One cup." She took her hand away from the rim and let him fill it to the brim.

George's smile was back full-blast. "To heroes!" He clinked their cups together soundly.

"To friends." She tossed back a large gulp before it could slosh too much over her hand.

"To the Hogwarts Champion!" Someone leaned over from behind her and tapped their cup to hers, and she drank politely.

"To Rigel's victory!" That call came from Ron, but at the answering round of cheers, she lifted her own glass again.

If only that were the end of it.

"To Rigel's strength!"

"To Rigel's cunning!"

"To his loyalty!"

"No—to his erudite-hic-ness!"

Draco laughed lowly as he slid into a seat beside her. "To Rigel's patience." He clinked their cups and Rigel took a very small sip while staring at him over the top of the rim. "Salazar, if you could feel the enmity coming off you right now."

"To Rigel's iron stomach!" Fred set the group off again, and Rigel slammed her empty goblet down on the table.

"Thank you, that's quite enough!" The sweet pumpkin juice became cloying in combination with whatever the twins had used to supplement it, and she was not keen to put Fred's toast to the test.

"No such thing." Aldon swiped another pitcher from George and refilled her goblet. "Can't have an empty glass in front of our guest of honor."

Rigel protested, "I can't make myself sick two days before the last task."

Her argument failed to impress him. "The greatest young Potions brewer this school has ever seen can surely make himself a draught in the morning."

She could, at that. Still, there was something unprincipled about it, and she said so.

George shook his head. "If I've learned anything from Percy over the years, it's that it isn't fun to be the most principled person in the room."

"Nor is it wise to be the least," she retorted.

George looked to where his brother was climbing on the end of the table with his tie wrapped around his head. "No danger of that."

Aldon reached over to clink their cups. "Go on, Rigel. You've been on edge for days."

She frowned. "I have not."

"You snarled at a first-year yesterday," Draco reminded her.

Rigel shot him a betrayed look. "I just corrected his homework."

"You said 'the notion that dragon liver should ever be mixed with undiluted bulbotuber puss is so misguided as to border on sociopathic.'"

She winced. "Which one was that again?" She had no recollection of using those exact words, but she should probably apologize.

"Carrow, but he forgave you after getting an E on the assignment," Pansy said from Draco's other side.

She sighed into her cup, but George clapped her smartly on the back. "No moping—it's a party, Rigel. Or don't you have those in Slytherin?"

"Rigel doesn't come to the parties," Draco said. His serious tone was somewhat blunted by the way his eyes blinked slow and heavy.

"Have you ever even been sloshed, then?"

She shook her head slowly, but stopped when she remembered. "A little, when I was practicing for the fifth task. I didn't like it."

"Not surprising, if it was a form of survival training." Aldon topped her glass off, then Draco's, then his own. "To better reasons for drinking."

"To never going back in time and re-doing the fifth task," she murmured.

"Only you would have to specifically rule that out." Draco sniggered.

Edmund physically nudged Aldon sideways on the bench and claimed the resulting space. "Corrupting the fourth-years, Al?"

"For all you know, I'm saving their immortal souls."

"Saving it from what?" Draco put a hand over his stomach, a bit protectively.

"Witches." Aldon smirked at Pansy, who rolled her eyes.

At Draco's confused look, Pansy shook her head. "It's a muggle thing. Aldon thinks he's being funny."

"So what else is new?" Draco yawned into his goblet. "Edmund, when's the stag party? You know it's my birthday in June, right?"

"Are you asking because you want to combine the two or deconflict them?" Aldon's smile had points. "Only I don't recall getting an invitation to your birthday party, Draco."

The blond boy wrinkled his nose. "My parents only let me invite my year-mates."

"But anyone of age can come to the garden party," Pansy pointed out.

Draco nodded enthusiastically. "Tha's right. You should both come this year."

"What's the average age at the Malfoy Summer Garden Party? Over one hundred?" Aldon grinned into his palm. "No thanks, mate."

"Oh. Yeah, true." Draco was still nodding, but much slower. "When's the stag party, then?"

Edmund slid his heavy gaze to Aldon. "I'm afraid Al's in charge of that."

Aldon leaned across the table on his hand, a smirk threatening to colonize his ear. "Are you sure you're up to it?"

Draco attempted to draw himself upright, but was interrupted by a yawn. "A Malfoy is up to anything."

"I don't know…it won't exactly be tailored to the fifteen-and-under crowd."

"I'm sure you know I'm highly mature for my age."

"Exceedingly so," Rigel added dryly.

"Are you recommending him, Rigel? I might consider it then." Aldon had pure mischief in his eyes as Draco looked blearily between the two of them.

Rigel eyed her friend's unfocused gaze. "He does hold his drink well, doesn't he?"

Draco inclined his head in thanks as Pansy smothered a sigh from his other side.

"So far—but the night is even younger than you lot." Aldon filled Draco's cup again and Rigel began to silently calculate the doses of Pain Relief and Sobering Draught that would be most effective for someone of Draco's size and metabolic class.

She stopped when the accelerating half-life co-efficient started to waltz. Her head felt as though Dom had filled the mindscape with water again and set her thoughts to swimming.

"Rigel?"

Someone poked her in the side, and she jerked her gaze up from the table. "Yes, George?"

"You zoned out there for a spell. All right?"

She nodded. Then she considered the question and shook her head. "I don't want anymore."

George downed the rest of her cup without hesitating. "Then no more shall you have." With a grin, he added, "You look more relaxed, anyway, which was the entire point."

Rigel stiffened her spine with effort, mildly alarmed by that pronouncement. Relaxation was something to which she could never completely surrender.

George laughed. "Only you would see relaxation as the enemy."

She blinked. Did I say that out loud?

"Yes, you did." George shook his head with a smile tugging on his lips. "That's what happens when you toast a dozen times in a row—it all catches up to you at once."

"What did you put in the pumpkin juice?" she asked, realizing that question was overdue.

"Not butterbeer," he said.

"Fairy wine?" she guessed hopefully.

"Something stronger," the redhead admitted. "We've been watching the young ones, though—no one's had too much."

"I have."

"You've had exactly as much as you needed. All of your friends have noticed you spinning yourself into orbit this week. Come back down to earth for a night and remember that you're not taking on the whole world by yourself."

She glanced around the table at the others. Aldon and Edmund nodded in unqualified agreement, Pansy gave her a guilty grimace, and Draco had his head pillowed on his arms. He rolled onto one ear to murmur, "You haven't been sleeping much."

Rigel rubbed her temple. "I have a lot on my mind."

"The maze." Edmund's rumbling voice gave weight to the phrase.

She dropped her hand to her lap and clenched it into a fist. "Yes." She'd spent too many hours to count staring up at the dark ceiling, wondering what awaited her in the hedges.

"You think it'll be bad?" George asked quietly.

She let out a slightly-hysterical laugh. "I keep wondering that. Will it somehow be worse than everything that came before? Or will it be…anticlimactic?"

"You're thinking 'bout politics, too," Draco grumbled into the table.

Of course she was. The dire possibilities shouted at her every time she closed her eyes. Would the legislation go through without Riddle's direct involvement after she won? Would the rights of halfbloods and muggleborns alike flicker and die in a gust of pureblood pride? Would the country explode into civil war to keep it from happening? Would anyone care at all?

"What if it's all for nothing?" she whispered.

"You done more'n anyone." Draco's mouth stretched into a yawn that he hid in his own elbow.

"He's right." Aldon toasted her with his cup. "Even if your plan doesn't work in the near term, you've hamstrung them for decades."

Edmund frowned at his friend. "What plan is this?"

Rigel wrinkled her nose. "It's a great, complicated thing."

"A conspiracy," Draco agreed.

"You conspirators should be careful," Pansy said sharply.

"Being careful is all I ever do," Rigel said mournfully.

"No one watching from the outside would guess," George said wryly. He, too, looked curious, but after Pansy's warning, neither he nor Edmund pressed them.

"It's all inside," Rigel put a hand to her chest and tugged at her robes in frustration. "Some days I'm so sick of it. Most days…I'm just really tired."

"'m tired too," Draco offered.

"You shouldn't be so hard on yourself," Pansy said over Draco's slumped form. "No one is asking more of you."

"They should." Rigel stared at Pansy. A sudden conviction reached into her throat and choked the words that came next. "You should, Pan; I'm a big fraud, really."

"A fraud doesn't slay a basilisk or cure a deadly illness," Aldon observed.

"'twasn't deadly," Draco muttered.

"A fraud doesn't earn the trust and loyalty of so many," Edmund added evenly.

"Riddle did." The words came hoarsely as she let the comparison rankle. "I don't deserve my friends."

"It's not about deserving." George's tone brooked no further argument.

"We're your friends forever, Rigel, whether you deserve it or not," Pansy said fiercely.

"No matter what you do," Aldon agreed.

Edmund slid his best friend a dry look. "No matter how annoying you are."

Rigel's mouth hitched for their sake. "Thanks." They didn't know what they promised, but it didn't hurt to hear it.

Fred sprawled into George's lap without warning, a laugh still on his lips. He looked about the group and fixed Rigel with an exasperated stare. "Mate, I hate to tell you, but the cloud of doom and gloom that's been hovering over your head all year appears to be procreating."

George dumped Fred onto the table, upsetting every glass in his path. "Bite your tongue! Moroseness never met a more menacing match than me!"

Draco startled upright as juice doused his fair strands and Pansy gasped in displeasure as he shook the drops into her face. Aldon leaned back on the bench and refilled his upturned cup from the river dripping off the edge of the table. He caught Rigel's eye and shrugged. "Ce la vie, Rigel. Drink while there's drink. Make merry while you've friends to be merry with. Time enough for melancholy later, when you're alone."

She watched Fred bowl himself down the length of the table to the accompaniment of general mayhem and felt her spirits lift a little. Time enough, indeed.

Music swanned across the lawn on the wings of the stadium's amplification spells. Descending from the castle with Draco and Pansy, Rigel saw a river of colored tents clustered about the main entrance to the pitch. The painted flags and souvenir stalls gave her a strong sense of déjà vu; it was like a very small World Cup, if most of the attendees had been sober. And children.

Her friends flitted to the stalls, fingering sparkling commodities with the energy of those who did not have an invisible weight on their shoulders. Pansy held up a scarf with Rigel's image patterned in thread and grinned mischievously. "Shall I pick up a few, for posterity's sake?"

"Get Dray one for his birthday."

Draco wrinkled his nose. "I'd rather have the animated hat. Look, it even speaks Parseltongue."

Rigel pressed her lips together at the incomprehensible spitting noises emanating from the headwear in question. With a straight face, she said, "You should hear what it's saying about your mother."

Draco dropped it in horrified surprise. "That's not funny."

Pansy's muffled laughter disagreed. The two moved on to a stand selling omnioculars, and didn't notice immediately when Rigel drifted away. She caught a familiar face in her periphery and stole closer for a better look.

Leo moved amidst a group of gayly dressed players, a pair of striped pantaloons accentuating his long legs as he marched with exaggerated aplomb. Bells on his shoes chimed sharply with every step, but it was his hands that drew the eye—they juggled half a dozen colored balls with the easy grace of old habit, weaving through the air like an artist with an invisible brush.

She had to marvel at how well he fit. Leo was a chameleon, blending effortlessly in any surroundings. He engaged the crowd with an easy grin, charming smiles and even blushes from the Hogwarts students. Cora, resplendent in silver sequins, tossed one of her juggling knives toward Leo. He ducked, bells jangling as he shook with exaggerated fear. Another performer caught the knife as it sailed over Leo's head, and the crowd laughed as he shook a finger admonishingly at the precocious child.

Rigel turned away before he spotted her. As nice as it was to see her friend, she wasn't prepared to speak to him as Archie. If there was one deception she could yet avoid, surely it was that one.

He watched the boy slip off without a word from the corner of his eye. Harry's cousin presented a curious puzzle. A pampered pureblood with a split personality who'd done much better than anyone expected in the high-profile tournament. The Black scion came off obliviously chipper at first acquaintance, but scratch the façade and something surprisingly savvy lurked beneath. He didn't look so cheerful today, but Leo wouldn't either, were he in the boy's spot.

A girl with long, raven hair tossed a Galleon as he winked at her—an entire Galleon, and wasn't it a bit sickening how much disposable income these children seemed to have? Cora goggled at the golden coin before her knives demanded her attention once more. The distraction cost her, and she stuck out a foot to hastily bounce the hilt of a knife back up into the air at the last moment. Several of the students whooped, and Cora smiled like she hadn't a care in the world. Like a Galleon wouldn't feed her for two months.

Arcturus had rejoined his friends. Leo followed the boy's ambling progress toward the stadium without seeming to. He hoped for Harry's sake the boy made it through the night all right. The task was only half of it—big tourney like this, sparkling in the public's imagination, would be an irresistible target to the likes of those wreaking havoc across the country of late. Judging by the number of plainclothes Aurors skulking about, he wasn't the only one who expected the ugly side of humanity to rear its head.

Leo tipped his cap to the audience as he swapped out with another performer. Jacques caught his eye and nodded. If there was trouble like the Cup, he and his troupe would help sort it. This time, they wouldn't have an entire brigade of players out their worldly possessions. Leo trailed Arcturus and his friends from a subtle distance. At the least, he would see the boy got home to his cousin. For her sake.

"Sport, over here!"

"Is he talking to you?" Draco murmured, a slightly disbelieving sneer on his mouth.

Rigel waved to Sirius, who grinned back from his spot between Lily and Remus. "That's my dad you're mocking."

"Not mocking," Draco protested. "Just constantly questioning the sanity of."

"I'm not sure that made grammatical sense," Pansy muttered through the side of her polite smile.

Rigel shook her head with a laugh. "No need to strain your manners. I'll see you both after."

Pansy took her in a brief hug. "Be careful."

Draco gave her a serious nod. "Do your best—we'll be watching."

"I daren't let you down," she said, sweeping them a playful bow. "Until we meet again."

"Good luck!" Pansy called after her. They locked eyes until Draco tugged the blonde girl toward the stands.

Rigel jogged over to her waiting family. "You all came, huh?"

Sirius crushed her in a hug that was slightly too desperate to be a mere greeting. "Course we did. How do you feel? Ready?"

She nodded, trying to project confidence and ease into her face. She would never be as convincing as Archie, but they would excuse any slips as nerves.

Sirius stepped back and clenched his fists as though to stop himself reaching for her again. "Last one," he said bracingly.

"You're going to be great," Remus said. "Just remember the basics."

"I've been practicing like mad," she said, laughing embarrassedly. "I hope it's enough."

Lily reached out to touch the cord around her neck. "You only have to come out alive, Archie."

She nodded reassuringly, but inside, her heart clenched. If only it were that easy. Surviving wasn't enough, though. She had to win.

"Rigel."

She turned. Professor Snape stood at an awkward distance, his hands in his robe pockets. He didn't acknowledge her family members, and simply said, "It's time."

She smiled apologetically at the other adults. "Looks like I'm running late, as usual. Sorry to run off—"

Sirius just hugged her again, resting a heavy hand on her head. "Good luck, son."

She gulped back a sudden sting in her eyes and closed them in a smile to hide the moisture. "Thanks, Dad."

Rigel stepped back and waved more confidently than she felt. Snape set a steady pace and she fell into sync with him automatically. As they stepped through the entrance, the air caught a bit in her chest. The pitch was gone. Only the maze remained.

"It's monstrous," she said.

"It's nothing but an overgrown garden," Snape said firmly. He gestured to the end of the stadium, where a square stage perched proudly on elegant legs—too elegant to be functional, she thought with a snort. How many stabilizing runes had that required? "That is your aim. The cup in the center of the maze is a portkey to the winner's podium. All of this—" he gestured dismissively to the great hedge before them "—is distraction. Keep focused on your goal, and I believe nothing can stop you."

Rigel eyed the roman-style podium fixed to the gazelle-like stage with a grimace. "It's a literal pedestal."

"Too late to shy from the lime light now," Snape said, clearly amused at her expense.

"There are hats out there with my face on them," she revealed, letting all the disquiet she felt drip into her voice.

Snape laughed before he caught himself. He led her to a narrow gap in the hedge. The other champions waited in the shadow of the great maze, both lost in their own thoughts. Snape placed a hand on her shoulder briefly and cleared his throat. "Make us proud," he said quietly.

Rigel nodded once, too overcome with emotion to offer more, and Snape left her. She looked around at Owens and Fleur, but neither met her gaze for long. The maze inexorably drew their attention, and she understood why. It bled magic like something radioactive. Waves of the power that went into its creation lapped at her senses, almost numbing in their intensity. Rigel didn't realize she was in its thrall until Bagman was at her shoulder.

"Ready, Champions?"

She spun around, shaking her head sharply. The stands were full, roaring noise all around her, and Bagman and Crouch waited like a pair of boatmen on the river Styx. Crouch thrust a headband toward her, and she put it on automatically, hardly noticing the weight of it anymore.

"I'm sure you're all chomping at the bit," Bagman said, clapping his hands together as though he, too, were anxious to get into the maze. "A bit of admin first, though."

Owens muttered something impolite under his breath, and Bagman pretended not to hear him.

"As you know, the champion with the highest running score will enter the maze first—that's you, Mr. Black. Next will be Mr. Owens after five minutes have passed, with Ms. Delacour entering last at the ten-minute mark." Bagman gave Fleur a patronizing smile. "I'm sure that will be plenty of time, darling, don't you worry. The criteria for winning—and this is very important, Mr. Owens, so please pay attention—well, all you have to do is touch the Triwizard Cup at the center of the maze. It will transport you instantly to the stage below the judges box, and there you will be crowned the True Triwizard Champion. You'll be expected to give a winner's speech at the podium, of course, so think of what you want to say while you're wandering around in our little puzzle. Any questions?"

"Are we allowed to hinder one another?" Predictably, it was Owens who voiced the crass query.

Bagman raised his eyebrows. "Well, there's no rule against it."

Crouch cut in sharply. "Whatever happens in there, just remember you have to live with it out here, young man."

Owens shrugged. Fleur glared at him and Rigel vowed to watch her back.

"Well, that's all we have for you. Good luck! Mr. Black, please take your starting position."

She moved to the mouth of the maze and stared into the darkness. Some cruel soul had fed it a twisting mist that denied the eye more than a dozen feet of visibility. The magic of the maze throbbed at her, and something inside her throbbed back in sympathy. It was all down to one last task.

She wasn't consciously aware of the cannon that signaled the start, but her feet moved on their own, and the maze swallowed her whole.

She watched her nephew enter the maze with a fearless stride, more worried for Sirius than for him. Their friend had been on edge all year, half-convinced that Archie's every goodbye would be his last. He clutched the edge of the balcony tight enough to test the strengthening charms, and Lily breathed a small sigh of relief when James pushed his way into the family box. James was better at calming Sirius than she or Remus.

"Sorry, had to placate the Minister," James said, dropping a warm kiss onto her cheek. "Has he gone in?"

"Just now," Remus said quietly. When James glanced over, he nodded meaningfully toward Sirius, who was staring intently down at the impenetrable hedge maze.

James followed his gaze and made a noise of understanding. "The mist will turn transparent once all the champions are in the maze," he revealed. "That way no one can pass information to them beforehand."

As he said it, the canon sounded a third time and the Beauxbatons champion darted into the maze. The great mirrors, suspended above the hedge in a gaudy sort of chandelier, cleared at once to reveal what each champion saw. Simultaneously, the mist that filled the maze shimmered into translucency.

Remus looked between the maze itself and the mirrors above it. "The mist is only transparent from above," he mused. "They'll be virtually blind in there."

The balcony rail grimaced under Sirius' hands.

"Look, there's Archie," James said, pointing left to a small figure near the beginning of the maze. "Not got much sense of direction, has he?"

"Gets that from his mum," Sirius murmured, his mouth quirking.

His grip relaxed a tad, and Lily sent James a grateful smile. He nodded slightly, soft understanding in his beautiful eyes. They would all be relieved when this tournament was over. Why Archie had insisted on participating, they still didn't fully understand. It was his right…but. If he could see what it was doing to Sirius…

"Is that a hippogriff?" Remus asked, pointing to a winged creature stalking the far-right side of the maze.

"And so many spells," Lily said, eyeing the tell-tale shimmer hanging in the air at several crucial junctures.

"Wizards, too," Sirius said. "Friends of yours, James?"

James winced. "The request came in, and I couldn't very well say no. I also considered the alternative—better trained, responsible Aurors than some duelist-for-hire or dangerous creature—"

"You mean like that Acromantula?" Sirius jutted his chin toward the scuttling spider almost as tall as the hedge itself and drawled, "Glad we avoided that."

James muttered a curse under his breath. "I talked them out of more dragons, at least."

"Those aren't all Aurors," Remus pointed out. He set a pair of omnioculars to his eyes and peered toward a small figure in shining armor.

Sirius swiped them and let out a grunt of surprise. "It's that Athenian champion. Antipathy or something."

"Antiope," Remus corrected, taking the glasses back. "Did they bring back all the previous champions?"

"Just the three who excelled in combat," James confirmed. "Antiope and Krum, and—"

"Oi, some kind of animal is going for Archie!" Sirius grabbed for the omnioculars and Remus surrendered them with a sigh of annoyance.

"That's not an animal, Sirius, it's an—"

"Animagus." Sirius hissed as the hyena sprang for Archie's shoulder.

"That'll be the third ex-champion," James agreed.

"What's happening?" Remus asked. When Sirius didn't answer, utterly engrossed in watching his son's progress, he nudged him with an elbow. "I asked if you wanted your own pair, you—"

"Here, Remus." Lily passed him her pair of omnioculars. "You narrate it for us."

Remus adjusted the settings to his preference and put them to his face. "He's doing well—he's fast."

"Archie or the hyena?" Lily asked, leaning forward to see Archie's mirror a bit better. It was difficult to get a sense of how his confrontation was going, as the view bobbed and swayed with Archie's every move.

"Both," Remus said. Admiration colored his tone. "Archie's got serious reflexes. He's dodging every bite and—whoops, caught a scratch in the elbow I think." Sirius drew in a sharp breath, glued to his omnioculars, and Remus hurriedly added, "Nothing serious, though. He's on the offensive, now. Good, Archie. He got the other boy with a stinging jinx to the nose. He's weaving again, did you know he could move so quick, Sirius? Now he's thrown the animagus into the side of the hedge and—yes, he's got him pinned. Good use of Incarcerous."

Sirius let the omnioculars fall with a long breath of relief. He dabbed at a bead of sweat on his neck, and James jumped in to distract him. "Antiope's found the Delacour girl."

At the sound of the French champion's name, a pair of stunningly beautiful heads turned to regard James with affront. Her oblivious husband kept talking, even as Lily pressed a hand to his arm in warning.

"I heard she really trounced the poor girl in the semi-finals."

A woman who could only be Delacour's mother hissed and a younger silver-haired girl made a tiny claw with her fingers. James froze, his instinct for danger finally alerting him to the very annoyed part-Veela on the other side of the families' box.

"It's a different story this time," Remus said, omnioculars fixed on the dueling witches. "Delacour must have learned a lot from their last match—look at her pivot!"

The hair on the back of James' neck settled as Delacour's family reined in the strength of their glares. As Remus' commentary turned complimentary, they returned their attention to the task.

"Antiope is not letting up; I think there's some bad blood there."

"Probably thinks she should have won the halfblood spot," James guessed.

"Owens has run into trouble, too," Lily pointed out. The American champion had chosen the middle-most path, but the Durmstrang boy was waiting for him. "I hear Krum is quite the duelist."

"Owens beat him last time," Remus said. "He can do it again."

"That's the boy that took Harry's friend, Hermione, to the ball, isn't it?" Lily and Remus turned to stare at James. He held up his hands. "What? I remember things."

"It is," Remus confirmed, turning his omnioculars toward the pair of boys. "Bad blood there, too—Owens was particularly harsh on Hermione in the semi-finals, according to the accounts I've read."

"So their past behavior plays a part tonight," James mused.

"What about Archie?" Sirius asked suddenly. "Does he have any enemies in there?"

Remus shook his head. "By all accounts, he's very well liked, despite having won nearly every task."

Sirius grinned. "'Course he is. Archie's a good kid."

James groaned through his teeth. "Oh no. Not that way, Arch."

Sirius whirled back around. "What is it?"

"Dawlish."

Lily squinted and could just make out the prowling form of James' most trusted lieutenant, lying in wait around the next corner Archie would round.

"He won't go full out against a kid," James muttered. She didn't know if he was trying to convince Sirius or himself.

Sirius was clenching the railing again, any equanimity he might have gained in the last few minutes erased. "If he hurts Archie—"

"He's just doing his job, Sirius. He won't take it too far."

Lily didn't think Sirius even heard the words. Every fiber of his being was tuned toward the pitch, where his son crept closer to the next surprise.

She hadn't realized how dependent she'd become on her sensing ability. In the maze, everything was magic. Unlike the comforting ambient magic of the castle, or the neutral backdrop of light and dark creatures of the forest, the maze was a thick, cloying presence. It was barely-tamed, semi-sentient magic that had been given one central, life-like directive: growth. Awash in its power, she was snow-blind.

At a crossroads, she paused. There were no landmarks in the maze—the mists blotted out the setting sun and every path looked the same. Which way to go? "Point me." The wand spun in her hand endlessly, as confused by all the ambient magic as she was. With a sigh, she went left again.

Rigel had no idea how long she'd been in the maze. She'd come across Tahiil in his animagus form almost immediately. The scratch on her arm stung as she jogged, and she felt a little better about spraining his ankle to slow him down. It wasn't easy to tie him up without hurting him, and she was in a race.

She did think she'd traveled farther than the length of a Quidditch pitch. Some kind of devilishly tricky expansion charms were at work. Even the sound of her own footsteps was muffled by the oppressive mist. As she rounded the next corner, instinct more than insight had her dropping into a slide to avoid the hex that came at chin-height.

Rigel came out of the roll in a defensive crouch and deflected two more spells before she even realized who she was facing. "Professor?"

"Not tonight." Dawlish darted into her comfort zone and she scarcely avoided an elbow to the nose.

She countered with a leg sweep and regained space to use her wand in a quick double-stunner. Dawlish parried them easily, even seemed to be enjoying himself. She had read the Auror handbook front to back, knew all the moves he was supposed to make, but Dawlish's style had evolved beyond the basic defensive postures taught at the Auror Academy. He was aggressively straightforward, but so fast that the directness was not much of a disadvantage.

Rigel sped up her own movements to match his pace, then pushed him a little further, speeding and slowing her spells at random, knowing she only needed that one moment of miscalculation to get under his guard. Dawlish had a good eye for spell speed, though, and he countered every one of her varied spells despite their unpredictability.

"You've been holding back in class," he accused her. She could take some consolation in the way he panted the words.

"I've heard this theory before." She took the duel closer in, betting that she could out-spar him hand to hand if their wands were out of play. He frustrated her at every turn, somehow maintaining exactly the distance he needed even with hedges hemming them in on either side.

When a mad sort of inspiration hit her, she didn't hesitate. Rigel cast a mirrored shield—not around herself, but around Dawlish. She held the magic around him, her wand arm quivering with the strain of it. He barely parried his own rebounded stunner. The Auror stared at her, and she at him through the fractal shield between them. "We're at an impasse," he said, gesturing to the shield. "I can't cast through it, and you can't drop it to cast at me."

She smiled, and brought her left hand up, palm out. The overpowered Banishing charm shoved him, shield and all, through the thick hedge at bruising speed. He lay winded in the next aisle, gazing wide-eyed at her through the hole in the hedge.

"That was for hexing Draco so many times," she called.

He wheezed out a dry laugh. "It was…the only way to get you…to respond."

The hedge grew together between one breath and the next, and the sound of Dawlish's laughter vanished, as though he had never been there.

She took a second to shake out her limbs, then began her slow jog to the next juncture. As she pivoted left and right, debating a direction, she noticed the color of the leaves changing slightly in the wandlight. To the right, the hedges were darker.

It took weeks to grow these hedges, she thought. New growth is a lighter green. The center of the maze grew first, which means…

She went right.

Immediately, the magic seemed to press tighter around her, and she knew she'd made the correct choice. It went against every instinct to run toward that feeling instead of away from it, but she put her head down and pressed forward.

In the middle of the next aisle, a Sphynx stirred from her nap, sat on her hind legs, and stared patiently at her.

Rigel was tempted to try stunning her straight off, but the gleam in the creature's eyes almost seemed to beg her to try it. "Is this…a riddle thing?"

The Sphynx stretched her wide jaw in a menacing yawn. "What can be learned but never taught?"

Rigel stared at the Sphynx. "Is that…all of it?"

The Sphynx smiled. "Would you like to answer two riddles?"

"No. Thank you." Rigel ran a hand though her short hair, wincing when her fingers caught on the plait Pansy had done on one side. "What can be learned but never taught? Lots of things, I'd think. Pain, maybe. Or…love?"

"These things can be shown by others, and thus taught," the Sphynx said with a haughty toss of her head. "There is but one thing that cannot be demonstrated by another."

Rigel blinked. "Are you…giving me a hint?"

"You seem significantly stupider without your maned companion."

"Maned—Hermione?" Rigel let out a breath. "Yeah, she's much better at these. One thing that cannot be demonstrated or taught…like, how to make your heart beat? No, that can't really be learned, either. Is it…self-confidence?"

She stared at the Sphynx. The Sphynx stared back. "I'm going to have to fight you, aren't I?"

The creature's smile was answer enough.

"Come on, Archie, it's not that hard," Lily bemoaned.

"I'd fight it, too," James said with a shrug. "Riddles are nonsensical."

Remus kept his eyes on Archie, but he could feel the heavy eye-roll Lily gave her husband. As the boy began to weave around the Sphynx's claws, Remus sharpened his omnioculars and slowed them down a few notches. Archie's style was unorthodox, but incredibly effective. He never hesitated, seeming as much a creature as the being he fought in the way his instincts guided his reactions.

Archie was nowhere near that skilled over the summer.

"How did he get so good?" Remus muttered the words to himself, but James heard him and answered.

"Training?"

"From who?" Remus shook his head. "This style is nothing like what is taught at Hogwarts, and they didn't even offer the dueling class this year."

Lily's gasp had them focusing on the maze once more, where Archie had caught the Sphynx in a partial-petrification. The creature panted harshly as its legs turned slowly to stone. Archie wiped the sweat from his brow, and began to move on.

"It's you."

The mirror transmitted the Sphynx's words loud and clear. Archie paused in the frame. "What?" he asked dully.

"The truth none can teach you; it's who you are."

Archie winced. "Oh. I suppose you're right."

He walked on. The sound pivoted to Owens, who was caught in some kind of vertigo spell. Remus tuned it out in favor of asking Sirius, "Has he mentioned extra training to you?"

"Why are you so fixated on his training?" Sirius muttered, avoiding Remus' gaze.

Remus gestured at Archie's mirror with an impatient hand. "Who is that boy up there, Sirius? How could he have changed so much so quickly?"

"Somehow Snape's involved, I just know it." James yelped as Lily slapped his shoulder.

"Even Severus's style doesn't quite match. How could—"

"He's my son," Sirius snapped. "It doesn't matter how he does it, only that he survives it."

"He out-dueled an Auror," Remus growled. "There's something not right, Sirius, I—"

"I know that!" Sirius rounded on him, his face so close Remus could smell the fear on his breath. Lily pulled gently on his arm, and Sirius backed away slightly. "I know, Remus. He's different. I don't know why or how, okay? I don't know my own son anymore." He whispered the last, his expression harshly bracketed in pain.

Remus regretted upsetting Sirius further, but he knew in his gut something was wrong. "You don't think he'd…" He couldn't finish the question.

Sirius sneered. "Pay someone else to do the tournament for him?" Remus winced at the way it sounded, but Sirius merely shook his head. "No. I would, but Archie is better than me. Anyway," he added under his breath, turning back toward the maze. "It's been longer than an hour."

It had been, at that.

Rigel could swear the hedge was growing more restless as she neared the center. She wondered if it was annoyed at her—she had blown a Professor-Dawlish-sized hole though one of its appendages.

Don't personify the hedge, she told herself sharply.

It rustled in an invisible wind, banishing all other sound until the only thing she could hear was the rushing of leaves. She gritted her teeth against the sound current and pressed on. The hedge fairly screamed at her as she turned the next corner. It felt like running into a headwind of pure magic—she had to be close.

The mists parted like a veil just a few steps from the junction, and the rest of the corridor was revealed in sudden, sharp relief—the cup stood in the center, gleaming with an active portkey's tell-tale glow, and on the far side—Fleur.

The silver-haired girl slumped slightly, a slash through her shoulder that was bleeding profusely. Rigel tensed the muscles in her legs a took a deep breath. They'd have to race for it. Her toes dug into the grass as she shot forward in an all-out sprint. Fleur was running, too—was it slower than she'd seen the girl run before? She couldn't be sure. She pumped her legs on sheer willpower, eating up the ground between herself and the cup. Her fast-twitch muscles protested, but she was past feeling the pain. They came within fifteen feet of the cup. Ten feet, eight, and—the hedge erupted around them.

Vines snaked out, tripped both of them, and Rigel went down hard as she grappled with the cantankerous bush. It dragged her across the ground, up, then back down, and she fought the nauseating vertigo as she struggled to right herself against the maze's will. She flared her magic violently, but there was something resistant in the plant's makeup. The bloddy thing was imbued with more magic than made any sense, and raw power alone wasn't—

A spell, white-hot and sizzling, sliced through the hedge cleanly. The bulk of what had attached itself to Rigel fell away, and she dropped to the ground on a rough roll. She came out of it in a backwards scramble and saw Fleur still trapped in the hedge ten feet away. In an instant, she knew what had happened. The other girl didn't meet her eyes, appeared to still be struggling with the hedge herself, but who else could it have been?

Fleur had deferred.

Rigel took the chance the other girl had bought her. She wrapped a shield around herself and dove for the cup. Vines grasped for purchase and failed. Five steps. Two. She put her wand back in its holster, and palmed the disk the twins had slipped her for the grand finale in her left hand. One step. It was over.

Her right hand closed on the handle and the world tilted sideways.

On.

Its.

Axis.

Finally. With a stumbling gasp, all of his plans fell into place. The boy won.

He would never admit to nerves, but it had been grating to watch the Delacour chit come so close. The boy had an unnatural luck—her spell misfired and released Rigel instead. He took the chance, naturally, Slytherin that he was. The great mirror shone white as the portkey activated.

He allowed himself a smile as the Minister stood to officiate the crowning. The boy reappeared on the stage, disheveled but whole and unquestionably—

Magic lashed out from the four corners of the stage. Tom reared to his feet, wand in hand, Dumbledore a moment behind.

"Tom, what have you—"

He hissed at the old fool. "Not. Me."

Five figures reillusioned themselves on the platform. One at each corner—ward casters. Barty, he cursed, eyes drawn to the blithering imbecile at the northern corner. He sharpened his magical sight, and now he could see the runes, hidden cleverly among innocuous strengthening arrays, bleeding to life across the structure.

He cast at the wards before anyone could react. His spell resounded against them with a thundering crack, but the winner's platform was left untouched. The fifth figure, standing in the center of the stage near their bewildered champion, threw back his hood and glared up at Tom defiantly, as though he was meant to recognize him.

A vampire, that much was obvious. He had never crossed the covens. Whosoever had the gall to interrupt his tournament was going to regret crossing him, however.

Dumbledore let loose an outlandish display of magic that poured over the wards like an undammed river. Those near them in the box backed away from the force of it, but Tom stood his ground a pace away. The old man strained visibly before coming to the conclusion Tom had reached already. As he pulled back his magic, for once looking all his hundred-some years, Dumbledore spoke the terrible realization aloud.

"They've anchored to Hogwarts."

Bloody. Damn. Wards.

Rigel's magic lashed out in terrified fury. She wouldnotbetrapped wouldnotbetrappedagain.

It didn't make it far from her skin. A vacuum opened up, like a gaping tear in the world, and sucked the magic away from her grasp. Rigel pushed herself up on shaking hands, eyes darting about the platform. Where did it go? She let a smaller amount of magic loose, and this time followed it carefully. It traveled less than a foot before being swept up in some kind of current, like metal shavings to a magnet. The invisible current carried it to the gaudy roman pedestal, stage center-left.

The podium was a magical magnet.

"Powerful, isn't it?"

That voice. Like dust on a stone step. She looked up and stared as Gavril threw back his hood and raised his sharp chin toward the judges' box. Magic slapped the side of the ward in a dull roar, and Rigel belatedly realized: this was not part of the task at all.

"Gavril. What are you…?"

Her voice echoed strangely all around her, and she realized her headband was still transmitting. She stopped speaking when a sinister smile, the likes of which she had never seen on the lieutenant, crawled over his face. She forced her exhausted legs to stand and turned in a slow circle.

Barty Jr was behind her at the nearest corner of the platform. A woman she didn't recognize stood at another, a masked man she knew as Scar, and—

She blinked. Jordan?

Lee Jordan sneered at her from across the square stage, but Gavril drew her attention as he took a menacing step toward her.

"So you recognize my host?" the vampire chuckled, a mirthless, creaking sound. "Small world. I wonder if you'll be so quick to recognize me."

Host…

Something that had been lurking in the back of her mind, a fear that she had never put fully to bed, rose up from its tangle of sheets with a strangled cry. Voldemort.

She dropped her wand into her hand and struck out with the laser-sharp point of a piercing spell. It flew like an arrow—until it curved back and fizzled against the podium's runes.

"A magical attractant," Gavril—Voldemort, dropped the words almost idly. "Well worth what it cost to procure, judging by the magic you're throwing around—someone's grown into their core, hm?" He gestured to the other four, all of whom knelt in obsequious patience, waiting for…something. "When they brought me tales of how powerful you'd become, I was dismissive…but then, I underestimated you once before, didn't I?"

"What are you trying to achieve, Voldemort? This stadium is surrounded. Aurors, Hogwarts professors, not to mention Dumbledore and Riddle." She spat the last name in his face and watched it twist with a vicious sense of satisfaction. "Do you think any of them will let you get away?"

"Do not speak my name." He took another step toward her. They were almost within arm's length.

"You shouldn't share a name you don't want people to use," she hissed.

His face contorted with fury and she use the moment of distraction to strike, slamming her foot into his knee—or where his knee should have been. A fist like a stone that she never saw coming smashed into the side of her head and Rigel hit the deck hard.

Through the ringing in her ears, she could just make out the sound of Gavril's stolen laugh. Vampire, kid, Dom whispered in her ear. Right.

Rigel sent magic to her wounded head and breathed a small sigh of relief when it wasn't sucked away by the magical attractant. The magic within her skin seemed to be safe; she could heal herself, at least. Dom helped her focus through the dizziness to stem the internal bleeding, and as her eardrums repaired themselves, she heard the battering ram of concussive magic pounding away at the platform wards in successive blows. The Aurors were working in tandem, and others would be helping—her family, her teachers. The wards couldn't withstand that forever. She just had to stall.

Rigel pushed herself up onto hands and knees and spat a glob of blood into her sleeve. "You must be…very weak."

Voldemort whirled to glare at her, the movements unnaturally graceful in the vampiric form he possessed. "I could crush you with two fingers, boy."

"Physically, sure," she bit out, forcing a laugh. "Like a muggle. You're magically weak, though, aren't you? That's why you need help from a school drop-out, an alley thug, a greedy politician's son, and…I assume, a lady with poor taste in friends."

The redheaded woman barred yellow teeth at her, but Voldemort bent close enough to block out the others and hissed, "I have magic enough to come back from the grave, boy. Magic enough to survive for years as mere shadow and vapor. Magic enough to possess the darkest of creatures—"

"With some help from Jordan's neuro-toxins, right?" Rigel sneered. "Face it. Without these wards, you'd already be finished—there are hundreds of wizards out there more powerful than you."

"But not more powerful than you," Voldemort said lowly.

He appeared behind her faster than her eyes could track. Her magic was whisked away as quickly as it left her skin. Her arms were wrenched behind her back and her wand torn from her hand with enough force to break two of her fingers. She cried out, enraged to see it taken, and Voldemort laughed into her ear. "Whoops. Don't know my own strength."

Each of her arms was secured to the podium, and she could feel the greedy magnet at her back suckling the stray edges of her magic. She wrapped it tightly inside herself and clamped down. It was trapped, as surely as she was, but not forever.

Voldemort stepped back to inspect his handiwork and twirled her wand in long, pale fingers. He frowned down at the tool, turning it over and over in his hands. "This wand. It calls to me…"

As well it might; it was his original wand's brother.

He tried to cast with it, but the holly wand's tip barely sparked. She thought he must have forgotten what happened when he tried to use her wand while possessing Ginny. With a moue of disappointment, he pocketed it. "Magic is beyond me in this form," he admitted. His eyes locked with hers, and she noticed they were a deep, glowing red. "Not for much longer, though."

She struggled instinctively against the bonds, every part of her rebelling against the thought of it. "I won't let you possess me," she growled.

"Tried that already." He shrugged, strangely nonchalant. "I do believe you'd die first. I don't need your body, however. Only your magic."

He snapped his fingers, and Lee Jordan approached from the far corner of the stage. He cradled a stone-grey device like a turnip in his hands, runes of darkest amethyst shining along it in twisting ribbons.

"I asked to be here," he said as he stopped in the middle. "I want to look into your eyes when the magic drains out of you."

Rigel stared at him. "You shame your House, Lee Jordan."

His handsome face contorted. "You—"

"Enough." Voldemort took the device from the boy and waved him back. When the center of the platform was clear, he took the device by the stem and spun it like a top. It whirled across the stage, spitting runes out in patterns much faster than anyone could have drawn them. Hundreds of runes were laid in the space of a minute. It was a marvel, and it told her one thing: he was conscious of the time, too. He knew the wards wouldn't last forever.

Scar stepped forward next. As he walked, he peeled an illusion away from a great cauldron at the back of the stage. Rigel goggled at it—it was the largest she'd ever seen. Scar hefted it carefully toward the center of the runic array. Smoke like dry ice drifted over its surface in cirrus clouds. She didn't recognize the brew, but it was certainly in the advanced stage. Coupled with a runic array large enough to fill half the platform…she didn't know what they had planned, but it wasn't casual magic.

Rigel steeled herself for the worst.

Lucius tried to follow the rapid argument unfolding beside him, but it was difficult to tear his eyes from the platform where Rigel Black was being held hostage. Narcissa trembled against him in impotent fury, and he felt much the same.

"They've anchored that ward to Hogwarts herself, Minister, what part of that don't you comprehend?"

Lucius winced. It was not like his lord to be so blunt with the Minister, but then, time was wasting.

"To get through it, we must dismantle the entire ward system around the school," Dumbledore told him. "There is no other way."

Fudge spluttered. "Those wards have stood since the Founders!"

"A child is in danger, Cornelius." Madam Marchbanks spoke sharply.

"But we don't even know what's going on yet! To tear down the Founder's wards just like that—"

"There is no discussion of if," Lord Riddle cut in, stark finality in his tone. "Only how."

Dumbledore inclined his head. "Well said, Tom. I will go to the lodestone and begin the unweaving."

"Begin the what—"

A flash of fire and heat prompted a flinch Lucius would deny to his dying breath. When he opened his eyes, Dumbledore was gone.

"Bloody phoenix," Goldentower muttered, wiping soot from his face.

"What on Merlin's green earth…"

Narcissa gripped his forearm hard enough to draw blood beneath his coat. Lucius turned back to the platform, where an array as large as the main foyer in his mansion had appeared out of nowhere.

"How…" he clamped his mouth shut before he could embarrass himself further. Turning to Lord Riddle, he said, "Is there anything we can do?"

The most powerful man Lucius knew clenched his fist helplessly and stared down at the unfolding drama. "Until he unravels the anchors, I can do nothing."

Lucius held his wife close, and thanked every ghost in his family tree that his son had not been selected for the tournament after all.

"I hate this, Lucius," Narcissa whispered for his ears alone.

"Rigel is strong. Believe in him."

The vampire—Voldemort, Rigel kept calling him, and what kind of French demon was that?—drew something small from his robes. A pair of vials, they could see through Rigel's mirror. Filled with…blood. Something sunk in Lucius' chest. Blood magic was never good.

"Recognize this, clever boy? It's yours." The creature tipped a vial over the input array, and the runes captured its contents in floating stasis. The empty vial was tossed aside, and the vampire sneered down at Rigel. "No use taking it now, when it will be so much more potent willingly given."

"Barty," Lord Riddle snarled.

Lucius frowned, trying to follow the logic of his rage, and Narcissa whispered, "The fifth task."

Of course. The final ward had required a blood sacrifice. But that meant…

"They meant him to win." Goldentower said it slowly, somewhat disbelieving. "Someone planned it months in advance, and designed the tasks to culminate in this moment." The man turned a weighty gaze on Lord Riddle, who drew himself to full height as his nostrils flared.

"Be careful whom you paint with accusations. Barty is a traitor and will be dealt with accordingly."

"By which you mean a fair trial and equitable sentence," Goldentower drawled, sarcastic disgust in every syllable.

"The second vial," Marchbanks said suddenly. She looked to Goldentower and they communicated something silently. "You don't think…"

They didn't have to wonder long. Rigel shook with anger as his captor upended the second vial onto the runes. "Your cousin's."

Rigel bucked wildly against the restraints. "If you've touched a hair on Harry's head, I'll—"

"Your blood cousin, fool."

"Tonks." The horrified whisper echoed throughout the stadium as Rigel slumped against the podium.

"She squealed like a pig when we cut her throat."

Narcissa went limp beside him. "Andy's child…" she moaned.

"She's alive." Goldentower said it confidently, leaving no room for doubt. "Rigel healed her in time."

"Silence." Riddle was fixated on the platform below, listening hard.

"The ritual is stronger with blood from a living family member—to give consent, so to speak." Voldemort said it slowly, mockingly. Every word was designed to hurt. "It'll anchor on your shared gift, and tear that from you, too."

The redheaded woman stepped forward. Lucius didn't recognize her—didn't recognize any of the interlopers apart from Crouch's misbegotten son—but she had the ragged look of a person who spent too much of their lives in drudgery. She held a weathered tome in both hands and when she spoke, it was with the Old Tongue.

The box was silent as they absorbed the words. Lucius had to till the frozen fields of his youth to recall their significance, but at last, it came to him.

"It's an ancient magical transference ritual," Lucius murmured, in case his lord didn't recognize it. Lord Riddle tilted his head slightly to indicate he was listening. "Its use is strongly discouraged. It will convey a pureblood's magic to a lesser vessel, but was only intended for times of true peril to a family line."

"The gift he speaks of…" It was not a question, but Lucius supplied the answer anyway.

"The boy's Metamorphism—his cousin shares it." At Riddle's sharp look, he elaborated. "A passive give, as I understand it, and not much under the boy's control. He may be hoping the ritual will amplify it."

Sharp gasps sounded throughout the box as the cauldron on the platform boiled over in ash-grey smoke.

The vampire stepped toward the cauldron, anticipation lighting his ancient features.

"You don't want to do this." Rigel pleaded with the creature, and Lucius' heart burned for him. A scion as powerful and talented as Rigel Black, stripped of his magic before his prime. It was unthinkable. But the ritual was immutable. If Dumbledore didn't work quickly, it would be too late. Squibhood…or worse.

The thing stalking the platform only laughed. It stepped into the cauldron, and its laugh turned to a shriek that slowly choked itself into silence.

The stadium held its breath as runes all across the array lit up in a blaze of power. The four humans bent to the edges of the circle and added their own power to it. Something writhed in the cauldron, obscured by the ashy mist.

Rigel screamed. He writhed and panted against his bonds, and Lucius had to master his stomach before he could sharpen his Sight and look as the ritual sunk its hooks into the child—or tried to. The connection between the cauldron and Rigel was warped, somehow.

"Something is awry," he breathed.

The figure in the cauldron stumbled out into a haze of magic that roiled in the air, seeking but denied an outlet. Rigel screamed again, and it was echoed by the other figures on the platform as magic unfettered burst in an uncontrolled wave from the array. Rigel was pressed to the podium as the others fell to the deck, and the magic was so thick Lucius could see the attractant attempting to pull it all into its powerful ensnarement.

The creature in the center fought through the storm of magic. "WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?"

The smoke from the cauldron cleared, and Lucius sucked in a breath as the figure was revealed—no longer a vampire, but a boy of perhaps seventeen. He turned in slow horror to regard his lord, whose features differed from the creature on the stage only in maturity. Their fury was perfectly matched.

A warning squeeze from Narcissa pulled his attention back to Rigel. The boy watched the newly-risen creature approach, his eyes narrowed against the intensity of the magical winds.

The…thing that looked so much like a young Riddle wrapped its hands around Rigel's neck and squeezed. Lucius braced himself, but Rigel didn't appear to be suffocating. "His vampiric strength is gone," he heard Goldentower say.

"What. Did. You. Do?"

In the mirror, they could see the hard lines of wrath and fear in the creature's face. Rigel's thin voice echoed through the stadium almost softly.

"You fucked up. The ritual won't work."

The creature turned on one of his own disciples with a howl. "Jordan. Fix this!"

The dark-skinned boy held up his hands in supplication. "The runes are correct, master! It's the boy—or the blood. The s-signatures aren't compatible!"

When it seemed as though the creature would strike his follower, Rigel laughed. It was a coarse, bruised sound, but there was unmistakable humor running through it like a thread of steel.

"Bad idea to use a…signature-sensitive ritual. So…delicate, aren't they?"

The creature took up Rigel's wand and attempted to cast with it. When it failed, he tossed the tool aside in utter fury. "Whose blood was that?"

Rigel gave a pained grin. "Not mine."

Narcissa gasped. Lucius bit his lip to keep from doing the same.

Marchbanks was unable to contain herself. "He used someone else's blood in the fifth task? How could he have anticipated…?"

"Draco calls him paranoid," Narcissa murmured.

"Perhaps it has saved him." Lucius held her hand tightly.

"No." Riddle said the word with bleak certainty, even as the creature below snarled.

"Take his blood. We will salvage it."

Barty Jr. advanced on Rigel with his wand outstretched.

"It won't be as strong unwilling," Lucius said, quietly desperate. "He may only get a portion."

Narcissa averted her eyes as Barty Jr. cut one of Rigel's arms free to bleed it. There was a blur of motion, and Barty stumbled back, clutching his stomach where a dark stain spread quickly. The creature let out a cry of anger and bodily hauled the stuck man out of the circle before he could bleed on the runes. Rigel held a knife in the hand that had been freed, and blood dripped from its blade to the decking.

"Here's your…blood," Rigel panted, flicking the tip of the knife toward the array. The masked man moved quickly, and his magic caught the drops just before they touched the circle.

Lucius loosed a frustrated growl. "So close…he almost ruined it." At Narcissa's questioning look, he said quietly, "The ritual can take one mistake, but two?" He shook his head. The boy was brilliant. It really would be such a loss.

The woman kicked the knife from Rigel's fingers, and the Jordan boy punched Rigel across the mouth. His head snapped back into the podium, and blood spluttered from his mouth as he coughed to keep from choking on it.

The dark-skinned boy wiped his fingers through the red liquid dribbling down Rigel's chin and smiled. He bent and smeared it on the runic array. Lucius braced himself as the magic snapped into a controlled whirlwind on the platform. With his Sight, he watched the connection re-establish itself—and sputter into nothing.

"It isn't working." The words felt wondering on his lips. A spark of hope flickered in his breast—and quailed as Lord Riddle erupted into furious Parseltongue. Lucius looked back at the boy with a lurch in his stomach, but no, it really wasn't working. And wasn't that a good thing? But then, why did Riddle look more furious than ever?

Jordan cowered on the platform as the creature laid its wrath on him for a second time. "Master, please, the b-blood—it isn't compatible. Look at the runes…"

"You just took it from him."

"It's not pure."

Lucius felt his blood freeze. He couldn't mean…

The creature on the platform turned slowly back to Rigel, who stood against the podium with his head held high, trembling and defiant…and not at all confused.

It was almost funny. Watching their faces contort. Watching their plans fall to pieces.

"How arrogant to use a ritual so specific," she muttered. She felt a little apathetic, watching him scream uselessly at her in his little boy body. "The blood of the family member should match the blood given. The magical signature in the blood given should match the magic being transferred. And most importantly…it's an unequal transfer." She rested her head against the podium, which still pulsed with magic behind her, bloated on all it had absorbed. "Pureblood to halfblood, I believe it was intended. Maybe it could be wrangled to work halfblood to muggleborn. But halfblood to halfblood?" She closed her eyes and shook her head with a wry smile. "Absolutely not."

The magic roared around them, twisted and shuddering as the ritual tried and failed to contain and channel it. Voldemort screamed over top of it, his voice echoing through her headband to every corner of the stadium.

"You. Are not. Arcturus Black. WHO ARE YOU!?"

It was almost funny.

The question she woke with every morning. The question she went to bed with every night.

She was so close to breaking free. Her untethered hand, unwisely cut free, was working on the ropes, but it was clumsy with newly-healed fingers. Her other hand still clutched what she'd portkeyed onto the platform with, what seems like hours ago.

There were still the wards to deal with, but she'd had time now to study them. Blaise had already shown her what to do, and she would think about why her friend's wards had been erected by Riddle's evil construct later. First, she had to get rid of the magical attractant. Free magic wouldn't work. Magic had to be bound by runes to get far from her skin.

Voldemort was bent double against the press of a magical storm of his own making. He wasn't nearly so strong now that he'd abandoned Gavril's body. The vampire lay crumpled beside the cauldron, and she spared a hope that there was something left of him when this was all over.

"I WILL TEAR THE TRUTH FROM YOUR MIND, IMPOSTER!"

The only power remaining to him, she thought tiredly. There was no question whether she was strong enough to fight off a Legilimency attack—she wasn't.

Cold hands gripped her neck once more and she felt his entry like a blade to her brain, like nails raking her very soul. Rigel thrashed, trying to use the pain as an anchor, to stay awake and fight. She was so close to finishing. The imbuing was…almost…there…

The violence of his intrusion slammed her into unconsciousness.

The enemy came boldly—foolishly. He tore through the snowstorm, leaving scars on the girl's mindscape that would take time and magic to heal.

Dom met him at the foot of the mountain with a forbidding scowl. "No vacancy, mate."

The curiously constructed bit of magic paused, looked him over, and sneered. "I won't be fooled twice by that puppet."

The fragile ego encased in magic attempted to move past him, and Dom pulled the mindscape out from under him.

"Agh!" The enemy construct slammed into a wall and reared back, finding itself suddenly in a crumbling tomb. It took a step back and—

Fell off the top of the mountain. Before it could re-orient itself, it slammed into the side of a pyramid and—

Bam, into one of the tunnels beneath the mountain and—

Splash, into the Nile. It came up wet and spluttering and found itself buried to the neck in the burning sand.

A Sphynx rested her taloned paw on the enemy's head, and Dom bent down to talk to the head in his most reasonable tone. "You like magic so much? Here's a little on the house."

He shuddered as the magic clawed its way up from his belly. With a great heave, he spat the little ball of foreign magic onto the construct's sand-crusted head. It caught fire, and smoldered as the enemy construct screamed.

"The resonance burns a bit, doesn't it?" Dom stood and stretched his arms. "Now, about your presence in this realm."

He hauled the construct up by the neck and stared into its soulless eyes. For a single, frozen moment, he let the sentient ball of angst see the endless depths of his existence. He revealed the ages of silence, the terrible question without an answer, the unending, unraveled, aloneness. Then he whispered.

"The position of magical advisor has been filled."

No longer wary of mingling her magic with the vile stuff in his belly, Dom drew on the golden sun and banished the construct through the mists.

The rest is up to you, kid. WAKE UP.

Rigel came to with a gasp. The podium dug into her back, but the knots were loose. She ripped at them with a grunt of effort, trying to get enough slack to slip them from her other arm. Blood rushed back into her limbs with a vengeance, but she dulled the pain automatically, her magic circulating inside her like a caged lioness.

Voldemort was seizing on the platform, the whites of his eyes showing. His minions hovered over him uncertainly; Scar waved his wand intently above the convulsing chest.

The resonance, Dom whispered with an ominous laugh. It's just different enough from his warped signature to be extremely unpleasant.

This was her only chance. She gave up on the bonds and focused on the tiny disk clenched in her left hand. She'd imbued it to the hilt, pumping magic straight from her palm too fast for the podium to steal. Rigel shoved just a little more magic into it. The runes started to heat uncomfortably against her skin.

Voldemort began to rouse. The only words he choked out were, "Kill him. Kill. Him."

Barty was still slumped and bleeding, but Jordan started toward her. A device glinted in his hands—it looked sharp.

"The world can watch what happens to filth when it reaches too high," he crooned.

This is going to hurt, Rigel acknowledged.

When he was within reach, she slammed her forehead into his. The crack of his skull against the headband sounded like a thunderclap in the stadium. Her knee came up to meet his crotch, her free arm grabbed the device from his limp hands, and she used the sharp end to cut the remainder of her bonds in one precise slice.

She dropped the disk and dove.

The pedestal latched onto the artifact that pulsed to the brim with power. It was pulled into the stone—

And exploded.

Rigel threw up a shield at her back and knew the magical attractant had been destroyed when it held. She heard Jordan scream as the shards of the podium found him unprepared. Cracks and booms and unintelligible light filled the platform as dozens of overpowered fireworks went off all at once, right on top of one another.

She couldn't hear anything but static, couldn't see beyond an impression of overwhelming light and force, but then, one color cut through all the rest.

A beam of green light, coming right for her.

Miscalculation, was all she could think as the Killing Curse washed out the world.

Heat in her chest, and she wondered—was this death? This light, so bright and unending; this warmth, like a searing sun setting in her heart.

She took a breath. Two breaths.

The light receded enough to identify the source—her necklace. Her mother's amulet was glowing. It was the burning in her chest. It had stopped the unstoppable curse.

The fireworks crackled out. Scar stared at his wand and everyone else stared at her.

She clung to the heartbeat in her veins and the air in her breath. Everything else could be wondered at later. Rigel unleashed her magic at last.

It blew the others back like a jet-stream, clearing the way to the nearest corner of the wards. Only one person was necessary to take it down from the inside. Rigel took the steps almost serenely.

She reached out to the anchoring runes and ripped. The wards resisted, like stakes frozen into the ground, but Rigel's will was stronger than the pull of whatever ley line they were tied into. With a groan, the wards rippled and strained, but they. Gave. Way.

A strange sort of vindictive pleasure rose in her as the wards shattered into a thousand shards of magic. The trapped little girl who had to be saved last year had broken the cage herself this time.

The roar of the crowd slammed into her. She could see everything clearer, now. The people in the stands, the Minister gaping just above her from his box. Riddle looked ready to flay her alive, and the Malfoys—they didn't seem to recognize her at all. Aurors rushed the stage. Scar saw them coming, looked at the injured Barty and Jordan, and apparated away with the convulsing construct in his arms. The redheaded woman was a beat behind him.

The anti-apparition wards were down. It took her a moment to realize what that meant.

Aurors started toward her, but an explosion outside the stadium turned every head but one.

In a sort of trance, she saw Sirius coming across the platform toward her. His hands were bloodied, as though he'd beat them against the wards. She reached up with numb fingers and pulled the transmitter off her head. She tossed it to the platform floor and summoned her wand, which lay abandoned on the other side of the stage. Sirius's face was so close she could see the exact moment it crumpled in disbelief.

She turned on the spot, and felt the whoosh of displaced air as his fingers almost caught her.

She didn't go far.

All around him, people shouted. They'd been shouting and panicking ever since Rigel touched that cup.

Draco held Pansy's hand, because he didn't know what else to do. His first instinct, when they realized something was wrong, had been to find his parents, but what could they do that Dumbledore and Riddle weren't already trying? He had to believe that Rigel would get out of it—he always had before.

And then, without any warning, Rigel wasn't Rigel. Or he was, but something really messed up was going on. A man shot the Killing Curse at him, and he had never heard Pansy scream like that before. He never wanted to hear it again.

Nothing made any sense after that. Rigel wasn't dead. Rigel tore down what seemed to be every ward for miles, and suddenly people were shouting about the stands being unstable. And they were shouting other things that he didn't want to hear.

"Are they going to arrest him?"

"How is he not dead?"

"He's some kind of undead—"

"He's a monster!"

Draco was barely holding it together under the absolute tsunami of emotions rioting around him. His friends weren't helping in the slightest. Blaise was pale, his lips white as he pressed them together against whatever words wanted to come out.

"Why did he run?" Millicent moaned. "Rigel, you idiot, you never run."

"'Course he ran," Theo snarled. "Millie, you saw the ritual fail. If he stays here, it'll be just like Greengrass! Worse, even. You could tell he knew it."

"Shut up," Draco snapped. "We don't know anything yet."

"You can't be that stupid—"

"Be quiet, Theodore." Pansy jumped into the argument with vehemence. "You cannot possibly presume to know circumstances—"

Draco tuned them out. He couldn't think. He pushed his way through the stands, not caring who he elbowed on his way to the stairs. As he rounded the first landing, he saw Sirius Black, kneeling with his head bowed on the winner's platform. A green headband clutched in his fingers.

He shook his head to erase the image. Not my problem. I've got to find Rigel.

Rigel. Where would Rigel go?

He slipped out of the chaos of the stadium, running as fast as he could back toward the castle. He passed a team of Aurors with tracking crups fanning out across the grounds.

"Young apparators can't go very far—search the forest!"

Draco cursed his own laziness for not learning to apparate over the summer like his father suggested. Still, he hadn't trained all those mornings for nothing. His legs soared over the flagstones of the entrance hall. He pounded down the stairs and flew through the dungeon corridors on wings of desperation.

The world had gone crazy. Rigel was a dizzying mess of contradictions, but a few fundamental truths wouldn't shift, no matter what else had.

He'd never leave without his potions kit.

She collapsed on her bed, the breath coming in short gasps between her ribs. For one, keening moment she wanted to cry.

There was no time.

She pointed her wand at the door and locked it with the strongest charm she knew. Her eyes traced the room. First, the bed. Slipping to the floor, she vanished her blankets, bedsheets, and pillows. The mirror went into her pocket.

The trunk was next. She slammed open the lid and rifled through it, deciding moment to moment what to vanish and what to take. The uniforms she wore, Archie's underclothes and socks—all vanished. No item of clothing survived, save for her father's cloak. With a mental apology, she vanished the shoes Draco had occasionally lent her.

She tore through the rest of the room. Her toiletries were removed from the bathroom, her towel—even the rug had to go. Anything she'd touched or might have shed essence on.

Her school bag was the last. Emptied of papers, notes, and books. All of it vanished along with every letter she'd ever kept—all but the Map. She swung the potions kit over her shoulder—

The door slammed open. She whirled, and caught Draco in the doorway, the knife Sirius had once given him shaking in his hand.

His eyes took in the room, the missing objects, and he shook his head slowly. "Rigel, what are you doing?"

"I don't have time to explain right now, Draco. I have to go."

"No. You should stay."

"I can't." She pleaded with her eyes, begged him to understand.

He took a step toward her, empty hand outstretched. "You've been through hell just now, Rye. Everyone will understand you panicked, but don't make it worse. Just come with me and explain."

"I can't explain."

"Everything will be like it was," he said.

She shook her head helplessly. "I can't…they all heard."

"That psychopath doesn't know anything about you," Draco said firmly. "We'll prove you're who you are. Here—" He held out the dagger, hilt toward her. "Take it. It will prove you're a Black. We can prove it to them…"

She heard the words he wasn't saying. Please, prove it to me.

She wanted to. She wanted to take all the doubt and confusion in his eyes and vanish it like everything else she'd touched. She held her hand out and moved it slowly toward the dagger. Perhaps she could overpower the recognition spell. Trick the mechanics, somehow…

Before she'd even touched it, the hilt turned an angry red and Draco hissed as it burned his fingers. She closed her fist and felt her heart solidify.

"I can't. Because it's true."

"No." He dropped the dagger to the carpet and shook his head angrily. "What does an old knife know?"

"Draco." She caught his gaze and held it. "It's true."

"I don't understand. Are you a bastard?"

She shook her head. "I'm not related to the Blacks at all. I'm not a pureblood—I'm not even English."

Draco flinched. "Did…did Rigel get you to do the tournament for him?"

Her face pinched and her eyes burned. "No. I've always been here. I'm just not…I wanted—" She blew out a shaky breath. "It doesn't matter what I wanted. I have to leave, now, Draco. I'm sorry."

"No, Rigel. We'll figure something out—"

"Don't you get it?" she snapped. He stared at her, and she said it as clearly and slowly as she could. "That's not even my name."

Understanding, cold and unforgiving, began to dawn at last in his eyes. She swept the room one last time, making certain she hadn't forgotten anything incriminating. When she turned back to her friend, he looked at her, lost. She had set him utterly adrift.

There was nothing she could do about it.

"You won't look for me," she said, building ice in careful layers with her words.

"I can't just forget everything—"

"You won't look for me, because I'm calling in your Life Debt."

Draco's face went white. "You can't."

"I, who saved you from the Sleeping Sickness, do hereby claim the debt of life you owe me." Her voice didn't shake, didn't crack like her insides were cracking. "You and your family, having taken on the debt in kind, shall not look for the boy you know as Rigel Black. You shall not seek news of him, search for signs of him, or participate in hunting for him at the direction of another. Through this, your debt is discharged. So mote it be."

Light flared between them, and Draco clutched at his heart. She wondered if a weight had settled there as surely as it had nested in her breast.

"How could you?" he whispered. "Rigel…"

"There is no Rigel."

"There was, though. We were friends."

She shook her head, and pushed him a little closer to hate. "That was just an elaborate lie, Draco Malfoy. Rigel Black isn't real. And I don't have any friends."

A clean break, she thought, her own heart breaking. She turned on the spot, and was gone before his knees hit the floor.

The tears made the journey with her, but didn't fall until she reappeared in the shadow of the clock tower. She knew she had to gather her strength, had to apparate a few more times to get safely away, but her mind couldn't focus past the look of betrayal on Draco's face.

She vomited into the bushes, vanished it shakily with a jerk of her wand, and sobbed into her fist until she could breathe again.

Before she was ready for the next jump, she felt anti-apparition spells spring like a trap over the school. They'd begun re-weaving the wards already. She pulled out the Map with shaking hands and processed the dotted lines of strangers in every direction. They'd set up a perimeter.

She had to get out.

Her mind raced through options, each more outlandish than the last.

She could don the cloak and try to sneak past highly alert Aurors who were on the lookout for someone sneaking around. She could fight the Aurors, and hope she got away before someone she couldn't overpower arrived.

She could hide in the Room of Requirement. She could brew Polyjuice and when a month had gone by and the search had died down, she could take the form of someone else and just…walk out.

Only she didn't have a month to lose hiding.

She could summon a broom, hope no one noticed it flying around unescorted, and ride it beyond the edges of the wards under the cloak.

The more she looked up at the dark night sky, the more attractive that option seemed. It might be easy. There were a few Aurors on brooms, but their patrols weren't seamless. She could slip through.

She closed her eyes and tried not to feel like a coward. Maybe Draco was right, and running away was the wrong thing to do. She wanted to, though. The desire to escape, to just flee, fluttered like wings in her ribcage. For once, she wanted to do the easy thing, not the hard thing. For once, she wanted to give into the urge that had been building in her quietly for years. She wanted to fly away, and never look back.

The urge became a wish, became a need, and she—

She became a bird.

All the thoughts in her head went quiet. Her wings reached out to touch the sky, and the sky was the only thing that mattered. Forward was the only direction left.

Her tears dried up in the wind.

Chapter 14

He'd been on the hunt all night. The coordinates they traced took them back to the boy's dorm room, then the clock tower, then nothing.

The boy had found some other means of escape.

Ground sweeps turned up nothing; no brooms had been recorded leaving the hastily erected perimeter wards. Even the two they'd captured at the scene—Jordan and Crouch Juniors—only knew as much as everyone else had witnessed. Moody was handling the investigation into this Voldemort person; budding Dark Lords were just his cup of tea.

James was personally selected to head the search for the boy once known as Rigel Black. A halfblood masquerading as a pureblood scion, fooling everyone in British society for…well, they really didn't know how long. The Minister was embarrassed, which meant the hunt for RBC—the Rigel Black Child—was his top priority.

He'd begged off shift nearing noon the next morning, citing the need for sleep. He left the hastily compiled task force plotting a timeline and drafting lists of potential character witnesses. On his way out of the office, he chartered an emergency international portkey. The trainee on duty didn't question the coordinates; crazier things would be done in the midst of this mess.

When he Flooed through to Potter's Place to check in with Lily, Sirius met him at the grate.

"Anything?"

James shook his head. "He's in the wind."

"What next?" Sirius rocked on his heels, looking one loud noise from bolting. James felt sick just imagining what he must be thinking—his son was missing, wanted for questioning in a case of blood identity theft, and Sirius had no idea how long ago the swap had been made. There was no way to know if Archie was complicit or incapacitated—or alive at all.

It wasn't often his official responsibilities and family duties collided. James felt the tension in the line he walked as he removed his Head Auror badge and drew the portkey out of his pocket. "Harry."

Sirius nodded, eyes shadowed. Harry was the only person closer to Archie than Sirius. If anyone other than Archie himself knew something about this doppelganger, it was she.

"James." Lily came through the open doorway, Addy on her hip. James met her with an embrace, feeling the weight of the last twelve hours ease somewhat as she burrowed her face into his neck. "Is there any word?"

"Not yet. I'm going to talk to Harry."

"To America?" Lily drew back, a crease between her brows. "It can't wait until she's home next week?"

He shook his head sharply. "This is going to get out of control fast. There's already talk of blood-testing the whole school, and only Sirius' lordship has shielded him from official questioning. That won't last. If there's anything Harry knows…anything she even suspects, I have to know."

"As her father, or as the Head Auror?"

He grimaced. "Both."

Sirius put a hand on his shoulder. "Best we go." His voice held a harsh tremor, a frisson of horror that had not yet come to rest in his mind.

Lily bit her lip, but nodded. "Quickly, then. You won't be the only ones to think of her."

James pressed their foreheads together, bussed Addy's cheek, and stepped back. He held out the other end of the portkey to Sirius, knowing it was unprofessional and potentially unwise to bring the shattered man along. He also knew if he didn't offer Sirius a direction, his friend would pursue an even less wise one on his own; better Sirius felt he was part of the investigation.

At the activation phrase, they were swept into the distorted shadow-hand of magic and borne painfully through a rip in the world.

Sirius heaved as they hit the manicured lawn of the American Institute of Magic. Cross-Atlantic portkeys carried a small risk of scrambling body parts, but it was the magical backlash that deterred most from resorting to such travel. Still, James winced to see the usually collected man so affected by international travel; his brother in all but blood was reeling, and it showed. Sirius kept what little there was in his stomach and pulled himself upright on shaking legs. James swept the dew from their robes and cast a glance around the unfamiliar grounds. He and Lily had seen it only in pictures. The main entrance was easy to spot: a set of handsome double doors shining in the early morning light, and he set off toward them at a brisk pace.

A witch with Molly Weasley's build and stare met them at the entrance. She wore American style short-robes in Healer's blue and took in his distinctively cut uniform swiftly, eyes lingering on the spot where his badge ought to hang. "What business does the British Ministry have at our school? I hope you know we require a warrant for any searches."

James chose his words carefully. "Britain has no official business here yet. I've simply come to speak to my kid. Harry Potter."

"This is most unusual. The children have just started their final exams."

"I don't care," James said.

"Family emergency," Sirius put in softly.

The witch looked between them somewhat mistrustfully. James could tell she didn't like the way Sirius' eyes shifted restlessly between her face and the school. "I see. And do you have identification to prove your relationship, Mr. Potter?"

"It's Lord Potter," Sirius muttered. If anything, the woman's face closed further.

James gave an apologetic grimace and reached into his robes for his wand. It was internationally registered, as his work often took him abroad. "Will this do?"

She took out her own wand and ran a standard identification charm. "Mahogany, eleven inches, registered to Auror James Potter. Very well." She handed his wand back and produced a list out of thin air. After a moment's consultation, she said, "Potter is taking his first exam in auditorium 1B, right down the first hallway—"

James' heart stopped.

His?

They'd gotten to his little girl, too.

James pushed past the witch at a sprint, ignoring her startled cry. He rounded the corner and flew down the corridor with darkness pushing the edges of his thoughts closer together.

Thisonewon'tgetaway.

He burst into the lecture hall. A dozen heads looked up from their papers, but his gaze caught the one in the third row wearing his daughter's face. The professor shouted something; James didn't hear it. He took a bit of pleasure watching the boy scramble up from the bench as he stalked up the stairs toward him. Whatever he saw in James' face must have terrified him.

"I can explain—"

James levered the imposter up by his collar and growled. "Where is she?"

One of the students—Hermione, of course—tried to stun him. James batted the spell away without loosening his grip.

"Put him down!" the girl shrieked. Two other students grabbed her wand arm before she could hurl something stronger, but James had his focus entirely on the gasping body-snatcher in his daughter's school robes.

"In three seconds, I'm going to forget I'm an Auror and you're going to regret the day you were born if you don't—"

The boy choked, hands scrambling at James' wrist. "P-please…Unc..le..Ja—"

James dropped him like a hot stone.

"Arch?" Sirius came up the stairs beside him. James hated the way the hope clawed up into his friend's voice.

The boy looked between them, swallowing against the pain in his throat convulsively. "Dad? What's going on?"

Sirius fairly vibrated with conflicting impulses. His hand reached out shakily, but James held an arm between them. "Security question," he snapped.

Sirius licked his lips. "What…what animals did I find in your room over winter hols?"

The green-eyed boy regarded them for a long moment, then said quietly, "A fox and a raven."

Sirius released a ragged sob and collapsed on his son, holding him as though he would never again let go. James was left to clench the air between his fists, everything he'd assumed re-evaluated between heartbeats.

As Sirius cried into the boy's—Archie's AIM uniform, James tried not to imagine where his own child could be. Was she the imposter at Hogwarts? The idea was dizzying. Devastating.

"You're coming with us, Arch," he managed hoarsely.

The professor protested once more. "I demand you cease this violent interruption into our final examination, Aurors. Whatever business you have with Mr. Potter—"

Sirius let out a hic-cupping laugh and James felt his expression fold into something dangerous. Before he could refute the woman, Archie pushed back from his father's embrace.

"Something's happened to Rigel, hasn't it? Is he…dead?" Archie's voice cracked on the last word and the fear in his eyes made James' stomach sink.

He shook his head slowly, and the relief in Archie's face was staggering.

"Thank Merlin," the boy whispered.

Hermione could contain herself no longer. She reached across Sirius to pull Archie a little closer toward her. "What's happening, Harry? What are they talking about? If you don't want to go with them, I won't let them take you."

Archie looked at the girl, willing to fight two grown wizards for him, and his eyes glistened. To James' frustration, the boy attempted a wry smile. "Somehow, I thought it would be more dramatic than this."

"It was dramatic, I assure you," James bit out.

Archie winced. He took his classmate's hand in both of his and let out a shaky breath. "You're going to read some terrible things about me in the paper. Just know…it wasn't ever what they'll say it was, and I'll never regret coming here and being your friend."

The girl scowled fiercely. "Harry, what—"

"That's not his name," James snapped. "Harry is my daughter's name."

"But he is your daughter," Hermione said, still scowling. The contradiction in gender appeared to mean nothing to her.

Archie squeezed her hand and shook his head. "No…I'm not. My name is Archie, and I was never Harry Potter."

Hermione took half a step back, visibly unnerved, and Archie dropped her hand.

"I'll explain it all in a letter, if you'll read it."

First, he would be explaining it to his father, then him and Lily, then likely all of magical Britain.

Hermione searched Archie's eyes for a long moment, and lifted her chin. "I'll expect the letter on my desk by Monday morning."

"I promise," Archie whispered.

James put a hand on his shoulder and steered him toward the door.

"Your exam—" the professor said weakly, clearly unclear on what to do. The witch who had met them at the entrance put a hand on her colleague's arm and shook her head.

"From the sound of it, that's the least of his troubles." She met James' gaze with a steely challenge. "Now that it has been established this is not your son, Mr. Potter, I'm no longer sure you have the right to remove him from our campus."

"He's my son," Sirius growled. He moved between the two witches and Archie faster than they could draw their wands. "This is the Heir to the House of Black and you will not be preventing his return to England."

"He's also a person of interest in an open investigation into blood-identify theft."

"That's not a crime here in the States," the blue-robed Healer argued.

"It was a crime where they committed it. Consider this a lawful extradition." He pulled out his badge and held it up for her scrutiny.

The witch looked regretfully toward Archie, who shook his head quickly. "It's all right, Healer Beauchamps. This is my dad and uncle, and…I am in a lot of trouble." He fell into a deep bow. "I'm very sorry for lying to you all these years."

Years. The word stuck James like a physical blow.

He clamped down on the boy's shoulder and near-dragged him the rest of the way out of the auditorium. As the doors swung shut behind them, he backed the boy up against the corridor wall and got right into his face. With a voice he'd never used on his nephew before, he demanded. "Where. Is. Harry?"

Archie's chin set stubbornly. "If you don't know…then she's safe."

"Archie," James snarled.

"The mirror," Sirius put in quickly. "Does she have it?"

Archie shook his head. "No, we gave it to Rigel."

"Who is Rigel?"

"What is going on, Archie?" Sirius added, desperately confused, but increasingly present as his worst fears receded.

Archie was the picture of miserable guilt. "It's…complicated. What happened at Hogwarts?"

In his relief and confusion, Sirius forgot the first rule of interrogation—give no information until you know the extent of their information. "Some maniac crashed the last task and tried to drain your—his—magic. Whatever game you were playing was blown right out the water when they realized he wasn't you."

Archie had gone white again. "Did—did they take Rigel's magic?"

"We don't think so, considering he pulled down centuries-old wards and apparated away."

"Enough, Sirius," James interrupted. "Archie, who is that person? Is it…" He had to ask. "Is it Harry?"

Sirius' face fell into dismayed shock. "No…"

"No!" Archie shook his head vigorously, suddenly full of information. "No, it's just this kid we met. He wanted to go to Hogwarts, and I didn't really want to. Harry let me take her place here, and she…"

"Where?" James had to hold himself back from shaking the boy as he hesitated. "Tell me where she is right now, Arcturus Black, or so help me—"

Archie looked to the side, shame hooding his gaze. "I don't know for certain, but she's usually in London."

"London." James gave Archie a flat look.

"Diagon Alley," he muttered. "If you let me get my things from Pettingill, I have the address."

James released him, fighting the relief in his chest that wanted to lull him into relaxation. His girl was fine. Probably wondering what to do next, but fine. In so much trouble she was never leaving the house again—but fine. And Archie was fine. So Sirius would be fine. The rest of it mattered less.

"Quickly," he bit out. "We have a return portkey in twenty minutes."

"I'll go with him." Sirius offered as though it weren't obvious he wasn't letting Archie out of his sight anytime soon.

James made for the lawn, head down as he tried to reconcile everything Archie had just said with what had been revealed the night before. Some kid—and when had they even met and when had they switched?—had taken Archie's place at Hogwarts. Archie was at AIM. And Harry was…

His mind tallied everything in a single column. The Guild internship. Her entrepreneurial ventures. All the time spent in Diagon Alley over the summer hols. The Hurst kid.

Harry was brewing potions. It always came back to that.

Archie and Sirius hurried back across the lawn. Archie was explaining something with a guilty tone.

"—haven't seen the paper yet this morning. Hermione and I were up all night studying for our finals, and I figured Rigel would give a ring on the mirror if anything this bad had happened. I don't know why he wouldn't warn me…"

"So you haven't heard from him?" James cut in sharply.

"Mirror's been quiet the past few days. Nothing seemed off when we spoke last."

James grunted.

"Uncle James, I'm sorry this all—"

James shot him a dark look. "I'm not prepared to take your apology until we find Harry. If anything's happened to her…"

Archie understood that he would never be forgiven unless Harry was all right. "I take full responsibility." As the portkey lit from within, James heard him add under his breath, "Just as she would for me."

It was hours of flying before she was calm enough to change back. Well into the wild Scottish countryside, she collapsed in a heap of limp limbs and disheveled clothing. The leaves of the trees rustled just like the maze, sending shivers of energy down her spine.

Rest was a luxury she had not yet earned.

She pushed to her feet, straightened her robes, and turned on the spot. Again and again, gasping for breath between each jump like a sprinter running consecutive races. When the black edges of her vision receded, she jumped again, knowing even as she ran against the clock that her deadline was no clear thing.

Archie was the only one who could tell them where she was—would be. It would take time for anyone to figure out he was at AIM. She may have to lay low for several days before Archie realized what had happened and came forward. She dared not use the mirror—it was exploitable by à priori magic. While conversations couldn't be replayed, the right spell would reveal how often and for how long the mirrors were connected. Archie had to retain plausible deniability—communicating with 'Rigel' after he was revealed a felon would not help his case.

She had to trust her cousin would follow their plan.

Hours later, Harry leaned against the crumbling wall of an alley in downtown London. The sun threatened to rise at any moment. Her legs trembled in the wake of the chain apparition, but there was no time to strengthen them. She pulled her cloak, temporarily spelled to appear a nondescript grey, tighter around her as she stepped shakily out onto the street. The hood was deep and too heavy to blow in the wind; it easily shadowed a face that no longer served any purpose.

The Leaky Cauldron was sparsely populated at the early hour, but every customer she passed had their face in a newspaper. She tried not to look, but the headline—HOGWARTS HALFBLOOD FLEES THE SCENE—WHO IS RBC?—shouted at her. The picture was blurry, but it showed her fingers curled into claws as she tore through the wards imprisoning—

She hurried out of the pub, breathing heavily through her nose to keep the dizziness at bay.

Diagon Alley was similarly depopulated. She moved as quickly as she dared along the long street, keeping her eyes to the cobblestones. As she passed the intersection where one of the great mirrors had been established for the tournament, she had to consciously resist the urge to hunch guiltily. A hastily draped length of fabric did not disguise what had happened; broken glass littered the street. Someone had shattered it.

Harry moved past it with a purpose and didn't pause until she reached the steps of Gringotts.

The goblin at the door held his spear across it when she tried to enter. "No withdrawals today."

She put some gravel in her voice as she asked, "Why not?"

"Anti-volatility measure. Due to recent political events," the goblin drawled.

"That's fine. I'm here to deposit."

He peered distrustfully into the shadows of her hood, but stood aside.

She was approached by one of the tellers as soon as she entered—that alone was unusual enough to tell her the goblins were unnerved. "Business?" he asked briskly.

"I'd like to deposit something in my family vault."

"Name?"

"Potter."

"Wand?"

She faltered. Her wand was registered to Archie's name. Instead, she held out a bare hand. "Will blood suffice?"

He sliced her palm with the tip of his spear. "Wait here."

She hadn't been to her family vault since she was a small child, and never without her parents. Her personal vault was a low-security option: close to the surface, and not requiring identification beyond an account number and signature. That trip would not suffice for what she had to do.

The goblin returned with a clean spear, evidently satisfied by the tests they'd run. "Right this way, Ms. Potter."

She climbed into the cart he specified. As he climbed in after her, she saw his nostrils flare and wondered if he could smell the blood on her clothes. She curled into herself and ignored his stare.

The cart took off with a rattling jerk and plummeted into the darkness.

It was a much longer ride than she was used to. Torches appeared only sporadically to throw their surroundings into sharp relief. She had brief impressions of honeycomb caverns, ornately carved pillars, and the heat of recent dragon fire. Then they turned a corner, and a waterfall splashed down over the cart, soaking them both.

The cart screeched to a halt and Harry had to gulp air desperately and brace against the rail to keep from hurling. The nausea was much worse than she expected; it felt as though a colony of peaceful snakes in her belly had been tossed like lo mein. When it passed, Harry shook the Thief's Downfall from her eyes and looked up. The goblin had his spear at her throat. "Reveal yourself, imposter."

She raised a hand slowly to grasp the edge of the cloak and pushed it back. The goblin's expression did not change; nor did he strike. Harry gave a vapid smile. "Can you blame a girl for her beauty charms?"

"All such magic must be disclosed prior to visiting the deep vaults."

"I forgot," she said with a sniff. "You already tested my blood. Do you really want to test it again?"

The goblin scowled at her, but retreated to his side of the cart and touched a pendant around his neck. The cart took off again, slowly at first, but with increasing speed.

Harry drew her hood back over her face, trying not to think about how different her hair felt beneath her fingers as she tucked it away. She felt a little bit drunk, all the weight in her body having shifted subtly beneath her clothes, and the jostling cart was not helping the feeling of being suddenly off-balance.

The goblin yanked on the handle and the cart screeched in a piercing protest as it came to rest before the Potter family vault. Harry nearly tripped getting out of the vehicle—there was an inch of extra room in her boots now, and her limbs felt as ungainly as a newborn colt's.

She made a show of digging in her bag, stomping her foot in irritation, and turning back to the cart with a flourish. "I forgot to put it in my bag! Ugh."

"You will not be entering the vault?" the goblin growled. His irritation was not an act.

"Sorry, no. I'll have to come back another time."

She didn't know for certain, but she thought the cart took off even faster on the way back up.

The sun was fully risen when she stepped blinking through the marble doors. Diagon bustled, an unspoken tension thrumming beneath its usual energy—or perhaps that was Harry, projecting her own turmoil outward. She peered with a frown up the long street until she realized she was straining her eyes hard enough to give herself a headache.

Merlin, I forgot how poor my vision was. She'd have to hope she had a pair of glasses at her flat.

She kept the hood up, but wasn't too worried about anyone catching sight of her face. No one could connect her with Rigel Black now.

Her feet found the familiar turn down Knockturn Alley. She took the less commonly used alleys on her way to Dogwood Lane and didn't see anyone she knew. On the other side of Kyprioth Court, she felt most of the anxiety drain from her shoulders.

She stopped at the nearest market and bought a bag of basic pantry items without bargaining. At the corner of Dogwood Lane, she loitered unobtrusively until she was sure none of her neighbors had their windows open. She stole up the steps to her apartment and fit the rarely used key into the dusty lock with difficulty. Finally, she shut the door behind her and sank to the floor.

Her head came to rest against her knees, and she took several long breaths. Part of her had trouble accepting that she'd actually made it. The rest of her had been stuck on a loop since the lights of Hogwarts fell away beneath her.

It was over.

Everything was over.

And yet—there was still work to do.

Harry dragged herself upright. The food went to the cupboards, a couple pieces of fruit artfully displayed on the counter. She pulled down a dish and placed it in the sink as though dirty.

In the bedroom she dug out a set of clothes Flint's mother had left behind. Relieved that she wouldn't have to conjure anything, she started the shower in the bathroom and shucked the filthy garments from her back as the pipes groaned. She Vanished them as they hit the floor. It stung to lose the jersey the twins had given her, the gloves from Blaise, and Edmund and Aldon's cloak, but that small pain was barely a breeze in the hurricane of hurt that was her heart. Nearly everything she wore as Rigel had to go.

She took the beacon from her ear and what was left of the amulet from around her neck, carefully placing them in her bag with the other items she couldn't bear to destroy. Draco's gauntlets went in there, too, nested with the Invisibility Cloak, Map, and mirror. The watch from Archie. Her wand. All of it would be wrapped in mokeskin, hidden away until the world no longer searched for Rigel Black.

Harry sank to her knees on the bathroom floor, a boot in each hand. She knew she had to, but…

Are you crying over your shoes?

Shut up, Dom.

She shook the tears from her cheeks and Vanished them both ruthlessly. Her fingers closed over air and she drew another long breath. She was just tired, that was all. She'd get a new pair of boots, a set untainted by Rigel's history.

The steam was visible in the air, so she pushed herself upright again and stepped gingerly into the spray. The water swept over her, erasing the last vestiges of Rigel from her skin. The sweat, blood, and tears of four long years circled the drain almost indifferently. Sharp stinging drew her attention to every scrape and gash, and though she didn't recognize the body she inhabited, she healed it carefully.

She left the shower's thrall after she fell asleep standing up.

Mrs. Flint's clothes didn't fit perfectly, but they were close enough to resize. She ran her fingers through her hair compulsively, eyeing the fogged-over mirror with trepidation. She couldn't avoid her reflection forever.

Her hand slid through the condensation smoothly, and Harriett Potter looked back at her, a girl caught unaware. Her eyes. Had they always been so bright? Against a bloodshot-red backdrop, her natural green looked as vibrant as an emerald.

Her mother's bone structure peeked out from beneath soft cheeks, and a full lower lip gave her a somewhat dissatisfied moue. No one could mistake this girl for a boy. She supposed that was good, all things considered.

Her fingers went to work on the tangles in her hair—the same length but so much curlier, now. She was no hairdresser, but she flipped the part to the opposite side and coaxed the tiniest of growing charms into the tresses to try and cover the way some of it had been sheared. It flopped into her face annoyingly, and for a brief moment she wished Pansy was there to plait it back. The girl in the mirror pressed her lips together. Pansy would never touch her hair again.

Harry hefted her potions kit and took it to the living room to re-pack. Everything associated with Rigel went in a mokeskin wrapping at the very bottom of an undetectably extended pocket, and she re-organized the rest of the bag almost automatically. While she was at it, she pulled out a handful of ingredients for a basic strengthening brew and set them on the coffee table.

She had a couple of cauldrons in the cupboard. It took no time at all to set one up in the living room and toss together the base of the potion. With a timer set to the second stage, she curled up on the sofa and sank into its lulling embrace. She could afford a few hours' rest. Maybe there were things she was forgetting, but her brain was too knackered to hold out any longer.

Sleep was what she needed. Everything else could wait.

The front door slamming into its jamb startled her from a dead sleep. Harry tried to summon her wand blearily before she remembered it was packed away in mokeskin. She pushed the hair out of her face and froze at the sight of her father silhouetted in righteous anger on her doorstep.

"What's—Dad?" she made a show of stumbling upright, checking the still-simmering cauldron out of the corner of her eye as she stepped toward James uncertainly. The surprise was real, at least—he'd found her much more quickly than she anticipated. She spotted Archie and Sirius on the stairs behind James and allowed her face to fall. "Oh, shite."

"Harry?" James stared, some of the wind seeming to have escaped his sails at the sight of her. His eyes traced her face, got stuck on her eyes, and finally blinked hard. "What does Lily crave when she's pregnant?"

"Ice mice."

James released a long breath and ducked into the small flat. "Thank Godric."

"What's happened?" she looked to Archie, whose expression of utter guilt and misery meant he'd at least partially confessed to the ruse.

Her cousin summoned a grimace as he and Sirius crowded into the living room. "You didn't even watch the task?"

"Can't be seen out of school," she muttered, eyes tightening. "Is Rigel okay?"

"He's gone," Archie said, widening his eyes as though he couldn't quite believe it. Maybe he couldn't—Harry was definitely still processing all that had occurred.

"Gone? What do you mean—"

"Enough. We are not here to chat, Harry." James leveled his Auror-look at her, and Harry affected an appropriately chagrined expression in return. "What in the seven hells is going on? Why are you here and not at school?"

She glanced at Archie, who tucked his chin in the barest of nods. "I've always been here. Since first year."

Sirius made a startled noise. "That long? I thought it was just for the tournament."

Archie shook his head slowly. "We switched before leaving for school, four years ago."

"So all the letters I wrote…" Sirius was pale, his tone just a hair short of accusatory.

Archie's face crumpled with grief. "Rigel always forwarded them to me. But anything about being at Hogwarts…was a lie."

"We've both been lying," Harry offered, trying to take the mountain of guilt from Archie's shoulders. "To all of you. I'm sorry for the lying, but I can't say I'm sorry to have let Archie take my place at AIM."

James scoffed. "I'm sure you had a grand time skiving, Harry, but schools exist for a reason; there are things you have to learn, no matter how much you don't want to—"

"I've learned plenty," she shot back, the picture of offended youth. "I'm years ahead of my peers in coursework."

"You think I'm upset about the coursework?" James gestured to the apartment with an exasperated scowl. "Harry, you're living in the lower alleys. Four years with no supervision—do you have any idea what might have happened?"

"I'm fine though, Dad. Nothing happened."

"Fine. You're fine." He repeated the word as though it was stuck in his teeth. "Well, the rest of us aren't fine. Nothing is fine, Harry, because there's an international manhunt and our family is about to be caught in the crosshairs—"

"Prongs." Sirius put a hand on James' shoulder and waited until his friend had visibly calmed before turning to Harry and Archie and asking, "Who was going to Hogwarts in Archie's place?" He leveled them with an earnest stare. "It's important that we know. This is bigger than you probably understand right now."

Harry creased her forehead in a perplexed frown. "He said it was better if we didn't know his name."

"He approached you?" James asked sharply.

"Well, Archie met him at Junior Quidditch League the spring before school…"

Archie picked up the thread of the story with a nod. "Yeah, we were in the medic tent together. I had to get my arm patched up, and he was icing his shoulder. We got to talking about schools, and he was envious that I got to go to a school like Hogwarts. Said his family had fallen on hard times and couldn't afford to send him to their ancestral school, so he was being homeschooled. I felt bad for him, but didn't really think much of it. Then…"

"It was my idea," Harry confessed. "I didn't want to go to AIM. Their potions program is garbage. I knew I could learn more on my own. Archie did want to go to AIM, though. But people would notice if he never showed up at Hogwarts. So, I thought, what if there was someone who wanted to go to Hogwarts, but couldn't?"

"And I remembered that other kid!" Archie put in. "I found him at the next match and just asked him point-blank if he wanted to go to Hogwarts. And he said yes."

Sirius and James exchanged disbelieving looks. "You just asked some random kid you met at the International Quidditch League to pretend to be you for four years?"

"Seven years," Harry said, diplomatically ignoring the way her father's face darkened.

"And yeah, pretty much. I mean, at first we weren't taking it too seriously." Archie rubbed his neck sheepishly. "We exchanged letters, and it was almost like a game. We talked and talked about it, until it just…didn't seem so crazy. By the end of the summer, when I couldn't convince you to let me go with Harry, we just…did it."

"What address did you send the letters to? What name did you use?" James ticked the questions off his fingers. "What team was he playing for? What—"

"All right, Uncle James, slow down," Archie said. "Let me think. When we met, I think he said his name was Romeo? Romello? Something with an R—that's why it was easier for him to use my middle name. We didn't use real names in our letters, though."

"He was Rook," Rigel supplied.

Archie nodded. "I was Knight and you were…Bishop? Yeah. We used post office addresses. Harry would pick up and mail our letters from the Diagon Alley post when she went to the apothecary."

"We sent his to the post office in Paris, but it took weeks to get an answer sometimes—I'm not sure he lived near there at all." She said it thoughtfully, as though she hadn't considered the matter very carefully before.

"So he played for one of the French teams?" James clarified. He had a notebook out and had jotted down every detail they relayed.

Archie scrunched up his face. "I…maybe? Which one had a big cat as a mascot? A tiger, or maybe a lion? Or maybe the team was from Lyon? It was definitely blue and white. Or blue and yellow. I think."

"Was he in your age bracket?" Sirius asked. He had a suspicious glint in his eye.

They exchanged a bemused glance. Archie shook his head. "No, I think he was at least one above me."

"He was definitely older," Harry confirmed. She pretended not to notice the way Sirius' face hardened.

James dutifully wrote it down. "Did he have an accent?"

"A slight one, maybe, but by the time we met again to make the switch, I think it was gone. I don't remember it very well, though. It was so long ago," Archie said mournfully. "We never thought it would go so far, but once we did it, there was really no turning back…"

Harry drew their attention with an earnest sigh. "We thought it was the perfect solution. You'd think Archie was at Hogwarts, that I was at AIM, and we all got what we wanted. What was the harm?"

"He was a halfblood," James growled.

She froze. Her eyes darted between the two adults frantically. "Oh."

Archie paled several shades, and she wondered if he'd used his metamorphism to make it so dramatic. "That's…"

"Neglected to mention that, did he?"

Harry winced. "Did they arrest him?"

"He ran."

She winced again. "I am starting to appreciate the amount of trouble we're in."

"Welcome to the program. Get your things."

Harry blinked. She looked over at her potion. "Can I just—"

The cauldron exploded. Archie yelped and Harry shielded just in time to avoid singing. James regained control of his magic with an audible growl and Harry frowned reproachfully as the potion seeped over the floorboards.

"I've got downstairs neighbors, Dad," she muttered, Vanishing the mess with a wave of her hand.

"You use magic outside of school, too? Do you have wards up?" James asked gruffly.

"Technically, I'm enrolled in a correspondence course, so I can just say I'm practicing."

"Right. Is this grate connected?"

James started toward the Floo. As he was reaching for the powder pot, a knock came at the door. Harry hurried to answer it before her father or uncle could. It was Mrs. Botting.

"All right, Harry? Heard some shouting, and then it sounded like some crockery might have been dropped." The woman eyed James' Auror robes suspiciously.

"Everything's fine, Mrs. Botting. My…family found out I haven't been at proper school all this time like I said." She widened her eyes as she said it, and hoped the woman would understand. "They've just come to take me home."

Her eyes flitted from James to Harry and back, calculating. "I see. I'll just lock up for you then…?" She gestured vaguely toward the door, but two of her fingers crossed in a question.

Trouble?

"Thank you, ma'am," Harry said with a polite smile. "Sorry to disturb you." As she turned toward the Floo with the others, she made a thief sign behind her back.

All is well.

How true that turned out to be remained to be seen.

James marched them into the living room like prisoners of war. They didn't need pillories around their necks to hang their heads at the sight of Lily and Remus' shocked and concerned faces.

"Archie! You're—Harry? Why do you look so…?" Lily reached out a tentative hand toward Harry's face.

"Where did you find him? With Harry?" Remus asked. He took Archie in a hard embrace. "We were worried sick, son."

"I'm sorry," Archie said into his uncle's robes.

"We're both sorry," Harry added, nudged by her father.

"You look like Lily," Remus said wonderingly, getting a proper look at her new features. "But we just saw you a few months ago…"

"That was me," Archie muttered.

"I've…always looked like this." Harry glanced between Lily and Remus, guilt eating a hole in her stomach. Somehow, confessing to them was exponentially worse than James and Sirius.

"What do you mean?" Lily demanded, a frown beginning to trace its way across her lovely brow.

James cleared his throat pointedly, and Archie sent her a pleading glance. Harry withheld a sigh. It was on her, then. "The last four years, Archie and I have been involved in something…unwise. We did a dangerous thing, and what's worse—we lied to you all about it. Mum, I never went to AIM. I let Archie take my place there, so I could focus on my potions."

"She's been living in Knockturn Alley," James cut in.

Lily's lips parted on a sharp inhale, and Harry shot her father a scowl. "Not on Knockturn. I live in a perfectly respectable neighborhood south of the alleys."

Remus set his mouth in a hard line, and she could tell exactly what he was thinking—that he'd kept a bigger secret for her than he intended.

Her mother was only able to blurt one question. "But what about your O.W.L.s?"

Harry shifted uncomfortably. "I can still take them. I'm enrolled in the—"

"—correspondence course." Lily's face settled into understanding. "Oh, Harry. That's no equal to a real education."

"That's all you have to say?" Sirius exclaimed. "Lils, our children have been living an elaborate charade right in front of our eyes for years. Archie's never even set foot in Hogwarts."

"I did go to the Yule Ball as Harry," Archie corrected him.

"You—what?" Sirius was easily de-railed. "But how…" He gestured to Archie's rather masculine physique and spluttered, "Polyjuice?"

"Only I had to take Polyjuice," Harry said.

"You both changed your appearance to match Rigel's?" James consulted his notebook with a frown.

"Who is Rigel? Not Archie, I take it." Remus rubbed his temple.

"A kid we met at the Junior Quidditch League." Harry withstood Remus' disbelieving stare with guileless alacrity. "He wanted to go to Hogwarts, and that was exactly what we needed for our plan to work."

"How convenient," Remus said slowly.

"It did take some convincing," Archie admitted. "His was the most dangerous part of the ruse."

"The ruse?" Sirius snorted. "Think a lot of your little lie, don't you?"

"It snowballed into a capital-R Ruse rather quickly, Dad."

"Of course it did," Lily said. Her eyes were lit with terrible calculation. "To fool even us for so long…Harry, I've seen you Heal. Did you learn that to keep the cover story intact?"

Harry nodded, surprised her mother had picked up on the logical consequences so swiftly.

Sirius was quick on the uptake, too. "I'm certain I overheard you speaking Parseltongue with the snakes, Arch. But that was something the other kid could do, or at least he claimed to…"

Archie flushed. "I was faking. I can't speak Parseltongue at all. After Rigel's defeat of the basilisk was widely known, I had no choice."

If anything, Sirius looked vaguely relieved. He clapped his hands together and let out a shout as the next realization hit. "And you were never sorted into Slytherin! In retrospect, it's so obvious."

Harry kept her mouth shut, and did not roll her eyes even a little bit.

"And you can't out-duel an Auror, either, I suppose?" Remus said quietly. His eyes flickered to Harry very briefly, and she could see the question forming in his eyes.

"Definitely not." Archie shook his head vigorously. "Harry and Rigel trained endlessly in the alleys over summer break, but I was at that internship—"

"The Healing internship," Sirius groaned.

"—so I couldn't practice with them."

"You met up with this kid over the holidays, too?" James asked, pen poised. He was using the others as a foil, Harry realized—the interrogation was still happening, only their guard was that much lower with Remus and Lily in the room.

"Sure, we had to switch pretty often," Archie confirmed. "All the events Rigel kept getting invited to, every time we went to or came home from school, plus meet-ups with Hermione…I don't even remember all the times we switched."

"But when did you physically switch?" Remus asked, consternated. "And we would have noticed you taking Polyjuice for weeks at a time…wouldn't we?" The uncertainty in his voice was reflected on all the adults' face, and it was like a cloud settling over the room.

Archie shifted his weight in the silence that followed. "My gift might be…slightly less passive than I let on." He closed his eyes, took a deep breath, and let his metamorphism go all at once.

It was Sirius' turn to gasp, and Harry winced to see his eyes well up in an instant. "You look…" He gulped, and took Archie's head in both his hands. "You have Diana's chin."

Archie burst into tears.

Addy wailed from the other room, evidently woken from her nap. Lily rushed to soothe the child, and James scrawled the word Metamorphmagus so hard into his notebook it scratched through to the next page.

"What about you, Harry?" Remus asked quietly. Sirius and Archie were stuck in an embrace, oblivious to anything but one another's pain.

"What about me?" she asked as Lily came back into the room with a sniffling toddler.

"How did we not notice you taking Polyjuice for four summers? And why would you have to change appearance at all?" Remus fixed her with a hard look. "If you were mostly out of the picture, surely Archie's morphing would have been enough to cover for this other boy at events."

Harry held her face impassive, but silently cursed Remus' perceptive nature. "At first, we were worried someone who knew Archie in America but lived in Britain would see a picture of me or run into Archie at the airport with my parents and figure out something was up. Best if I looked however Archie looked at school, which means the easiest way was to have just one face, and three people."

"Easiest," Remus repeated, unconvinced. "And the Polyjuice?"

He really wasn't going to let that one go. "I improved the recipe," Harry said. "My version lasts as long as I want it to."

"Harriett Potter, do not tell me you're dosing yourself with experimental Potions again." Lily shot her a massively disapproving look over Addy's head.

"It's perfectly safe." As far as she knew. "I didn't use it to change my biological sex, anyway."

"Oh." Mollified, Lily nodded. "It does sound as though you considered the potential ramifications, then."

"Does it?" James skewered them all with a glare. "When you're all done being impressed with our junior criminals, can we discuss the particular ramifications I'm concerned with?"

"We didn't know he wasn't a pureblood," Archie said earnestly. "They can't really charge us with aiding and abetting, can they?"

"Whether they can or can't remains to be seen, but you must believe they are going to try, Archie. The Minister is not pleased. Riddle is fit to be tied, and the international community is in an absolute uproar." James started to pace, but Lily put a hand on his arm.

"They couldn't have predicted this," she said quietly. "I don't condone it. But I…well, how many of us dreamed of a different path? If someone had offered me a seat at Hogwarts when I was eleven, even if I had to change myself drastically…I'm not sure I wouldn't have done it."

James gave her a betrayed look. Lily lifted her lips in a small smile.

"You couldn't really understand, Darling. It was never in doubt for you."

Harry had never felt closer to her mother than in that moment, as she forgave a boy who didn't exist.

"And anyway, Harry didn't do anything," Archie insisted. "I'm the only one who officially abetted him. Harry just…homeschooled herself and lied to her parents."

"Which I feel terrible about," Harry added.

"Me, too." Archie turned to Sirius, who couldn't seem to stop tracing his features with bright eyes. "Dad, it was horrible lying to you, but I had to follow my heart. I know I'm meant to be a Healer."

Remus stifled an incredulous chuckle and breathed, "You really do get the children you raise."

Sirius raised an eyebrow at his friend. "And what's your excuse, werewolf? You were at school with this other kid for a whole year."

Remus' smile dropped. "You're right, but…he smelled like Archie."

A spark of slyness kindled in Archie's eyes. "Fooled you, huh?"

"He sounded like you, too," Remus muttered, eyes narrowed.

"We made a perfume of Archie's sweat and mailed it to him," Harry explained.

James put his head in his hands and shook it slowly back and forth. Sirius just snorted. "Remus, you useless pile of fur—did you think he never showered?"

"He's a teenager." Remus' ears turned pink and he crossed his arms. "I'm never going to live this down."

"Anyone would be fooled by one of Harry's concoctions, Uncle Remus. She's a genius."

"You'd both better hope you're as smart as you think," James said flatly. He pulled out his pocket watch and grimaced. "I can't delay any longer, Arch. I have to take you to the Ministry before the search for the missing Black Heir gets out of hand."

"The Prophet says they've posted pictures of Rigel all across Scotland," Lily relayed.

Harry frowned. "Why would they expect him to stay there?"

Her mother gave her a patient look. "He's fourteen. Young wizards can manage perhaps a few miles at a time, but not as many consecutive jumps as would be needed to get as far as Northern Ireland or Northumberland in less than a day."

"He burned a lot of magic in the maze, too," Remus said thoughtfully. "Not to mention what happened after."

Had she? Harry couldn't recall doing anything too strenuous in the maze itself, and while the wards had been grounded strongly, she'd felt the anchor loose even as she pulled on them.

Archie sent her a hard-to-read look. She dropped her gaze in the facsimile of a nod. It wouldn't do them any good to have the search for Rigel Black happening close to home.

"You shouldn't underestimate him." Archie said firmly. "For one, he's not fourteen—he may even be fully of age for all we know."

"And he's known he might have to run for years," Harry added. "To think he'd have no escape plan…I wouldn't make that assumption."

James' face hardened. "You're saying he could be anywhere. Kids, now is not the time to try and protect this person—"

"We're just saying if you ignore everything he's done over the last four years, you'll never find him." Archie looked between the adults with perfect consternation on his face. "This is the guy who slew a basilisk. He faced down a dragon, out-dueled half a dozen rivals—for Merlin's sake, Dad said he tore down the Founders' wards!"

"He what?" Harry tried to turn her alarm into detached amazement, but wasn't sure how well she succeeded if the warning flash in Archie's eyes was any indication.

"Dumbledore had unraveled the lodestone already." James had a far-away look in his eyes. "Still, it was no small feat. I'd assumed he was running on fumes when we lost his trail, but…perhaps we'll distribute those posters a bit further afield."

"Not that there's anyone in the world who doesn't know what he looks like," Sirius put in helpfully. "Really, you're just advertising the fact that he's wanted."

"Poor boy," Lily murmured, holding Addy close. "He'll never know a moment's peace."

"He'll lie low for a while, then change his name," Remus predicted.

"And his face?"

"There are plenty of ways." Sirius clamped a hand down on his son's shoulder and his smile became slightly sharp. "These two figured that out."

They both winced. Archie put a hand up to grasp Sirius' briefly, taking a long breath and letting it out slowly. "We should go, Uncle James."

James nodded, and Harry looked at her father carefully. "Just Archie?"

"He's the only one I have proof committed a crime, so, yes."

"Will I be able to go back to school after?" Archie asked.

"Let's focus on keeping you out of prison, first."

Archie stepped toward the Floo room, Sirius a beat behind him. James looked for a moment as though he would argue, but whatever he saw in Sirius' face dissuaded him. Harry tried not to worry too much.

She had faith in Archie. He already had plausible deniability going for him, and the protection of his blood wasn't nothing. All he had to do was stick to their story.

In their absence, Remus and Lily turned their attention to her in one coordinated movement, and she abruptly realized her own interrogation was just beginning.

His head hadn't stopped spinning since Uncle James burst into his exam room and everything fell to pieces.

Pre-determined pieces, like glass that had been carefully scored, but pieces all the same.

Merlin bless Harriett Potter. He didn't know how she'd done it—how she'd slipped the security perimeter around Hogwarts, how she'd even survived what sounded like a harrowing disaster of a final task with her magic intact—but she did. There she was napping, perfectly blasé, when they descended on her place in the alleys.

Everything Harry did seemed impossibly effortless. Even Archie couldn't see the ghosts in her eyes anymore.

The Floo didn't help matters in his head. He stumbled out of the grate and opened his eyes—only the slam them shut again as a dozen cameras flashed in his face. A hand came down hard on his shoulder and steered him forward; Archie felt his feet move automatically as the spots in his vision receded.

Reporters. They must have recognized Uncle James when he came through.

"Auror Potter, can you comment?"

"Are you heading the investigation into the Rigel Black Case?"

"Is this the imposter?"

Sirius spoke loudly over the clamoring crowd in the Ministry lobby. "This is my son, Arcturus Black, and he is not available for comment."

Cameras flashed again, and Archie did his best not to vomit.

"Were you too afraid to fight in the tournament, son?"

"Is the Black Heir under arrest, Auror Potter?"

Uncle James pushed through the throng and pitched his voice in a tone that brooked no argument. "Make way, people. We have a lot of paperwork to do today."

Astonishingly, the wry remark gained a smattering of chuckles. As the reporters cleared a path for James, Archie realized they liked him. He didn't think reporters liked anyone.

"Does he know where Rigel Black is?"

"How long did this impersonation last?"

Sirius steered him quickly toward the lifts, and Archie felt his hands unclench as the doors closed between them and the story-hungry journalists. Uncle James tapped his foot restlessly as the dial crawled toward Level 2.

"Have they been waiting here all night?" Archie asked quietly.

"Most likely," James confirmed. With a sideways look, he added. "This isn't just some schoolboy hijinks, Arch. What that boy did—what you helped him do—is going to ripple through our world for years."

Archie blinked the moisture back from his eyes. "We didn't set out to change the world," he whispered.

"What you intended no longer matters."

The lift chimed and a woman's voice droned, "Department of Magical Law Enforcement."

James stepped off with surety, Sirius and Archie behind him. Down the long hallway, through the heavy oak doors into the Auror Department talent pool. Heads craned from every cubicle they passed, but no one dared to call out when they caught the look on their boss's face.

"Webber."

A round-faced young man popped up from the cubical at the end of the row like a startled meerkat. "Yes, sir."

"Coffee."

The young Auror—trainee, by the cut of his robes—scrambled to the break room. James started for his office, but the door swung outward before he reached it.

A grizzled Auror with piercing blue eyes and a suspicious expression stepped out, closely followed by a man Archie recognized easily—the Minister of Magic.

"Potter! Did you catch him?" Fudge peered around James with a calculating squint. Archie held very still, even as he felt Sirius bristle behind him like a cornered canine.

"No, Minister." James' voice was firm and quiet, as though he didn't know every Auror in the pit held their breath to better hear. "The boy who impersonated my nephew is still at large."

"Still at—who's this then? A classmate? Does he know something?" Fudge's voice rose with each question, audibly impatient.

James took one step to the side and fixed Archie with a stare that said I'm not going to make this easy for you.

Archie cleared his throat and lifted his chin. "I am the real Arcturus Black, Minister."

Fudge looked between Archie and Sirius for a long moment. "Ah. I do see the resemblance. At least one person has been found today. Quite confident this is the real one, are you?"

Archie could hear his father's teeth creak.

"We're certain, Minister," James said. "If you'll excuse us, Mr. Black has a number of questions to answer."

The Minister spluttered. "But surely you're not going to interrogate him yourself, Potter!" He looked around at the grizzled Auror and the young trainee who hovered awkwardly with a steaming mug. "Isn't that a conflict of interest?"

James set his jaw, but bowed his head ever-so-slightly. "Indeed. I am merely his escort."

"James—" Sirius began. A sharp gesture cut him off.

"The Minister is correct, Sirius. It would be entirely inappropriate for me to participate in questioning. Moody, can you spare an hour?"

Auror Moody's gaze could have flayed mutton. "I have real Dark Wizards to hunt." He stalked past their group with one last, dismissive look in Archie's direction. "Shame about the other kid. He was really something."

Archie tried not to take that comment personally.

James claimed his coffee and took a long swig while the relieved trainee slunk back to his desk. He pivoted sharply and caught sight of someone too slow in ducking. "Shacklebolt! Get your shiny head over here."

A broad-shouldered Auror with a gold hoop in one ear rose from his cubicle unhurriedly. When he spoke, it was in a low, measured tone. "Yes, sir?"

"Interrogation room three, fifteen minutes."

Shacklebolt tilted his head agreeably. "Want me to book him?"

"I'll do it," James muttered.

Archie followed his uncle to a room down the hall, where he was somewhat unceremoniously searched and scanned. All the while, James intoned a long list of warnings and caveats that Archie didn't fully understand. He felt a bit dazed by the surrealness of the experience. Often, he had imagined it all going wrong—he pictured himself in Azkaban, sometimes, cold and afraid—but this brusque, barely human interaction with his own uncle was in some ways stranger.

"—can use anything you say against you, against Rigel, and against anyone else implicated—"

His wand went into a box along with his spare testing quill.

"—does not amount to suspension of your right to self-defense or council—"

His school uniform was swapped for a plain set of grey utility robes.

"—use of Veritaserum on minors is strictly prohibited, but a written statement on spelled parchment will be—"

"Uncle James, am I going home?" Archie interrupted, clenching his toes in the too-big shoes he was issued.

"Of course you are," Sirius said fiercely.

James did not agree right away. "If Auror Shacklebolt finds no reason to detain you."

If he didn't confess to an imprisonable offense, in other words.

Archie nodded. James signed his name to the paperwork he was filling out with an angry flourish. "Sirius, fill out the rest of the demographics while you wait."

"Wait?" Sirius clutched Archie's shoulders in both hands.

James shook his head slowly. "He has to do this part alone, Sirius. If there's any hint of nepotism, he'll never shake this."

Archie pulled free of his father's embrace. "Uncle James is right, Dad. I have to answer for this."

Sirius took a deep breath. Then another. Then a shorter one, a faster one, and the next thing Archie knew his father was hyperventilating and James was half-supporting him.

"I—I can't—"

"Sirius, breathe."

"Dad!" Archie dove for his wand and pushed his magic into his father's airways without permission. It was the simplest thing to convert excess oxygen to carbon dioxide. Less simple was facing the devastating fear in his father's eyes.

"I c-can't lose you, Arch," Sirius wheezed.

Archie hugged his father hard and swallowed back his tears. "You won't, Dad. I promise. I swear it." He brushed his father's hair back from his face and looked straight into his eyes. "I won't let them take me away, Dad. If they find me guilty, we'll flee the country. Even if they put me in Azkaban, I'll escape."

"No one…escapes Azkaban," Sirius whispered shakily. He clung to Archie weakly.

"I will. I'll use my animagus form and slip right through the bars," Archie said wildly. He would say anything to bring the life back into his father's eyes.

"I'm not hearing this," James muttered. He took Archie's wand away from him and ran a hand through his hair. "Sirius, I'm sorry, but we can't delay much longer. If you require a sedative, I'll—"

"He's fine." Archie shook his father gently by the shoulders. "Aren't you, Dad? We're fine, aren't we? I don't want to you worry. I got myself into this, and I can get myself out."

He tried to sound more confident than he felt. Sirius was shaking his head back and forth mutely, but he was also breathing normally once more.

"It's gonna be okay, Dad. I promise. I'll come home to you and Harry and Remus and everyone. You can ground me for a whole month, all right?"

"A year," Sirius muttered.

"We can talk about it later," Archie said, relieved when that drew a small laugh from his father.

When James was certain that Sirius would be able to compose himself, he opened the door. "This way, Archie."

Archie kept his father's gaze until they left the room. Uncle James took him to a door with a tinted window set into the face. He paused with a hand on the knob and said quietly, "Be respectful. Listen carefully. Don't elaborate unless pressed and don't let yourself become emotional."

Archie nodded, though privately he suspected it was too late for the last bit.

James turned him over without a word, and Shacklebolt gestured to the thin, metal chair across from him with an unreadable expression.

He sat, and immediately noticed the seat was sloped in such a way to prevent comfort of any kind. Shacklebolt opened a slim, blue folder and began to peruse the papers within. The text was too small for Archie to read, but he could tell it had been penned recently—some of the ink shill shone dully in the torchlight.

Shacklebolt reviewed the folder leisurely, at times making a noise of surprise or interest. When he finished the last page, the Auror leaned back in his chair—a much sturdier construction of cushioned wood—and regarded Archie silently.

When he could take no more of the quiet, Archie said, "Aren't you going to ask me questions?"

"Is there anything you'd like to tell me, first?"

Archie clamped his mouth shut. Uncle James had just told him to listen, not talk.

Shacklebolt shrugged his big shoulders. "Well, that's all right. Not much to say, is there? The chain of events seems pretty clear."

Archie frowned uncertainly. "Er, does it?"

Shacklebolt folded his hands on the table and looked at Archie frankly. "Got in over your head, I'd say. It started off as an easy lark; just a couple of schoolboys switching places, right? You got an American holiday, and this other kid got to attend the most prestigious magical school in the West. I imagine you weren't thinking about it in the terms they're bandying about now—blood theft, capital crimes, and all that." He paused, and peered at Archie curiously.

Archie shook his head slowly. He didn't like that characterization of their ruse, exactly, but he tried to repeat Uncle James' advice in his head and not protest.

"No, of course not. What does a boy know of blood politics?" Shacklebolt tapped his long fingers on the desk idly. "You just wanted to go your own way. Make a path in this world on your own terms. It's a heady thing…and I suppose it spun out of control at some point."

Archie nodded, then caught the sharp glint in Shacklebolt's steady gaze. "I…what exactly is your question?"

"No question, really," Shacklebolt said. His voice was impossibly smooth, too reassuring to make any sense in the situation. "I'm just trying to understand what happened. We all want to understand, you see?"

He hesitated. What was he supposed to say? Be respectful, James had said. "I'm sure it's confusing. How can I help clarify matters?"

Shacklebolt raised his eyebrows. "Well, you might want to clarify just how long this charade of yours went on. There is some speculation that you chickened out of the tournament and paid this less privileged boy to brave the dangers in your place, but I don't believe that." Shacklebolt leaned in, a bit conspiratorially. "For one, you don't look anything like the boy who competed in the tournament. Since not one of his friends seems to have suspected a switch, I'm thinking you've never been to Hogwarts."

"That's correct. I never attended Hogwarts," Archie said carefully. "Four years ago, I went to America and let another kid take my place there."

Shacklebolt clapped his hands together. "That explains it. The boy who participated in the tournament was there at Hogwarts all along—of course his friends didn't notice anything different."

"Of course," Archie agreed.

"But then—it is devilishly odd that your father never noticed this boy wasn't you." Shacklebolt spread his fingers somewhat apologetically. "As we've established—you don't really look like him."

Archie took a deep breath. "Am I allowed to do magic in here?"

Shacklebolt frowned. "Your wand should have been confiscated."

"I don't need one for this, and it'll make more sense if I show you."

The Auror palmed his own wand, then gestured cautiously for Archie to proceed. Archie slipped into Rigel's face easily, like an old hat perfectly molded to his head. He tilted his head to different angles, then let the change drop away.

Shacklebolt slowly took out a quill and make several notes in the blue folder. "That is most enlightening, Mr. Black. Thank you."

Archie felt an easing in his chest and tensed against it. Too reassuring, he reminded himself.

Shacklebolt smiled with perfect teeth at him. "I was worried we might have to charge you with use of a controlled substance, but I see that Polyjuice would not have been necessary for you. I suppose only your co-conspirator will have to face that charge."

Archie gulped.

The Auror went on somewhat blithely. "That is the case with many of these charges, of course. You'll both have to answer for academic fraud, but with a little plausible deniability, that is where your part in it will end. Rigel alone will face the blowback for blood identity theft, conspiracy to defraud an international competition, four years of controlled substance abuse—"

"We knew the risks," Archie snapped. He didn't need to be reminded how much greater Harry's risk had been. He lived with the knowledge every day.

Shacklebolt made a noise of understanding. "It was premeditated, then. I didn't realize you were both fully aware of the laws regarding the impersonation of pureblooded wizards by those of inferior birth."

Archie winced. "I didn't say that."

"I'm not sure what you're trying to say, then."

"I just meant—Rigel must have known. It didn't occur to me that blood was something to worry about." He tried to channel the dismissive privilege Shacklebolt had all but accused him of. "I wanted to go to school in America, but Dad wouldn't let me. So I found a kid who wanted to go to Hogwarts and we switched. All this other stuff…how could I have known if he was a halfblood?"

Shacklebolt did not look impressed. "Simple logic might suggest that this boy would not have pretended to be you if he could go to Hogwarts as himself. You must have been aware that halfbloods are prohibited from attending the school."

"I suppose I knew that rule, but it didn't affect me, so I didn't pay it much mind." Archie shrugged. "I was selfish. I know that. It's not like I forced Rigel to take my place, though. And since I didn't know he was a halfblood, my only crime was ignorance."

"And also the academic fraud."

"Right. I'll admit to that."

Shacklebolt sighed. "If that's the story you want to stick to, fine, but understand the position we're in: whether you knew it or not, you helped a halfblood pose as a pureblood in an international competition specifically designed to challenge the merits of blood discrimination. If this was just about the schooling, Hogwarts would handle it internally. If he'd made a fool of people less powerful, Rigel might have been able to disappear quietly and move on with his life." Shacklebolt shook his head solemnly. "We're far beyond that now, son."

Archie put his head in his hands. "Rigel didn't even want to participate in that stupid tournament. Riddle near well forced him—"

"Regardless of how it happened, it happened," Shacklebolt said smoothly. "All that matters now is straightening it out. For that, we need to talk to Rigel."

Archie stiffened. "I don't know where—"

"Now, now, no need to say something you'll regret. Here's the thing." Shacklebolt ticked the points off his fingers slowly. "This impersonation of yours was nearly perfect—that takes a lot of coordination and planning, doesn't it? Add to that an escape so smooth we still have no idea where this kid went. You, a wealthy scion of a powerful family, dozens of resources at your fingertips. Him, a halfblood with no name and no one to miss him for four years. You'll understand if I think it's unlikely you had no hand in his exit strategy."

His lips were pressed so tightly together they ached.

Shacklebolt tapped the folder, his expression openly sympathetic. "Look, I understand this is a lot. Your uncle says you're a good kid. I know you got top grades at that American school. We ran an à priori diagnostic on your wand—three dozen spells back, all very advanced Light magic. You're a good person, Mr. Black. I don't think you want to be mixed up in this. You made a mistake, and that's okay. Just help us get to the bottom of this."

Archie stared at the table, not moving a muscle.

"It's like you said," Shacklebolt went on in that even, cajoling tone. "He knew the risks. He knew he was halfblooded, even if you didn't, and he chose to impersonate you anyway. Maybe he told you a sad story about not being able to afford schooling. And you helped him out. What do you really owe him? We just want the truth, son. No more lies. That's what you want, too, isn't it? When we find him, we can get all this straightened out."

It might have worked, if it really had been some kid from the Continent. Just some boy he didn't know very well, who'd been a means to an end but not a true friend.

But it was Harry. And he would never.

His hands shook, but his voice didn't. "I'm sorry, sir, but I won't be able to help you."

Shacklebolt opened his mouth, but the door to the interrogation room opened with a wrenching creak and a skinny redhead with a sternness beyond his years strode through it.

Percy Weasley looked down his nose at Auror Shacklebolt and said in a disapproving clip, "Interrogating a minor without his guardian present? I expect better, Kingsley."

Shacklebolt waved a hand toward the left side of the room, and a ward Archie hadn't noticed dropped to reveal a broad panel of clear glass. Sirius, James, the Minister, and several others stood behind it, evidently having witnessed the entire proceeding. Archie felt both better and worse for it.

"Weasley. Come to rescue another poor soul from our evil clutches?" Shacklebolt tucked the papers back into the folder with leisurely resignation.

Percy produced a roll of parchment and passed it to Shacklebolt for his perusal. "My services have been secured for the defense of one Arcturus Rigel Black. Unless you have evidence of any crimes other than what he has already admitted to, I insist you release him into his family's custody."

Shacklebolt hummed. "We're only charging him with academic fraud."

"He'll be happy to pay the fines incurred," Percy said with a sniff.

"He still has to write a statement." Shacklebolt palmed his own roll of parchment and passed it across the table with a quill. "I suggest you include as much as you can, lest we think of any reason to call you back in."

"I hope you realize none of his answers today will be admissible in court," Percy said sharply. To Archie, he added, "They aren't allowed to question you without counsel, as you're underage."

"Answers?" Shacklebolt scratched his bald head with a lazy grin. "I didn't ask him any questions. This upstanding citizen provided information to the DMLE out of what I can only assume is a strong sense of civic duty." To a flummoxed Archie, he added, "I'm sure a guilty conscience had nothing to do with it."

Archie gaped at him. That wasn't right. Shacklebolt had asked him dozens of questions…hadn't he? The Auror saluted James through the glass and left the room whistling.

Archie's stomach turned over. What had he said? It was already hard to remember.

"Best write your statement quickly," Percy said quietly. "After that, we can go." With a glance toward the viewing window, he added, "It's truth parchment, mind. You can't write a lie."

His nerves utterly shot, Archie put quill to parchment and did his best to reiterate the truths—and steer clear of the lies.

I, Arcturus Rigel Black, do hereby affirm the following:

That I did knowingly defraud the American Institute of Magic by attending under a false name.

That I did knowingly allow another person to defraud Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry by attending in my name.

That I did not, at any time, question or inquire into the blood status of the person who impersonated me at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.

That I did not encourage my impostor to participate in the Triwizard Tournament.

That I did not help my impersonator escape Scotland following the tournament's conclusion.

That my father, Lord Sirius Black, had no knowledge of this impersonation.

That my adopted uncle, Lord James Potter, had no knowledge of this impersonation.

That I did not intend international embarrassment of the British magical community.

That I am sorry for all most of the trouble this plot has caused.

Apart from the burning away of one word in the final line, the statement held up against the runes designed to detect intentional falsehoods.

Sirius met him at the door. James took his statement, but it was snatched up by the Minister at once.

"What is the meaning of this? You haven't affirmed you don't know who Rigel Black is. Who is he!?"

"You do not have to answer," Percy said firmly.

Archie met the Minister's eyes with tired resignation. "Rigel Black could be anyone, Minister. That's kind of the point."

Fudge gaped at him. "Just what is that supposed to mean?"

Sirius squeezed his shoulder, but Archie couldn't bite his tongue any longer.

"A no-name halfblood just won an international tournament in Britain's name. The question is not 'who is Rigel Black' but rather, how many more Rigel Blacks are we missing out on?"

"That's quite enough," James said sharply. "Please excuse us, Minister. It's been a long day for everyone."

"Very long." Fudge muttered. "Positively lingering. Go home, then, and this time try to actually get some rest. Tell Moody I want a status report on the whereabouts of that Dark Voldiwart fellow by tomorrow morning."

"I'll tell him."

"And don't speak to The Prophet about this without me."

"No one in this office will engage the press."

"Good."

The Minister bustled out toward the lifts, and James ushered the rest of them into his personal office. Sirius enveloped Archie in a firm hug when the door was closed.

"You did good, kid."

"Shacklebolt tricked me," Archie mumbled into Sirius' robes.

"That's his job," James said. He didn't sound apologetic at all. "Percy, thank you for coming so quickly."

"I dropped everything when I got your message," Percy said quietly. "I'm only sorry I didn't get here sooner."

Archie half-turned from Sirius' hold to say, "You know I'm not Rigel, right?"

"I've been fully briefed on the situation."

"But why would you want to help? You don't know me," Archie said, letting his confusion show.

Percy adjusted his glasses fastidiously. "Helping you is the only way I can help him right now."

"You aren't…mad at him, or anything?" Archie asked.

"Rigel is a good person. Anyone who really knows him can't forget that." Percy's eyes grew distant as he added, "He always went out of his way to help people he didn't have to. I can do at least as much."

"Well, thank you. I—Dad, we can cover his rate or something, right?"

Percy cleared his throat sharply. "I won't hear of it. What Rigel has done will echo in the chambers of history. That I am even a small voice on the side of righteousness is his doing. Raising it in his favor is hardly a sacrifice. I only hope he is safe, and that he will remain so."

Archie grimaced guiltily, but Percy held up a hand.

"No, don't tell me. I cannot be party to any criminal activity."

"Nor can I," James grumbled.

Archie bit his lip and thought carefully before saying, "I have no way to know for certain…but I would bet that Rigel is just fine, wherever he is."

Percy smiled approvingly. "That's nice to imagine." He pulled a stack of papers from his briefcase and handed them to Sirius. "These are all the precedents I pulled for his defense. If he gets called in again or formally arrested, please Floo me posthaste."

"We will." Sirius clasped hands with the young redhead gratefully. "My best to your father."

"And our best to your family in these difficult times."

At the office door, Percy paused and said, "Fred and George would like Rigel to know that it's the most brilliant prank they've ever heard of. They cede the prank war indefinitely."

"I suppose, wherever he is, Rigel would just be gratified to have retained their friendship."

"A Weasley's friendship is not easily lost."

Percy left, and it was just the three of them once more. James took a long breath, then said. "I will finish the paperwork. Archie is officially being treated as a source, not a suspect, in the Rigel Black Case, and the separate charges against him for academic fraud will be settled when the fines are paid. You'll receive an official bill from the court sometime this week."

Sirius nodded. "James, I can't thank you enough—"

James waved him off. "Those words don't pass between us, Sirius. Archie's like my own son, you know that. I'm just relieved he and Harry are safe. As far as I'm concerned, we can conduct the rest of the investigation without them."

"So…we can go home, now?" Archie asked tentatively.

James fixed him with a hard stare. "Are you going to pick up paperwork from the Animagus Registration Office on the way out?"

"That is exactly what we were planning to do," Sirius said bracingly.

"Better get two sets," Archie muttered.

James rubbed his temple, opened the door to his office, and barked, "Webber!"

"Yes, sir?"

"Coffee." He held the door open and favored Sirius with a flat look. "Get your son home before I strangle him, Sirius."

His father's hand on his collar marched him out of the Auror pit without argument.

After a short detour at the Improper Use of Magic Office, they were able to sneak out the Floo closest to the lifts before the crowd of milling reporters spotted their exit. Archie stumbled back into the Potters' receiving room with his clothes and wand clutched tightly in his arms.

He could hear Harry talking loudly in the other room—arguing with Remus and Lily, who seemed to be firing questions in rapid succession. Archie rubbed his eyes tiredly, but manfully made his way to the living room to back her up.

"—depends on whether it was Vanished into a temporary spatial pocket or true Nonbeing." Harry was saying. She sounded more than a mite annoyed.

"And how can it be summoned back from true Nonbeing?" Remus demanded.

Harry scowled. "That's impossible, and you know it."

"All right, well how does that square with the Third Law of Recombobulation?" Lily asked sharply. Addy cooed uneasily up at her mother, but the redheaded witch was laser-focused on Harry's response.

"Mum, I know that's N.E.W.T. level. Aren't you satisfied yet?"

Lily and Remus exchanged disgruntled looks, and Archie gaped at them. All the while he was being grilled on the exact details of the blood identity theft, Harry was being questioned on her academics?

"I just can't believe you learned all of that on your own," Lily grumbled. "You didn't have any tutors?"

"I had all the correspondence course instructors," Harry said reprovingly. "I never realized you two were such private school snobs."

"Snobs?" Remus visibly balked at the descriptor. "Just because we know the value of a traditional education—"

"You assume the value of such an education can't be duplicated," Harry argued. "I don't know what you gain from arguing the un-substitutable nature of such old-fashioned institutions, anyway."

"That's not—"

Sirius interrupted Lily. "Are you really still on about Harry's schooling? She's clearly no worse off for it. Probably gained some street-smarts, too."

"Easy for you to say, Sirius. Your child still had the benefit of a well-rounded education in all this—"

"But not the benefit of a conferred degree," Archie put in glumly. "I'm going to have to take all those classes over again in my own name."

"You can test out of them, I bet," Harry offered.

Sirius turned to Archie slowly, a somewhat disbelieving look in his eyes. "We just averted a bloody prison sentence and your only concern is going back to that school?"

Archie felt his temper flare. "I did all this in the first place to go to 'that school,' Dad. It matters to me."

"Clearly. It mattered more than being honest for four years, didn't it? Mattered more than your cousin getting her education."

"Now hold on, you just said—"

"It must have mattered more than our relationship ever did, as you threw every ounce of my trust and good will away without a second thought, didn't you?"

His father's words slapped across his already bruised conscience and left their mark unerringly.

Archie's gaze fell to the floor, and he saw Harry's feet come to stand between them.

"I think you should get some rest, Uncle Sirius."

"And I think you've stood between my son and me long enough, Harriet Potter."

"Don't speak to her that way—"

"Someone has to get it through their thick skulls, Lily!" Sirius' magic flared and the lights flickered. Addy began to cry. "I'm relieved to have them safe—Godric knows I am. But what they've done has changed everything. There are things that cannot be undone. Someone has to make them understand."

"We do understand," Harry said firmly. Archie didn't know how she could speak at all; his tongue felt like lead in his mouth.

"Oh, you understand?" The sarcasm in Sirius' voice was sharp. "You understand that this country is on the verge of a blood war? You understand that there is discriminatory legislation being voted on in less than a month, and that this throws a giant, stinking dung bomb into the middle of hundreds of peoples' political machinations? Years of planning and compromise to bring a coalition of people together to defeat this bill. You understand that, Harry?"

Harry stood her ground. "Ignoring how hypocritical it is for you to lecture anyone about disrupting society's political calculations, Uncle Sirius, yes, we do understand that. None of us wanted Rigel to be found out—maintaining that neither Archie nor I knew he was even halfblooded—but on top of that, it's entirely because of this legislation that Rigel was in that dratted tournament in the first place. Don't you think it was unwise, for a boy with so many secrets to participate in something so high-profile and ridiculous?"

"I thought it was unwise for Archie to do it, much less a halfblood masquerading as him," Remus mused.

"Exactly." Archie looked up to see his cousin's face lit with indignant stubbornness as she went on. "Rigel didn't want to. Riddle blackmailed him into it, first by threatening our family—who Rigel has no reason to protect, by the way—and then using the possibility of victory as a political bargaining chip."

Lily turned white and Remus sat down abruptly in the nearest armchair.

"That boy got Riddle to agree to an Unbreakable Vow, Sirius. Because Rigel won the tournament, Riddle can never back a piece of discriminatory blood legislation related to employment, healthcare, or marriage ever again."

Sirius froze. "What…Riddle would never agree to that."

"He wanted Rigel to participate that badly," Harry said, her voice growing gentler as her words started to sink in. "And he thought Rigel winning would prove the point of pureblood supremacy anyway, and that he wouldn't need any more legislation after the marriage law. But now, don't you see? Rigel has upset the Light's political calculus, sure, but he's upset the Dark's even more. A halfblood won the Triwizard Tournament. Riddle is bound and his point will go unproven."

"Disproven, if anything," Archie added. Part of him realized he had yet to feel properly proud of Harry for that. She had won the Triwizard Tournament.

"If we beat this bill…it's the last," Lily said quietly. Wonderingly.

"The last backed by Riddle," Remus corrected her shrewdly. "His party can still introduce legislation."

"But they're hamstrung without his explicit support," Lily said, a smile beginning to form on her lips. "Sirius, sit down. Let's think about this. We must speak with Dumbledore, Augusta, and—I'm not even sure who will believe it."

Sirius shook his head, clenching his fists helplessly. "That's not…it doesn't excuse…"

"Just say why you're really angry, Uncle Sirius," Harry challenged.

Archie stepped around Harry to take his father's hand. "Dad, I know it doesn't change that we lied to you. I will spend the rest of my life making that up to you. Lying to you was the hardest part of it, and I am more sorry than I can say with words alone. I know Harry is, too."

"I am," Harry said impatiently. "But the guilt I feel doesn't mean we can ignore the wider consequences of our actions, including the potentially beneficial ones," Harry added, somewhat unhelpfully. "We're the ones who will be affected by this law if it passes. And we're the ones who just gave the Light its best chance at beating it. You can be mad at us forever, but the chance to beat Riddle is here now."

"She's right." Remus shook his head slowly as Sirius glared at him. "I know, Sirius, but…she's right. I was only thinking about Archie and the trouble he was in, but a halfblood did win the Triwizard Tournament. Not only that—he destroyed the competition. If we get behind this quick enough—"

"I can't hear this right now." Sirius pulled away from Archie, turned his back on the rest of them, and ran his hands through his hair. He looked like a man at the end of his rope. "I'm going to—"

The Floo alarm went off, and they froze. "That can't be James," Lily said, standing with a frown.

"I'll get it," Remus said quickly, urging Lily to stay with Addy on the sofa. "Might be some nosy reporter."

"Oh, Merlin, we'll be inundated," Lily muttered bleakly.

Remus was only gone a few moments, and when he came back, his face was carefully blank. "Sirius." His friend looked over with a drawn expression. "It's for you."

Regulus Black strode into the room on a storm cloud, looking very much like a man who had slept in his robes. "Where is he, brother?"

Sirius groaned aloud. "I do not have the patience today, Reggie."

Regulus grabbed a handful of his older brothers' robes and shook Sirius bodily. "Where. Is. The imposter? Where's the little mongrel that dragged our line through the mud in front of the entire—"

"Geroooff, you rabid arsehole." Sirius shook Regulus loose with a growl. "You think I'm harboring him, do you?"

"Do not pretend you didn't know," Regulus shot back. "You can fool the rest of the world, but I know how close you two are. There's no way you were fooled."

Sirius went green, and his hands began to shake.

"Uncle Regulus, that's quite enough," Archie said quickly. "I assure you, my father had no idea, and you making him feel worse about it is not helpful."

Regulus turned to scowl at him, then did a double-take. "You…am I to understand that you are my actual nephew?"

"As though my identity matters to you beyond a set of chromosomes?" Archie shook his head. "Whatever your intentions in coming here, we have enough on our plates today."

"And whose fault is that?" Regulus sneered.

"Mine."

"Mine," Harry said at the same time.

Regulus turned to glower at her. "I'm not at all surprised to find you involved, Miss Potter, if I may presume your identity despite a rather desperate shift in outward appearance."

"I beg your pardon—"

"It's fine, Mum. Mr. Black also won't be surprised to know that it was my idea," Harry said baldly.

"On the contrary, it confirms my worst suspicions of your influence on my nephew."

"Which nephew? The one you just met, or the one you thought was your nephew that you were so very proud of until you found out he was a halfblood?" Harry's eyes were alight with something Archie had never seen in her before. It was like seeing a light bulb without a lampshade for the first time. There was something unapologetically sharp and bright and free in her eyes, and he wondered if that flame had always been there or if the events of the last 24 hours had ignited it.

"Do you think it funny, to fool so many people with your little game? Do you think it amusing to watch people pin their hopes to a false idol and see their plans in ruins at your feet?" Regulus leaned down to menace over Harry, and Lily got to her feet.

"Be quiet, Regulus. This is my house, and I won't have you—"

"I wouldn't be here if my brother were ever at home."

"—barging in to berate my daughter for your own disappointments." Lily took a deep breath.

"Misplaced disappointments at that," Harry added acerbically. "Archie is a better heir than Rigel would ever have been, and it's not because of his perfect pedigree."

Archie wished Harry hadn't found her voice in defending him, as he didn't feel he needed it. Whether or not his uncle liked him really wasn't a hill worth taking, and earning his ire wasn't something Harry needed when she was supposed to be lying low.

Regulus dismissed him with a glance. "The Black line will need more than a good heir to come back from this travesty. We look like fools, brother. Incompetent fools."

Sirius laughed dryly. "That may be my silver lining. Thanks, Reg."

"This is no joke, Sirius! Lord Riddle is furious. Do you understand? If I survive the next six months, it will be down to how useful I can be in finding this boy for him."

For the first time, Archie noticed how scared Regulus was, under the veneer of fury.

"You'll never find him," Harry said softly.

"And I'm not going to let you trade Riddle that kid to save your own skin," Sirius spat, disgust in his tone. "Maybe stop serving the psychopath, did you think of that?"

Regulus bared his teeth. "Riddle has marked him, Sirius. It is only a matter of time before he tracks him down. The kid is doomed either way, but if we get to him first…Riddle may be merciful."

Sirius took Regulus by the arm and searched his face with a hard stare. "You really believe Riddle will forgive you for not noticing? No, Reggie. He might pretend to, but your days in the sun of the SOW Party are done. You should cut and run."

"A Black doesn't turn his back on his principles—"

"Oh, what principles?" Sirius made an impatient noise. "Is your priority this family or your pride?"

Regulus shrugged off his brother's hand with a sneer. "Rich, coming from you."

"I'm on a hypocritical roll today, apparently."

Remus spoke up tentatively, bravely ignoring Regulus' hostile expression as he asked, "Are you in earnest fear for your life, Regulus? We can protect you."

"You? Or Dumbledore? I would rather be cursed in the back." Regulus tossed his head like an offended stallion. "I will find some other way to get back in Lord Riddle's good graces."

"His bare-tolerance, you mean," Harry said. "Riddle has no good graces."

"You know nothing, you impudent little—"

"I know something that will get you back within tolerance, actually."

Regulus froze. His eyes narrowed. "You know where the imposter is?"

Harry set her chin. "No. But I know something Riddle doesn't, that will change the way he looks for Rigel."

Regulus worked his jaw, clearly torn between believing her and dismissing her. Archie wondered why Harry would offer information to Regulus of all people—she hated him, as far as he knew.

"I won't even make you ask," Harry said briskly. "I don't hate you nearly enough to give Riddle the satisfaction of punishing Rigel through you."

Regulus scowled, but held his tongue for once.

Harry lowered her voice and said, "Tell Riddle that his mark is no longer on Rigel Black."

"And what does that me—"

"Tell him Voldemort bears it instead. If he tracks it, he'll find Voldemort, not Rigel."

"Voldemort? The dark wizard who attacked the tournament?"

"What do you know about this madman, Harry?" Remus asked, disturbed.

"I know he's been recruiting thugs from the lower alleys," Harry said. "I know he attacked a coven of vampires who live up the street from me. I know he's bad news."

"And you somehow know he bears the mark Lord Riddle himself believes is carried by Rigel," Regulus said, suspicion warring with accusation.

Harry bowed her head. "Rigel got a patronus to me, before he fled. He explained what happened in the final task."

"Harry, you didn't mention—"

"Dad can't know." Harry looked around at them all very seriously. "James cannot know that I have been in contact with Rigel since yesterday. I know you don't believe us, Uncle Remus, when we say we don't know who Rigel is or where he is. Mum, I know you have doubts, too. Neither of you is good at hiding your thoughts. It's fine if you don't believe us. But Dad has to believe us. It's his career on the line if he has suspicions and doesn't turn us in."

"I should turn you in," Regulus snarled.

"On hearsay?" Harry favored him with an unimpressed look. "And cut off your only source of information on the impostor?"

Regulus looked to Archie, who held up his hands and shook his head. "Don't look at me. Harry was the one in England all this time. Whatever Rigel needed, he went to her." This lie was new, and felt unwieldy on his lips. He hadn't practiced it. Harry was going off-script.

Regulus took a deep breath, set his gaze on Harry's hard face and let it out. "If you're lying, girl…"

"Riddle will know the truth in any case when he tracks that bit of magic he tried to shove into Rigel's core."

"He what?" Remus looked sick, and Lily put a hand to Addy's head in reflexive recoil.

Archie felt a little ill himself, and he didn't fully understand what Harry even meant.

Harry seemed utterly unconcerned. "If you tell him first, Rigel loses nothing, and maybe Riddle doesn't kill you."

"And maybe he comes after you when he hears how I knew this," Regulus suggested darkly.

Lily made a noise of distress, but Harry only smiled. "That would be a poor look for him. I think he'll have enough bad press as it is."

Archie hated how confident Harry sounded, as though she faced down terrible men all the time, and it didn't scare her anymore. He knew the ruse had changed them—had felt it within himself, a callous at the center of his soul—but he hadn't realized how much it had affected Harry, on a level so deep that only now, when the first few layers of illusion had violently ruptured, was a hint of it beginning to shine through.

"Take your information and try to repair your tattered reputation, Reggie." Sirius said it tiredly, but his face was firm. "You won't mention Harry if you know what's good for you."

"Then how will I explain—"

"You'll explain that the Black Family Head will disown you if you reveal your source. How much use do you think he'd find you if you had no last name at all, brother?"

Regulus blanched, and backed away from Sirius. With a last glare at all of them, he strode from the room. The flare of the Floo broke the silence that fell in the living room, but only briefly.

"We should…all get some rest," Archie suggested weakly.

Sirius nodded, all his fight having left the room with his younger brother. Remus shuffled slowly toward the door, but Lily waylaid him.

"Will you take Addy for me tonight?"

Addy held out her arms for Remus with happy yammerings of agreement. Remus took her gently, though he looked uncertain. "Would you rather me stay here to help—?"

"No, thank you. My daughter and I are going to have a talk."

Harry winced, but didn't argue.

Archie wished he could help, but they couldn't protect one another from everything. Anyway, he had his own parental quagmire to wade through and Harry had no one to blame but herself. Helping Regulus made no sense…except, Harry always went out of her way to help people, even when she didn't have to.

And that was kind of the point, wasn't it?

The first time she tried to use the Floo, it didn't work. The second time, it stung her. Shaking her smarting fingers, Harry ducked into the kitchen where Lily was feeding Addy for what must have been the twentieth time that morning.

"Mum, the Floo—"

"Talk to your father."

Right. James was holed up in his study, and had been for several weeks. Harry had been avoiding him mostly, aware that his quality of life had significantly worsened since the debacle of the last task and the accompanying fall out. Owls hounded their breakfast table until he adjusted the wards, and now they crowded the front step agitatedly until James got around to collecting or burning their cargo. She'd seen snapshots in the paper of James hassled repeatedly in the Ministry lobby, and finally Amelia Bones had directed James to work from home.

Harry suspected he'd rather be hassled by reporters than attempt to work down the hall from a demanding toddler.

She knocked at the door and took the ensuing grunt for permission to enter. James was surrounded by stacks of newspapers, letters, and blue government folders. He nudged an empty mug her way without looking up from a statement he was taking notes on.

"Could use another cuppa, darling."

"I'll get you one, Dad." Harry reached out for the mug, but James put a hand on it quickly.

"Harry. What is it?"

Harry tensed the muscles in her leg against the impulse to shift her weight uncomfortably. "I just came to ask about the Floo, actually."

"No."

"I—I just wanted to go to the apothecary. I'm low on ingredients."

"No."

Harry swallowed her first and second complaints and tried to see things from his perspective. "I won't talk to any reporters," she said, eyeing the screaming headlines piled on his desk corner.

HOGWARTS HALFBLOOD STILL AT LARGE

WHO IS THE RIGEL BLACK CHILD?

S.O.W. BILL BATTERED IN HAILSTORM HEARING

THE END OF PUREBLOOD POLITICS AS WE KNOW IT?

James set down his quill with an impatient sigh. "It's not about the reporters, Harry. The public is in an uproar. Do you know how many death threats Sirius has received?"

She felt her heart shrink several sizes. "No," she said quietly.

"Suffice to say there are two dozen open cases on malicious harassment for the Blacks alone." James fixed her with a serious look. "For every person celebrating Rigel's win as a symbolic de-yoking of the oppressive status quo, there is someone the status quo benefits who wants this kid dead. The public knows how close the Potters and the Blacks are. It is now common knowledge that the real Black heir was galivanting in America for four years in your name. It's not a large leap to assume you were involved in the plot to destabilize the pureblood hegemony, too."

"But there was no plot," Harry protested.

"That doesn't matter, Harry." James worked his jaw tiredly. "I just…need you to stay in the house right now, all right?"

She nodded. "I'll just get you another coffee, Dad."

He pushed the mug her way, and it was almost a peace offering. In reaching to take it, her elbow caught the edge of a stack of papers and a mountain slide ensued. The coffee cup was swept off the desk with two dozen copies of The Daily Prophet and a tinkling crunch reported its fate.

"Sorry, sorry," Harry muttered, dropping to her knees to stack the papers. "I can't get used to the size of my limbs, and I forgot what not having peripheral vision is like…"

She shot a simple repairing spell from her fingertips and recovered the mug with a relieved smile. James cleared his throat.

"You can't do magic at home like that, Harry. You don't live in the alleys anymore."

Harry winced. "Sorry. I—Remus is devising a revision schedule for me. I'm going to take my O.W.L.s at the end of the summer."

"Until then, no magic without adult supervision."

Harry stood, a stack of papers under one arm and the mug cradled in her hands. "Yes, Dad. Do you need these, or shall I take them…?"

"Just put them in the basement. I may need them later."

She retreated from the study and told herself it wasn't cowardice. Lily took the coffee cup from her when she reached the kitchen.

"I'll handle it, Harry. Maybe you should go study some more."

Studying was all she and Archie were allowed to do, at least until Remus was satisfied he had mapped the edges of their education. No amount of reassurance that they were both well ahead of the standard British syllabus would do. Lily and Remus had to see it proven.

She carried the stack of newspapers down to her lab and arranged them chronologically. Part of her didn't want to know, but it wouldn't do to live in ignorance while the rest of the world went on.

The accounts immediately following the final task were the most damning. Public opinion oscillated wildly between confusion, fear, and outrage. Voldemort was mentioned, misspelled and misquoted, dozens of times. Speculation was quick to tie him to the terrorist activities at the World Cup and violent extremist events over the last year. After that, predictions devolved into a predictable pattern of vampire demonization and Dark wizard accusations leveled like political spears at the S.O.W. Party.

Curiosity and a sense of delecticious scandal seemed to permeate writing about Rigel Black, at least for the first several issues. She could feel the relish oozing from Skeeter's pen in a particularly damning essay aimed at the political elite on both sides.

One has to wonder at it, readers. How could two such celebrated geniuses both be so wildly misled by a child's playacting? Albus Dumbledore harbored RBC amidst the children of our pureblood elite for four years, and sources say the boy was Lord Riddle's own pick for a pureblood spot in what was supposed to be a rigorously vetted international tournament. With a wolf so long-languishing among their sheep, are these the shepherds we should trust to lead us at all?

Harry shuffled through the next several issues, looking for a shift in the public conversation toward the upcoming legislation vote.

There. An interview with Dumbledore himself.

Q -Thank you for sitting down with us today, Headmaster. I know this is a busy time of year for you.

A -More for my students, as you likely recall, Miss Orinthia [this reporter must confess she does not remember the Hogwarts end-of-term examinations fondly].

Q -Of course. So things are proceeding as normal at the school?

A -As normal as possible, considering all that has happened. Understandably, the students have a number of questions about their former classmate. Alas, they may never receive complete answers.

Q -Rigel Black was well-liked, wasn't he?

A -Phenomenally so. You must remember, this is a boy who saved many of his classmates from the evil Sleeping Sickness his first year here.

Q -That's right, and he defeated a basilisk that was terrorizing the school his second year, didn't he? Quite a legacy he leaves behind. It almost makes you wonder what his next three years would have been like, had he continued at Hogwarts.

A -I will wonder that for the rest of my life.

Q -People are also wondering, and I have to ask—you really had no idea? Forgive me, but the general consensus when I went to school was that you knew everything, Headmaster.

A -Not everyone will know this, but I have a close relationship with Lord Sirius Black. I met his son several times when he was very small, but a child can change significantly in the first eleven years of his life. Many exhibit radical shifts in identity during their youth, and the boarding school environment actually encourages children to discover themselves independently of the expectations of their families and friends back home.

Q -So you chalked up any discrepancies to the boy being a teenager, essentially.

A -The simplest explanation is usually the best. In this exceptional case, the explanation was much more complicated than anyone could have possibly imagined. A boy of eleven—do you remember yourself at eleven?

Q -By Merlin, I could barely find my way to Charms class.

A -A boy of those tender years assumed not only a new name, but a prominent title and an entire chess board of expectations to navigate from the very start. Looking back, I marvel at it. He came here with none of the preparation our pureblooded students receive. None of the private tutors or ancient stockpiles of knowledge. Yet, he was top of his year. He achieved things not seen in half a century at this school.

Q -He won an international tournament, pitted against the best students in the world. Yes, I know what you mean. It is incredible, and, you know, it really makes you think. Hogwarts must be one heck of a school.

A -I would like to take total credit, but I suspect there was just something extraordinary about the boy we know as Rigel Black.

Harry had to put the paper down as the words began to blur. She wiped at her eyes and called herself an idiot several times over. Her glasses were smudged by the tears and she removed them with a huff of annoyance. She hated wearing glasses again. At times it made her crave the Modified Polyjuice Potion. She'd gladly look like Archie the rest of her life if it meant she could see—

She froze, the embryo of an idea taking root on the sidewall of her brain without warning. Scrambling for her notebook, she jotted down three words. Partial Modified Polyjuice.

"Harry! Come upstairs!"

Halfway between reality and what could be, she shook herself loose of the idea and jogged up the stairs to answer her mother's call.

"Archie's here," Lily said when she came into the kitchen. Addy was somehow still eating. Perhaps toddlers were an exception to Gant's Law, and there was a hole to Nonbeing in Addy's stomach. "Back garden. Thirty minutes."

Ah yes. Their allotted outdoor time. It was more than prisoners of Azkaban got, she reminded herself wryly. Somehow, draconian policies born of a reflexive need to re-exert control hadn't factored into Harry's calculation of this particular scenario.

It was hard to feel indignant, though. She could see every time her parents looked at her how deep the ruse had cut. How confused they were. How betrayed they felt. Sometimes her mother stared at her as though she'd never seen her before. Eventually, they would get used to Harry and Archie's new appearances. Eventually, the wounds of trust would have to heal.

Archie looked up from where he was kicking at a plod of grass and summoned a smile for her. They started walking the perimeter of the lawn automatically, Harry walking a bit faster to keep up with Archie's significantly longer stride.

"How's he been?" Harry asked.

"Better. He stopped all his volunteer work, so he's been a bit restless. It's not good for him to be cooped up, but I've been helping him redecorate the house. We're…I told him we could get rid of the snakes," Archie said, a slightly hysterical laugh bubbling up in his throat. "I think he likes them, though."

Snakes. Treeslider. Harry's heart clenched, and she hoped the boomslang had found his way to the kitchens without her. She supposed there were plenty of mice in Hogwarts, but…she did miss having the snake around.

"How are your parents?"

"Kind of distant," she admitted. "Lily especially. She doesn't like keeping a secret from James, but she can't tell him that I knew before he found me that Rigel had fled. It feels like I'm constantly trying not to freak them out. Like I forgot how to be normal at some point."

"They're probably just a lot more observant right now. We really shocked them."

"We really shocked everyone. Have you seen the papers?"

Archie shook his head with a grimace. "I couldn't bear to. Dad either. I think our mail's just piling up somewhere."

"Did you write Hermione?"

"Yeah." Archie blew out a long breath. "Nothing from her yet. Hell, I don't know if she'll ever want to speak to me again."

"If she's that mad, she'll want to tell you," Harry said wryly.

Archie chuckled weakly. "Yeah. It's her dismissal I'm really afraid of."

"I'm trying to figure out how to get those items back from Rigel," Harry said carefully. She wouldn't put it entirely past her parents to have eavesdropping wards on them, though she didn't feel any when she bathed the garden with her magic. "Maybe he can mail them back to us."

"The mirror, you mean?"

"And the locket. Lily's gotten a lot of questions about it, and having the original would help her assess its effectiveness."

"A lot of job offers, too, I bet."

"The Department of Mysteries wants to canonize her, I think."

Archie sent her a sidelong look that was studiously neutral. "Is it true the necklace stopped a Killing Curse?"

Harry nodded, her mood darkening. She'd been so stupid that night. So desperate to get free that she left herself wide open to a lethal attack. She shouldn't have survived—wouldn't have, without that locket. "It was like a really powerful ward anchored to the wearer. The Killing Curse isn't blockable by any magic an individual can summon at a moment's disposal, but it can't penetrate everything. It can be physically stopped, and wards that are anchored firmly enough and woven tightly enough will stop it, too. Lily put weeks of magic into a single moment, ready to be unleashed at the right trigger. The cleverest bit was how she set the triggering mechanisms—it didn't activate any of the dozens of times Rigel was cursed or attacked. Only when he would have otherwise died."

"Ruddy brilliant. She could outfit the whole Auror division, and Dark wizards wouldn't stand a chance," Archie said, admiring.

"It would be hard to scale up significantly without a lot more help," Harry said, mentally calculating the amount of power even one Dark Detection Disk would require.

"What could be more worth throwing magic at than saving lives?" Archie looked up at the sky and grimaced. "That was naïve, huh? I'm working on that."

"Don't." Harry nudged him with her shoulder. "I like that you see the best in the world."

"Do I? Or do I imagine a world that doesn't exist?" He looked down at her glumly. "Lately, I've been wondering if anything I think about the world is real."

"There are good and bad things in this world," Harry said firmly. "There are evil psychopaths who want to crush other people beneath their boots and then there are really nice pairs of boots, with fireproofing and acid-resistant soles and stretchy leather that's soft on the ankles—"

"I get it, Harry, you miss your boots." Archie laughed, and this time it was stronger. "Little does the world appreciate the true casualty of our double-life."

"It's all about perspective," she agreed. When Archie smiled, her own heart felt a little lighter. "Speaking of perspective, would you be offended if I kept your eyesight after all?"

"You've lost me, Harry."

"I was just thinking I actually missed the Polyjuice a little. I miss being tall, and I really, really miss good vision. Then I thought, what if there was a way to select the exact attributes that Polyjuice imitates? Isolate the genes expressed to one specific desirable trait, instead of clumsily copying the whole strand of genetic material."

"You want to steal my eyes."

"I want to steal your eyesight. You can keep the color."

Archie shot her an offended look. "Grey goes with everything."

"It's a Black color. I'd like to try being a Potter for a while, if it's all the same to you."

"Your loss," Archie said. For a moment, it was like they were kids again.

"Arch!"

The back door opened and Sirius came jogging out, holding a smoking red letter in his hand.

"You'd better take this, sport."

Archie eyed it with alarm. "You didn't vanish it like the others?"

"This one's from your friend."

Harry pressed her lips together but couldn't contain a snort.

"Something funny, Harry?"

"Hermione sent you a Howler?" Harry burst into laughter. "Sorry. Haha—sorry, sorry. Can I listen?"

"You may not have a choice." Sirius thrust it into Archie's hands hurriedly. "It's gonna blow."

"No, no, I'm not ready for—"

The Howler burst open at Archie's touch and zoomed into the air before him, red paper twisting to form a very displeased moue as it shouted—

"DIDN'T I TELL YOU TO INCLUDE ME IN YOUR STUPID PLOTS!? ALL THIS TIME I COULD HAVE HELPED YOU!"

Sirius choked and Harry had to smother her amusement once more as Archie stared in wondering confusion at the shrieking missive.

"IF I DIDN'T THINK IT ENTIRELY BEYOND YOU, I'D ACCUSE YOU OF SLUMMING IT WITH THE GULLIBLE MUGGLEBORN AND TAKING A SPOT HELD OPEN FOR LESSER BLOODED STUDENTS AT AIM IN THE SAME BREATH."

Archie blanched.

"BUT I KNOW YOU. EVERYTHING MAKES MORE SENSE NOW, NOT LESS! DO YOU KNOW HOW OFTEN I QUESTIONED MY OWN SANITY? HOW I DISMISSED MY OWN CONFUSION WHEN WHAT I OBSERVED AND WHAT I KNEW DIDN'T ADD UP? DON'T YOU EVER MAKE ME QUESTION MYSELF AGAIN YOU SELFISH, STUPID, BOY—IF THAT IS YOUR PREFERRED GENDER."

Harry muffled an unkind guffaw at the way Archie's face slid from guilt to shame to hope again.

"WHEN YOUR MOST DESERVED GROUNDING COMES TO AN END I EXPECT YOU TO GROVEL PROFUSELY AND APOLOGIZE TO MY PARENTS. THEY ARE QUITE CONCERNED THAT MY BEST FRIEND HAS BEEN LYING TO ME FOR FOUR YEARS. THEN YOU ARE GOING TO EXPLAIN WHICH ONE OF YOU I WAS RUNNING AROUND THE LOWER ALLEYS WITH ALL SUMMER AND JUST HOW YOU INTEND TO CONTINUE YOUR STUDIES WITH YOUR FIRST FOUR YEARS OF MARKS UTTERLY VOIDED!"

The letter paused, as though to catch its breath, then said, in a much-softer-but-still-somewhat-shouting tone, "I Do Hope Nothing Bad Has Befallen Rigel. I Have THOUGHTS Regarding His Methods, But He Is A Hero Of Human Rights And A Person Of Relatively Sound Moral Fiber From All I Have Witnessed. Please Write Back. Hermione."

The Howler shredded itself and collapsed in a heap of smoking paper on the lawn. Sirius put it out with his wand and didn't bother to hide the wide smirk on his face.

"You sure know how to pick 'em, Archie."

"I don't deserve her friendship."

"Don't flatter yourself, cousin," Harry teased. "Just be grateful Hermione is a merciful god."

Sirius barked a laugh, and Archie looked immediately more at ease. He blinked the moisture back from his eyes and said, "You're just jealous. I bet none of your friends have sent you a Howler."

Harry stiffened. Forcing a huff, she said, "My brewer is probably drafting one as we speak. It's been weeks since I delivered any orders to him."

Archie grimaced apologetically when Sirius bent to make sure the Howler was no longer a fire-hazard. Harry shrugged uncomfortably. She knew he didn't mean the joke to sting. Certainly, she wouldn't be receiving any letters at all from her former friends, though they might wish to send Rigel a Howler. She and Archie had decoupled the mail spells from their aliases entirely. Only letters addressed to Harriett Potter would reach her now, regardless of what address was used. Letters to Rigel Black would get turned around entirely, as Sirius had explicitly blocked the alias after the first dozen letters descended on Grimmauld Place.

Lily called them in for dinner, and Harry busied herself setting the table. She couldn't afford to wonder which of her friends might have tried to reach out. Probably, they were as angry and confused as everyone else. Draco…she tried not to think about what she'd done to him, but sometimes she woke up in a cold sweat, the weight on his devastated stare between her shoulder blades, unshruggable.

Remus came into the kitchen with James in tow, evidently having pried him from his case files. "Smells delicious, Lily."

"Sirius cooked tonight. He brought it over to escape the construction dust, I gather."

Sirius nodded emphatically. "The kitchen's a warzone, but the oven still functions."

"No dessert?" James asked, opening a covered container with a curious sniff.

"No cake for a month." Sirius sent Archie a stern look that even Harry could tell was mostly for James' benefit.

Archie rolled his eyes. "You could make a cake and not give me any, Dad. This way, we're all suffering."

Sirius pouted and Remus laughed. "Sirius knows he would cave the first time you eyed it longingly."

James and Lily did not laugh, and an awkwardness descended as they all took their seats. Harry had expected Sirius to take the ruse hardest—he depended so much on Archie, and their bond was already strained—but after an initial stormy period of extreme highs and lows, Sirius seemed to have embraced his parental relationship with Archie with new vigor. He gained visible satisfaction from imposing arbitrary and sometimes ridiculous rules and watching Archie follow them. Her cousin had reportedly gone an entire day without using any form of the verb 'to be' just to humor Sirius.

She supposed after the shock of the lie settled, Sirius was just glad to have an explanation for his son's erratic and distant behavior all these years. Harry's parents, who had no reason whatsoever to worry about her previously, felt the betrayal all the keener. James had the added stress of heading a politically charged investigation he knew she was at least tangentially involved in, and Lily…

Harry suspected she was using concern over Harry's evident lack of formal education to cover a deeper anxiety about the world her daughter inhabited and the measures she had taken to secure a place there. Lily had explicitly begged her to never contact Rigel Black again. She'd all but wept when she explained in wrenching detail exactly what would happen to Harry were she discovered to be any more central to the blood-identity crime. Archie's assertion of guilt was the only thing between her and much harsher public scrutiny. The power of Archie's word, vested in the purity of his blood and social status, had saved her, even as their crime threatened to sweep the legs out from under that very power. Lily was terrified for her, and that, Harry thought, translated mostly to a defensive chill.

Out of nowhere, Sirius asked, "That one time when you went to the Weasleys'—was that you or Rigel?"

Archie swallowed a mouthful of carrots. "Me. It was too hard to switch then, so I just pretended to be him for a day."

"You pretended to be yourself," Sirius repeated thoughtfully.

"I pretended to be the kid the Weasleys knew from school," Archie clarified.

"Whenever we picked you up from school…"

"That was Rigel," Archie said quietly. "He'd go home with you. I'd go home with the Potters. Sometime the next day, usually, he would Floo here, Harry would Floo back from Diagon Alley, and we'd all swap."

James stabbed a red potato with unnecessary force.

Remus gestured with his water glass in Harry's direction. "That wasn't you at the Yule Ball."

"Definitely not." Harry made a disgusted face. "Archie took some serious artistic liberties that night."

"I'm not an expert on girls' fashion!"

"That explains so much," Sirius said.

"Horrifying," James agreed with a surly grunt.

"At the Malfoys' summer parties?" Remus asked.

"Rigel. We swapped the day of or before. I've never been to the Malfoys' place," Archie admitted.

Sirius gaped at him. "I went to all those stuffy parties for nothing? What about the New Year's Eve galas?"

Archie pretended to think about it. "Sometimes me. Sometimes Rigel. Harry—were you me once?"

"I don't remember," she lied. "We switched so many times…we had a lot of notes. Burned them," she added as James looked up from his plate inquiringly.

"Right," he muttered.

"I suppose we know why you never brought Hermione over," Lily said quietly.

"Because I don't know her at all, yes," Harry said dryly. "Also, she thought I was a girl who identified and presented as a boy."

"That's…involved," Remus said diplomatically.

"Yeah." Archie paused between bites of potatoes and said seriously. "Also, I'm in love with her."

"She just sent you a Howler," Sirius reminded him.

"Dear Merlin, it's Lily and James all over again." Remus chuckled. "When she hexes you, you'll know it's forever."

Even James and Lily had to smile at that. Something soft passed between them, and it gave Harry hope that everything could be salvaged after all.

A squawk like a dying rooster came from the back door and Addy shrieked back like a werewolf responding to the call of its own kind.

"What the devil now?" James threw his napkin down and stalked to the door. "Bloody owls got no respect for the morning part of morning post."

He cracked the door enough to allow the owl to deposit its burden at his feet with another ugly screech. James flipped it a Knut and frowned as he collected the missive—it was a newspaper, but only looked to be a couple of pages thick.

"Special edition," he murmured, slicing through the ties with a table knife.

Harry could read the headline from across the table.

FOREVER DO WE PART: MARRIAGE LAW MEETS DEFEAT!

Lily dropped her fork with a clatter and Sirius jumped to his feet.

"We did it? WE DID IT!" Sirius pulled Addy out of her highchair and spun her around the room with a shout of jubilation.

Addy vomited all over his robes. Sirius held her at arms' length and laughed. He laughed until he began to shake and Lily swiftly rescued her youngest daughter from her human roller-coaster of an uncle.

"The vote wasn't even close," James said wonderingly. His eyes flew across the page. "'Resoundingly rejected by a clear margin' it says. 'A final reckoning for a party plagued with publicity problems who provoked a populist backlash by proving before one and all the puerile pretension on their own platform.' By Godric, that's nice to read."

"Skeeter does have a way with alliteration," Harry said. Her cheeks hurt with how hard she wanted to grin.

Lily rounded the table and James embraced her with a laugh that was half-cry. Harry caught Archie's eye, and for the first time in a long time, something like pride bloomed quietly between them.

"Well done," Remus said quietly. Harry looked over and caught the full weight of his approval. "You pushed us to capitalize on Rigel's story. It worked, Harry."

"You all made it happen," she said, shrugging slightly. "I was stuck here. Rigel was like…a penalty shot. He gave you the chance, but in the end, the same people who worked all these years to combat systematic discrimination made the final play. So well done you."

"Well done all of us," Sirius said loudly. "James, I'm breaking into your wine cellar."

"We don't have a cellar—"

"I'm diving into the back of that cabinet you think we don't know about in your study!" Sirius made a break for the door, and James darted after him.

"Now, wait just a second. Some of those were inherited—"

Archie put his hand on Harry's and said, comically solemn, "I'm afraid I'm going to have to break our engagement, Miss Potter."

Harry put a hand to heart and fluttered her lashes in distress. "Be honest, is there someone else?"

He squeezed her hand tightly. "I've found my perfect person, it's true, but more than that—I simply don't think you require my protection any longer."

"Let's tear up the contract, then."

"I was thinking we'd burn it."

"Can I keep the cauldrons in the divorce?"

"We both know I wouldn't care for them properly."

Remus laughed. "This can only be for the good of the universe."

"You've certainly proven how dangerous the two of you are together," Lily said on a sigh. She came to lay a soft hand on Harry's curls. "Remus is right, though. While the rest of us were fumbling, you pushed through the fog with startling clarity. This is your victory, too. The magical world will be a better place for all witches and wizards tomorrow."

"Technically, it will be exactly the same," Archie said slowly. "It just won't have gotten worse. The S.O.W. Party still exists."

"The absence of the threat of arbitrary discrimination is what makes the world free, Archie." Lily smiled down at Addy with perfect hope. "The existence of that Party itself is not the problem. The problem is the concentration of power in the hands of those who would use it to arbitrarily constrain the autonomy of others. Such a concentration of arbitrary power will always be a stain on the tapestry of a tolerant and open society, but today that power was blunted. The discriminatory views of those people no longer matter—because they cannot wield power over us anymore."

"The next step is dismantling the damage they've already done," Remus added. "The legislation that prevents Hogwarts from schooling children based on blood has to be our target. Access to education in the absence of other discriminatory legislation means access to jobs, security, and happiness."

Lily and Remus devolved into a side panel on the logical next avenues of political action, but Harry had trouble focusing. She was still a little shell-shocked. How much time had she spent agonizing over the problem of the marriage law? Especially in the last year, it had come to feel like a problem that was entirely her own. If it passed, it was her fault for winning the tournament as a pureblood. If it failed, it would be because of something she did or said to turn the tide of public sentiment.

Well the tide was turned, but not from anything she could have predicted or wanted. What she said to Remus was the truth. In the end, it had almost nothing to do with her. People all over, who she didn't know and would probably never meet, had made their own voices heard. The status quo would change. The world would adjust in fits and starts to the new balance of power, even though most would never know that the stuttering collapse of S.O.W. momentum hinged on an Unbreakable Vow between one man and one child.

Harry would have to adjust, too. It wasn't just the breaking of the engagement contract with Archie. Unlike her cousin, she had no school to go back to in the Fall. She had no friends to keep in touch with. All she'd done as Rigel was nothing, now. She would have to make her own way at last.

Narcissa met her at the grate, a look in her eye that told her things were worse than she suspected.

"Pansy, thank you for coming."

"I would have come sooner, but Draco's been ignoring my letters," Pansy said quietly. "How is he?"

Narcissa removed the ashes from Pansy's robes without looking her in the eye. "He's shaken. Angry, but only on the surface."

Pansy didn't have to ask what was beneath that surface—it would be the same churning mass of questions that found purchase in her own chest. Along with a good dose of self-recrimination, knowing Draco.

A crash like glass shattering against stone startled from some distance and Narcissa pursed her lips. "Excuse me, dear. I must see to my husband. You remember the way?"

She nodded. Narcissa left at something slightly slower than a jog, and Pansy wondered what Lord Malfoy had to be so upset about. It had been a trying few weeks for everyone, but then, men were so much more fragile about disappointment.

Draco's door was closed when she approached it. It required true petulance to close a door in a house as big as Malfoy Manor; she braced herself for a scene.

Pansy knocked firmly several times.

"I'm not hungry," Draco called through the door.

Pansy allowed herself an eye-roll and pushed the door open regardless. "I'm not here to bring you a snack, Draco."

"Pansy!" Draco yelped her name more than said it and scrambled up from where he'd been lying indolently on the bedspread. The curtains in the room were drawn tightly together and her nose caught the musty smell of a boy who had not bathed in days. "What are you doing here?"

"I've come to see why you're ignoring my correspondence," Pansy said primly. "I didn't realize you were sulking. So sorry to have disturbed you." She made as though to leave and heard Draco sigh irritably behind her. With a smile, she looked back over her shoulder and said sweetly, "Unless you'd like to be a big boy today?"

"You're worse than Mother," Draco complained, dragging his feet over to the window to let in some afternoon light.

"Why do you think she recruited me?" Pansy shot back. She inspected the bench at the end of Draco's bed, but thought better of sitting on it when she spied the pile of dirty socks camping out underneath. "How long have you been wallowing?"

"I'm not wallowing," Draco said, running hands though his hair as though he could undo days of bedhead in thirty seconds. "I'm thinking."

"Good, because that's what I've been doing, too." Pansy stared at the socks until Draco found his wand and removed them from her presence. She sat and adjusted her skirts. "What have you concluded, then?"

Draco pulled a chair out from the vanity and sat backwards in it, arms crossed over the back. "Nothing. I'm just going in circles. Nothing makes any sense anymore."

"It has been difficult to reconcile it all," Pansy admitted. "My parents cross-examined me at length—I bet everyone else's did, too—and it helped me see a few things more clearly."

Draco rested his forehead on his arms and grumbled into his rumpled shirt, "Good for you."

"Looking back, there were so many things…we knew he was hiding something, but this?" Even now, she marveled at it. "He was a wholly different person. Fooling us is one thing, but we saw him with his family."

"Or we thought we did," Draco muttered.

"He could only have fooled Lord Black with extensive training. This was planned for much longer than the papers are speculating, I think." Pansy drummed her fingers on her knee, waiting for Draco to say something constructive.

Her friend only shrugged. "So what, Pansy?"

"So, what are we going to do about it, Draco?"

"Do? Nothing." Draco's voice was flat. Lifeless.

She stared at him. "You don't mean that."

"I have to," he snapped. There it was—real emotion sparked in the depths of his eyes as he glared at her. "Do you know what that sneak did to me? He called in the life debt." Draco stood and threw the chair sideways, where it collided into a wall with a crunching noise she hoped he found satisfying. Lord Malfoy really ought to set a better example. "I'm forbidden from looking for him. As if I'd want to." Draco cast a blasting curse at the crumpled chair and it burst violently into pieces.

"You're still angry with him, then?"

"What else should I be?" Draco snarled. "Supportive? Forgiving? That's what a friend would do and he made it pretty damn clear that our friendship was a complete lie from the start."

"Draco," Pansy started, but he was already in full ranting mode.

"He was just trying to get in good with my family, Pansy. To—to get leverage over us in case he got caught. He used me, used all of us to get what he wanted and then—then—" Draco's breath came in rapid pants, so Pansy finished his sentence for him.

"Then he left. And it hurt."

Draco bared his teeth at her and she resisted the urge to slap the manners back into him physically. She would do it verbally, instead.

"Weeks of thinking has gotten you nowhere, I see."

"You weren't there, Pansy. I caught him erasing traces of himself in our dorm room. You didn't hear what he said—"

"Forget what he said." Pansy rose to her feet and looked down her perfect nose at her perfectly obtuse friend. "Honestly, Draco. You find out your best friend has lied to you for four years and then you decide to believe everything he says?" Draco froze. Pansy gentled her tone but not the steel in her gaze. "Is Rigel Black a liar, or is he not?"

"I…" Draco closed his mouth, cleared his throat, and addressed her with considerably more deference. "What exactly are you saying, Pansy?"

"That if Rigel's purpose was to stop you from coming after him, then he succeeded on multiple fronts." Pansy moved forward to put a hand on Draco's face. "Didn't you use your empathy at all?"

She was close enough to see his cheeks grow ruddy. "I was too upset. I suppressed it before the last task, and then everything was so confusing. I could barely get hold of my own emotions, much less parse through his."

"I'm sure he saw to that," Pansy said. Boys were completely hopeless. "I admit I didn't foresee him using the life debt in this manner. Is your father bound, too?"

"All the Malfoys," he confirmed. "As we took the debt on as a family."

"Can't blame Rigel for that one," Pansy said dryly. Merlin save her from the pride of men. "Very well. Leave this to me."

"You?" Draco frowned at her.

"Of course. I haven't been sitting in my room for three weeks, Draco. Millie is checking with her family's contacts abroad. We can't assume we know what he really looks like, but he knew enough about purebloods to pass as one of us from the start." Pansy began to pace the room. "Either he had a lot of training, or his family is recently impure and he was raised with our traditions. I think the latter more likely, given the timeframe. His English is perfect, but my father heard from a friend at the Ministry that the Aurors are looking closely at the old French lines."

"They think he's a bastard?" Draco seemed surprised by the notion. Pansy wasn't sure how he had rationalized away Rigel's Parseltongue in the last few weeks, but she reflected the lack of his input might not be a real loss for the investigation.

"Or an orphan. Think about it—how could he have gone four years without his own people wondering where he was? Aside from last summer when he was out of touch, he's been in England more or less constantly for four years."

"That internship in the Americas…he never was in the Darian Gap, was he?"

"Probably not. When you accept that there are three of them rather than two, it's easier to sort through the things that are distinctly Heir Black and those that are purely Rigel."

"Three of them?"

Pansy blinked at him. "Rigel, Heir Black, and Miss Potter, of course."

Draco blinked back. "What…do you think Potter has to do with it?"

Salazar, he was slower than usual. "There's absolutely no way she wasn't in on it," Pansy said slowly. "Fooling your parent is one thing, but Harriett Potter and her cousin are closer than close. Looking back over their interactions, don't they seem a little too close? In retrospect, Rigel dodged questions from a lot of people over the years. His family did seem confused sometimes, though I brushed it off as him not telling them everything, but Harriett was never confused. She never once questioned him, did she? They defended one another in every situation, and at least some of those times it was Rigel, not Arcturus."

"But if she knew…" Draco shook his head. "She'd never admit it."

"Naturally, as I'd imagine she doesn't relish a stay in Azkaban prison. Her cousin has shielded her by claiming full responsibility. She can claim ignorance with the rest of her family, at least to some extent. That doesn't change the fact that she knew. She certainly knew Heir Black was in America using her name to enroll in one of their schools, and I would be very surprised if she didn't know who Rigel was and where he came from, too." The picture was obvious, once you had all the pieces. Pansy caught Draco's gaze and held it confidently. "Black and Potter are the keys. Their families can't keep them hidden away forever. We'll find him, Draco, and then we'll make him explain everything."

"Everything," Draco repeated, holding her eyes almost desperately.

"Just don't give up on him in the meantime," Pansy implored. "The boy who needs your friendship now more than ever was real, Drake, and he is out there alone somewhere in a lot of trouble." She took his hand and squeezed it, relieved when he squeezed hers back.

"We always knew he was in over his head with something," Draco said, a quiver to his voice.

"We just didn't understand how far under the surface he was living."

It was a month before James let her leave the house.

"One trip to Tate's and back," he said from the top of the basement stairs. Harry looked up from her cauldron, scarcely daring to hope. James eyed the potion with resignation that was not entirely bad-humored. "Only because you're driving your mother crazy going through the pantry."

Harry stirred the very large vat of tea in her cauldron and fought a small smile. That was the idea. "I'll be back before sundown," she promised.

"You'll be back in one hour exactly, or your cauldrons will be confiscated."

"My studies—"

"Don't insult either of us, Harry. Potions is the last subject you require any additional practice in."

Harry bit her tongue before the argument could devolve further. Before James closed the door behind him, she called, "Thanks, Dad!"

"One hour!"

Harry scrambled for her list and dashed up the stairs. She slid into a pair of trainers she'd left near the back porch and took a couple of her mother's shopping bags from the hook near the keys. Before anyone could change their minds, she was through the Floo.

Stepping into the apothecary was like coming home. She breathed in the herbs, pickling fluids, and chemicals. Rather than wandering the isles first, Harry went straight to the counter.

"Mr. Tate, if I make a big order can you have most of it delivered?"

Tate peered at her a bit strangely. "Certainly, I can do that, Miss…?"

"Oh." She put a hand to her face and cursed her own stupidity. "It's me, Harriet Potter."

"Miss Potter?" Tate's eyes flew wide and realization set in. "Ah! I had heard some rumors that…well, no consequence. Forgive me for not recognizing you."

"Not at all," she said, her stomach falling a bit. She fingered the end of the plain ribbon she'd been using to try and tame her exuberant curls. "I have changed a bit. I don't know exactly what you heard, but I imagine some of those rumors are true," she added, figuring she may as well face it head-on. "I've been using an altered appearance for several years. Now I'm just me again, though."

"Oh." Tate scratched his curly head uncomfortably for a moment, then settled on, "Well, it'll be no trouble recognizing you in the future, then, Miss Potter. I hope your presence here indicates you intend to continue patronizing this shop for some time to come." Tate smiled generously at her, and she smiled back.

"Thank you, Mr. Tate. I certainly don't know where else I'd go for such quality supplies."

"What are you in need of today, then?"

She showed him her list and set about collecting the ingredients she wanted to inspect personally while leaving the bulk items to him. She'd have liked to spend a good deal longer browsing, but thought her father would appreciate it if she were back sooner than absolutely required. Harry stuck to her list, and was back at the counter with her baskets just as Tate finished ringing the rest of it up on his till.

Looking at the heap of fresh ingredients, Harry couldn't help but feel a little anticipatory. Pillaging the pantry hadn't been strictly necessary, but she had been scraping the bottom of her stores.

"How much of this do you want to carry out?" Tate asked.

She plucked a handful of items for a potion she wanted to try later than evening. "Just these. The rest are fine to be delivered."

"Your usual tab?"

"If you don't mind."

"Er…could you confirm your account number? Just as…your appearance has altered significantly, Miss Potter."

She grimaced. "Of course, Mr. Tate. I appreciate your attention to security."

Harry rattled off her Gringotts information and made a mental note to get a new wand before someone required more stringent identification from her. Mr. Tate began ferrying her purchases to the storeroom for later packaging, and Harry collected the empty baskets to stack back in their place by the door.

The bell jangled and she stepped to the side automatically to avoid the other customer coming in.

"If it isn't little-miss-homeless."

She looked up from arranging the baskets and her eyebrows flew upwards. Caelum Lestrange shut the door behind him, looking more disgustingly smug than usual.

"Somehow, you're even uglier than you were, Halfblood."

"Lestrange," she said flatly. "How did you even recognize me?"

He gave her the most insulting of once-overs and smirked. "Who else could you be?"

"What does that mean?" Harry looked down at her brewing robes, utterly confused as to how he'd managed what Tate hadn't, when Tate had known her so much longer.

Lestrange ignored her. "I heard you haven't been in America all these years after all," he said. Something about the anticipation in his voice made her think he'd been dying to rib her about the scandal. "They're saying you slept on the streets of London to let your pureblood cousin lark it up across the pond in your place."

"That's ridiculous," Harry said, scowling.

Lestrange made a moue of mock-sympathy. "You know, you could have crashed with me if you were so desperate."

She clicked her tongue. "Let's not be utterly absurd."

"What's absurd is the idea of you slumming it in they alleys for four years instead of attending school like a normal person." Lestrange sneered, and she saw through it to the jealousy beneath. "It's no wonder you've come up with so many incongruously insane new potioneering methods—you had all the time in the world, and no idea what right even looked like, didn't you?"

Harry put a hand on her hip and made a face at him. "I'm sure there's a compliment in there, but as usual, it's buried under two decades of prejudice and rubbish. Haven't you heard, Lestrange? Different is the new normal."

Lestrange gave a low, fake laugh. "Don't tell me you buy into that new wave trite? Nothing has changed, dummy. You're still you and I'm still me. There will never be a world where you're not a freak and I'm not in charge."

"You're really an arse sometimes," Harry said through gritted teeth. "The world is changing course whether you like it or not, Lestrange. You can adapt to it, or drown in it."

"I think I understand the world better than you, street rat."

Harry shook her head. "I don't have time to keep arguing with you, unfortunately. Fun as this is, I'm expected at home."

"I'm surprised your daddy let you out of his sight," Lestrange said sweetly. "I bet you, your cousin, and that little blood thief you abetted set his career back twenty years."

Harry pressed her lips together, but the question slipped out anyway. "What did you do with your dose of Liberespirare?"

Lestrange went still. "I…sold it."

She narrowed her eyes. "You, who collect priceless ingredients for the pride of it, sold a potion? I don't think so."

He was on the attack before she could register the snarl on his face. "I suppose you're angry about me helping your little friend's opponent? If I'd known it was going to a mudblood, I wouldn't have given it up." He leaned in close enough to hiss. "By the way, you may have everyone fooled, but I don't believe for a moment you didn't know that imposter was a halfblood. I bet you loved watching him win, making a fool of every pureblood there."

"He did do that, didn't he?" she spat.

"It wasn't a real competition, brat. How could it prove anything? There wasn't even a pureblood in the finals."

Harry shook her head in slow disbelief. "Because the halfblood beat them both.

She didn't understand the intractable hate in his eyes. She couldn't comprehend his point of view at all—what did it cost him, who had everything, to admit that a halfblood was good at something?

Quietly, she asked, "Did you make the potion for the ritual?" She'd been furiously researching it for weeks, trying to figure out what sort of powers it might give the construct, even botched as the magical transfer had been. She'd determined it had to be a new invention, as even her darkest texts made no mention of anything similar. She recalled a letter from Krait, who had been pressed hard for the identity of his brewer. She remembered a letter from Lestrange in which he'd boasted of someone taking an interest in his ability to Shaped Imbue.

Lestrange's face went perfectly blank, and she supposed that was answer enough. "I don't know what you're rambling about," he whispered.

"Teaching you was a mistake," she said.

He jerked away from her and yanked a basket from the stack on his way past. Harry stared sightlessly at the floor for a long moment.

The bell chimed again, jerking her out of the dark pit of what-ifs. A middle-aged woman bustled into the shop and Harry slipped out the door behind her.

Her feet turned home, but a familiar voice rooted her in place.

"Harry."

Leo was waiting for her, leaned up against Tate's apothecary like he'd been there forever, and always would be there.

Harry was acutely aware of how different she looked, how different she felt, and how long it had been since they'd met. Of how Aurors had come knocking on doors in the alleys because of her. Of how no one on Dogwood Lane gave her up or contradicted the story she gave Mrs. Botting in any way. Of how she owed him and everyone he represented a debt that could never be repaid.

Leo gave her a long look, then reached out to twist a curl between his fingers. "It suits you."

Her lip wobbled, and she wanted to die.

"Leo. I—"

He produced a knife from his sleeve, and she stiffened. It was hers—or rather, it was the one he'd given her. Last she'd seen it, the blade was dripping with Barty's blood.

"Nicked this off the young Auror watching the evidence boxes that night," he said, flipping it slowly. "Recognized it at once in the mirror."

Harry tried to swallow. "I…gave it to Rigel for the tournament. Just in case."

Leo caught her gaze and didn't let go. "Margo saw your boots below a hooded cloak, running through the alleys the morning after the last task. I know it was you, lass."

She didn't give her tears permission to fall, but they did anyway. She didn't tell her legs to move forward and she was pretty sure she didn't tell her head to bury itself in Leo's shoulder, but however it happened she was crying, he was holding her, and the cracks of the last month gave way with a wrenching sob and—

"Oh, Harry. What have you gotten yourself into?"

She shattered into pieces.

Epilogue

The rain that dashed itself against the windows didn't stir him. The wind howling at the shutters couldn't move him. He was calm. Focused. He had to be, or the Divination was all but useless.

Severus bent low over a large map, intention in every fiber as he drew his magic through the array with ruthless control. At the center of the runes, a cluster of fluorescent green spheres glowed softly, perfectly imbued far beyond the natural life of such things. Retaining the magical signature of the one who imbued them years before.

The crystal beneath his right hand grew scalding as it absorbed the magic in the array. At the last possible moment, when it was so hot he risked third-degree burns across his palm, he released it. The crystal lurched into the air and hung suspended over the map in quivering uncertainty. Slowly, as he began to strain with the effort of keeping the array active, the crystal lilted, tilted, and slid sideways to hover unerringly over south-east England.

Severus released the magic with a gasp, vindicated. The boy hadn't left the country.

His scrying was not accurate enough to geolocate his wayward pupil, but he was nonetheless satisfied. Let the offended imbeciles scour the continent for him. Severus would find the teen in his own time. Straightening, he fixed his sights on the pristine apron in the corner. It hung limp, abandoned, with no evidence it had ever been worn at all.

A potioneer like Rigel couldn't hide his talents forever.

The boy had ruined everything. The legislation needed to save the magical world in tatters, votes evaporated in the boil of public outrage.

To add insult to injury, he'd managed to hamstring his right-hand man on the way out. Lucius and all his resources—useless.

Anger simmered into incredulity, and the dregs of that congealed to insatiable curiosity and he had to know. How could the boy have done this? And who was he?

His spies at the Ministry reported the boy was European: French, possibly. Speculation put him the bastard of an old line, and naturally so—his magic was too great to be otherwise explained.

Parseltongue was not a trait that ran in European lines, however. He should know. He had traced the line extensively, perhaps further than anyone else. If not a Black, he could only be the by-blow of another family intermingled with the Peverell brothers.

He would find the boy.

The door to his study creaked open, and Jacob Owens strode though it with a sour expression.

Speaking of long-lost Slytherin heirs…

Chapter 1

It was weeks before they stopped warding the Floo. Even when the spells wore off, Harry didn't dare try her luck. It felt too much like a test—prove us wrong, the open Floo whispered. She wanted her parents to trust her again.

She also wanted to see Leo again.

There hadn't been time to talk. He hadn't pressed. A field of explanations lay fallow, and the more time went by, the more she worried he would think she wasn't coming back. The lord's daughter who cut ties when she was done playing pretend.

All she could do was continue sending potions to Krait and hope he understood. It was like a tiny pocket of warmth, that hope. A candle in the cavernous winter that was her frozen relationship with James and Lily.

Harry bottled the latest batch and carried it upstairs. The family owl would have to take multiple trips, but there was no help for it. James had finally been let back to work, and Lily had taken Addy to Sirius', so Harry nearly dropped the potions in alarm when she heard the floorboard creak in the living room.

Her magic flared and came to back to her, reassuringly familiar with the signature it encountered. "Remus," she called. "My parents aren't home."

Remus sidled into the kitchen and watched her ready the potions for post for a long moment. "I fancy a walk, Harry. We could take those wherever they're going, if you'd like to join me."

Her first thought: this is a trap. "I'd have to ask Mum and Dad."

"I've left them a note." Remus gestured to the kitchen counter where, sure enough, his penmanship outlined the errand clearly. "I'm sure you'd like to get out of the house."

"I would," she admitted. "Lately, though, I've become suspicious of situations that seem to give me exactly what I want."

Remus shrugged. "By all means, continue your rather convoluted freighting method."

Harry scowled down at the owl harness and accompanying strings. "If you're taking the blame..."

"That is how you operate, isn't it?"

Harry winced. "Pretty sure it's too soon to joke about that."

Remus chuckled. "No, Harry. Joking is the only way through it in this family. Go on, you try."

She swallowed an awkward mouth of spit and said, "Maybe we should switch places for the trip. You carry the potions and I'll ask the penetrating questions."

Remus gave her an approving smile. "There she is. I was wondering if the Harry who faced down Regulus Black would ever emerge from the limpid lampshade she's donned."

Harry blew out a short breath. "I'm trying to turn over a new leaf."

"No, you're trying to turn Devil's Snare into a house plant." Remus put a hand on her shoulder, and it was not unkind. "Dimming yourself and tiptoeing around conflict won't make them forgive you."

"What if they never do?"

"You know them better than that. But Harry, you have to earn their good will again. Being invisible won't do it. Not causing more trouble isn't enough. You have to make it up to them."

"How?"

"Let's start with a return to normalcy." Remus picked up her potion crate and made for the Floo. "Diagon Alley, I presume?"

She hurried to get the Floo Powder for him and stared at the grate after he'd gone through, wondering if it was really all right to go on with life as though it hadn't changed ineffably. It shouldn't be okay. If the real world matched her internal experience, there should have been a violent rift—life before the ruse and life after. Surely, nothing as ordinary as a potions delivery should bridge the distance between those two realities.

Then again…Harry took a handful of powder and stepped into the grate. If anything could transcend the disconnect, it would have to be potions.

Remus waited patiently, as though he hadn't noticed the delay her existential crisis had caused. That was the dangerous thing about Remus; it was hard to know how much he really saw. She fell into step and tapped the bricks with her fingers to trigger the passageway. Remus' gaze lingered, and she hunched her shoulders instinctively, wishing for a crazy moment she had Rigel's face to hide behind.

"I don't have a wand," she said quietly. "Ri—he used to bring it back between terms, but…I don't suppose I'll see it again." He absorbed the information without commenting, assessing the implications. She didn't know what to do with the Phoenix and Holly wand. She couldn't use it, not when it was so intimately connected with Rigel. Her stomach turned at the thought of destroying it. So, it sat in her mokeskin pouch, suspended between lives, just as she was.

Jason tipped his cap at her as they passed the owl emporium. Harry wiggled her fingers, surprised that word of her new appearance had spread so quickly—it was only her second time in the alley since the change, after all.

"Remember last summer, when you weren't sure whether to tell me about the dueling tournament?"

She raised an eyebrow at the non sequitur. "Ralph hit me hard, but not enough to cause memory loss."

Remus didn't smile. "You asked me a question."

She cast a lure back through her mind, but nothing bit. "Which one?"

"You asked whether I'd rather know something but have to keep it a secret or not know it at all."

Ah. She nodded carefully. "You said you'd rather know."

"I said I would rather someone knew what you were doing, in case you ever needed help," he corrected. "And you trusted me because you know I can keep a secret. Both of those things are still true, Harry."

She swallowed. It was impossible to guess what exactly he suspected without incriminating herself. "I'll keep that in mind," she said as they took the fork down Knockturn.

Remus tensed slightly as they picked their way along the narrow alley. When they reached the Serpent's Storeroom, he studied the window with a furrowed brow.

Harry held open the door. "I stack the crates in the back—"

"Harry!" Krait dropped the bottle he was inspecting and rounded the counter to look her over. Only once he'd scanned for visible injuries did the worried look fall into something nonchalant. "Brave to show your face after worrying us all sick."

"Krait." She clasped his hand. "Sorry I was away so long. It's been…complicated."

"Not too complicated to keep you from a cauldron, I see." He eyed the crate as Remus set it down, then sized her uncle with a gruff, "Hired some help?"

"This is my uncle, Remus," Harry said. "Remus, this is my employer, Mr. Krait."

"A pleasure." Remus stuck out his hand and Krait inspected it before giving it a perfunctory shake.

"Bout time. Was starting to wonder if her family cared for her safety at all."

Remus went very still, and Harry winced. Changing the subject, she asked quickly. "Can you get a message to the Shrouds for me?"

Krait wrinkled his brow. "The vamps? I'd rather not."

"To Leo, then. He'll get it there." With an apologetic glance at Remus, she added frankly, "My mail is being watched."

Remus grimaced, but turned away to inspect an advert for Wolfsbane that read: Inquire at Counter.

"What's the message, then?"

"Just an inquiry into Gavril's condition. I heard some of what happened to him, and I'm sure it's a difficult time for the coven. If there's anything I can do…"

"They don't like help from outsiders," Krait said firmly.

"I'd still like to offer it. Have Leo talk to Kasten. He'll understand."

"I'll tell Leo when I see him," Krait muttered doubtfully. "He'll be fussed he missed you."

She smiled as though the thought of seeing Leo after their last encounter didn't scare her at all. "I know he meets with the merchants on second Tuesdays. How are things otherwise? Have they…settled?"

Krait gave her a long look. "Yes and no. Aurors had a lot of questions, but everyone knows what answers to give. Your friends have questions, too, but they'll wait for you to tell the tale yourself."

"I'll come back as soon as I'm able." Krait shot Remus a dark look, but Harry shook her head. "Don't blame them. My cousin and I made a lot of enemies. It's not safe for me right now."

"It was never safe for you," Krait said staunchly. "But we take care of our own."

She let the man see how the sentiment humbled. That the alleys still considered her theirs put an entire subset of fears back in their boxes.

Remus broke the moment with an incredulous question. "Do you really sell the Wolfsbane series at this price? It can't be profitable."

Krait raised an eyebrow. "Your family doesn't even know which potions you brew for me?"

Harry gave him an unappreciative look, but Krait was unrepentant. Remus turned his incredulity to her. "You take commissions for this, Harry? I know you make it for me, but I thought it required a license to sell."

She hummed. "I am licensed." Wolfsbane was the first thing she'd tested for, after Seifer's Solution. It hadn't been difficult to convince the Guild after all, with Aldermaster Hurst putting in a word for her—the only annoying bit was the outrageous 'administration' fee each license required.

"You're supplying it at cost, aren't you? This price can't be anything else." Remus said, still frowning. "You must be booked out for months."

"That's the sticker price. We have it on shelf during the Full Moon. It's a little cheaper if they order ahead, because I can buy ingredients in bulk when I know how much I need," she explained.

"And there's an additional discount if it's purchased with a week's worth of Potter's Protection Potion," Krait added, likely sensing a business opportunity.

"But to make enough to advertise…it's so much magic, Harry."

She could see the suspicion entering his eyes, so she shrugged in a particularly blithe way. "I'm homeschooling, and way ahead of the curriculum. What else have I got to spend my magic on? Once I figured out brewing to exhaustion made my core grow stronger, I started doing it all the time. I've got plenty, now; it's actually a bit of a waste if I don't make high-level potions with it."

Remus shook his head, but smiled ruefully at her. "I wish you would tell us about this stuff."

She bit her lip and said, not entirely truthful, "I didn't think it would interest anyone else."

Remus stopped smiling. "Is that really it? Or were you keeping so many secrets it was easier to hold everything back? I'm not trying to be hard on you," he added, seeing the look in her eyes. "Your parents will come around eventually, but they might sooner if you shared this part of your life with them. Whatever else you have going on, you're so obviously a good kid." He gestured to the price on the sign. "I mean, Merlin, Harry. They'd be so proud."

She swallowed and ducked her head in a nod. "Maybe you're right," she said hoarsely.

He let it go at that, and they said their goodbyes to Krait. Harry couldn't stop thinking about the idea of sharing her work in the alleys.

It was easier to hide things from her parents when they didn't know too much about her life. About her. All that was over, now. It was officially year one in After Ruse time.

Maybe…she didn't have to hide anymore.

Sirius kept the snakes after all. There were several new rocks arrayed in the small courtyard at Grimmauld Place, each with a flat, inviting top, and at midday it looked as though the Blacks were running some sort of reptilian tanning salon.

Addy loved them. The toddler's approving babble punctuated an otherwise oppressively warm and still atmosphere, and Harry listened with one ear for any sign the snakes were growing irritated at the constant commentary.

Archie sighed as he rolled over to expose the back of his neck to the sun. He muttered something into the grass, and Harry nudged him lazily.

"What?"

Archie turned his head and repeated, "Dad's agreed to let Hermione come over."

Harry sat up straighter. "Truly?"

Her cousin nodded, pushing the grass with his head. "I'm going to show her my actual life and hope she continues to forgive me."

"I hope you work it out," Harry said encouragingly. "I'm sure Sirius will like her."

"Everyone likes Hermione," Archie agreed with a soft smile.

Addy attempted to generously bestow her sunhat on her favorite snake, and Harry rescued the straw bonnet from immanent sundering.

"Are you going to try to regain any of your friendships, Harry?" Archie asked quietly.

"As myself?" Harry snorted as she tied the sunhat under her little sister's chin, and Addy copied the sound like a miniature prize bull. "No. It was meant to be this way."

Addy rolled onto her back to defeat the intended purpose of the hat, and Harry scooped a small snake out of the way absently. "I've been thinking…it might be for the best that everything ended when it did."

Archie shot her a surprised look. "You think so, too?"

Harry picked at the grass. "Better now than three years from now, right? I always knew I would have to sever those ties. I tried not to weave them too strongly, but somewhere…" Her fists clenched around soft tufts and she shook her head. "I don't even know how it happened. I certainly didn't encourage—" She broke off when the blades of grass blurred into a verdant watercolor and she realized she was crying. "Sorry."

Addy's hand slapped against her cheek with a wet smack and Harry caught her up gently in her lap.

"Sorry," she said again as Archie's arm came around her shoulders. "It's Rookwood's wedding this week. It's stupid, but I finished their present ages ago, and I don't know what to do with it now."

"You should send it anyway," Archie said at once. Harry scoffed, but Archie squeezed her. "I mean it. I think…it'll mean a lot to them, to know Rigel is out there, safe enough to send them a wedding present, you know? As long as it can't be traced back to you…won't it make you feel better?"

She shrugged. "I'm a little afraid of things designed to make me feel better. Can't really afford that kind of self-gratification, can we?"

Archie frowned and transferred Addy to his lap, patting her hat-rumpled hair like she was an emotional support animal. Addy cooed, evidently pleased to be mussed. "I don't think there's anything wrong with self-gratification, and it kind of bums me out that the ruse has brought you to the point that you think it's inherently bad."

Harry thought about it as one of the more friendly snakes wound its way up her ankle. "Maybe I will," she said softly. "As a sort of apology."

"A reassurance," Archie corrected her.

Her mouth hitched. "If there's anyone left to be reassured by it." She flopped back into the grass with a hard sigh. "Assuming they don't all hate me."

The letters came to her already open, but at least they came.

Esteemed Friend,

I know not what you have heard, but Gavril is indeed returned to us. He is weakened, but himself, and Grandfather expects with my assistance he shall make a full recovery. It provides me the opportunity to re-focus my work on healing essences. I have not yet discovered many distillations which prove effective for our kind. Much of the work in the restorative field is done by wizards, whose access to active magics informs their solutions. Such draughts are ever beyond me, but I believe I have only begun to probe the boundaries of pure essences and their applications.

Your inquiry is met, as always, with pleasant surprise and a modicum of polite puzzlement. Grandfather asks, and I hesitantly relay the question: what is the manner of assistance you offer? If there is a specific brew you think to provide, please name it. If there is something you imagine we may ask of you, that, too, requires elocution. We are not in the habit of seeking assistance from wizards, and they are not in the habit of providing it. If, as I suspect, your offer to help was a verbal display of support of the kind one friend may extend another, then I thank you, and we shall say no more of it.

Yours in mutual understanding,

Kasten

She tucked the letter back into its heavy envelope, wondering how to rectify the confusion she'd caused the coven. Harry hadn't meant her open-ended offer of help to be enigmatic. She wasn't sure exactly what sort of assistance a coven whose lieutenant had been possessed by Voldemort would require, but she supposed they weren't sure exactly what help a wizarding schoolgirl with a cauldron could supply, either.

The idea that vampires couldn't brew potions as she understood them wasn't new, exactly—she knew that complicated brews required active imbuing and she knew that vampires had no ability to channel magic. She just hadn't thought through the implications before. Knowing that, it was more obvious what form her assistance would take. She just had to find a brew for the occasion.

Harry was tempted to begin brainstorming then and there, but the second letter glared accusingly at her from the workbench. She couldn't avoid it forever.

Her mentor's handwriting slashed across the parchment—but then, it always did. There was nothing especially vicious about the slant of it now, no ink blots or nib-tears that would indicate a festering homicidal rage permeating the page. That was something, at least. She laid it flat so the shaking in her hands didn't distort the message, and even then, the letters crossed until she shook her head sharply to focus her vision.

Stupid girl. He can't do anything to you that you haven't already done yourself.

She let out a long breath and made peace with it; whatever Snape had to say, she had to hear it.

Potter,

I will not waste ink enumerating the many artifices that now shade our professional interactions. While you and your co-conspirators are no doubt awash in questions, I write to ask but one: have you been and do you remain in earnest about this apprenticeship?

Whatever else has been the fallout, the fact persists: I am left one student. If you should seek a continuance, the pressures and expectations on your shoulders will henceforth double. I trust you are prepared for this—as you appear to have been prepared for the rest of it in spite of any sane expectation.

You have now a rare opportunity only afforded those whose every plan has utterly unraveled. Re-examine your life. Decide what was real and what merely the trappings of a grossly convoluted plot. If, at the end of your evaluation, you find Potions stuck fast at the center of your being, we will speak again.

SS

The relief and self-recrimination broke through her, almost indistinguishable. He was angry. He wrapped it in professionalism, but Harry could tell she fell squarely within the shadow of his blame. What must he have thought, when Rigel was revealed? He, who was so unfailingly in Rigel's corner. He, who was so sensitive to betrayal.

For all that, he hadn't severed the apprenticeship. She'd expected cold silence or heated demands for information. She'd braced for a devastating extraction—a severing of lingering attachments—and she wouldn't even have blamed him. Of all the relationships Rigel built, Snape's mentorship had the strongest hold on her ego, wrapped up as it was in the very definition of her ambitions and self-worth. She was cognizant enough to know that, if he'd wanted to, he could tear a hole from her soul that no achievement would ever fill.

Instead, he'd given her the choice. Let her decide whether or not to preserve a bargain he must know he had no duty nor expectation to honor.

Even as her stomach unknotted, she told herself not to trust it. Snape would never accept the loss of Rigel so easily. If he made a show of forgiving her, it would be to gain her confidence. To get information on the student he truly cared for. The thought twisted her gut back into tight cramps, but it was better than the alternative.

It would have been for nothing, if Snape renounced her completely. Even if he only meant to use her to get to Rigel, at least she would have something to show for it all. An apprenticeship with Master Snape. It wasn't nothing, no matter how hollow it sat.

The idea to find Harry Potter started as a whim, really.

Edmund was inundated with wedding preparations and Aldon didn't have anyone else to talk to about the thousand-and-one questions that plagued him without end. Pansy had all but moved into Malfoy Manor, which illustrated rather painfully how well Rigel's peers were managing, and if one more of Aldon's own year mates suggested they'd suspected Rigel was a halfblood all along, he would not be responsible for the ensuing homicide.

Wizards older and more professionally connected than Aldon were searching for Rigel already. Aldon hoped they never found him. He could also accept that the odds of his finding Rigel were nearly zero without a significant trail to follow. Still, he needed answers, and an outlet for the restless out-of-place feeling that pervaded his reality. He thought there must be something only he could do, and that's when it came to him: Harriett Potter.

She hadn't disappeared to France or wherever. She knew Rigel—or at least the person Rigel pretended to be—better than anyone, and she was right there in England, waiting to be asked.

At least, he assumed she was. The papers had torn through the real Arcturus Black's interrogation at the Ministry, but no mention was made of Heiress Potter being officially questioned. People had largely overlooked her, probably because she was a halfblood. Aldon no longer knew what to think of halfbloods, and he suspected her part in the charade was more interesting than assumed. Aldon could recognize interesting when he saw it, and Harry had that in spades.

If she was more than incidentally involved, she'd be in danger if anyone else figured that out. Armed with urgent purpose, Aldon stopped thinking about finding Harry Potter and actually left his manor to go and do it.

His sense of purpose waned as he approached the Potions Guild on Craftsman Alley and realized he had no secondary plan in the event that she wasn't there. He could turn up on Lord Potter's doorstep, but it wasn't quite correct to call upon a young lady at home without sending a card first.

He disliked the feeling of having all his eggs clustered in a loosely-woven basket, but admitted silently that he didn't know the girl well enough to guess where, besides the Potions Guild, she might turn up.

As he dithered rather embarrassingly in the street, an urchin with a basketful of flowers curtseyed before him somewhat charmingly. "A bloom for you, ser?"

He began to shake his head, but thought better. It would be rude to call on Miss Potter empty handed, no matter where she turned up, wouldn't it? "What kinds do you carry?"

The girl blinked solemnly up at him. "All kinds, ser. What's your occasion?"

Aldon searched for words to describe the situation. "What sort of flower would you give a young lady who does not know you are coming to visit and who has not, upon reflection, expressed any interest in flowers during past interactions?"

"You're not a stalker, I hope," the child said severely.

Aldon raised his eyebrows. "If I am to present the lady with a gift, that implies a certain willingness to be seen, does it not?"

"There's all types of stalkers," the flower girl informed him primly. "If she doesn't like you back, it has to be daffodils. If you have an understanding, red carnations are good. If you think you do but you don't want to come on too strongly, I recommend dahlias, for strength and grace."

"I'll take two dahlias," Aldon said weakly.

The girl wrinkled a dirt-smudged nose. "Two is awkward. Either make a small bouquet or take just one."

Aldon ran a hand through his hair. "Just one, then. Do you have red—"

"Too strong." She handed him a pink dahlia that he had to admit was rather striking. "Four knuts."

He fished into his robe pocket for his money pouch and peered into it with a frown. "Do you have change for a galleon?"

The child squinted disapprovingly at him but did produce the requisite coins from various places about her person. She took the golden galleon with trepidation and hid it with a slight of hand so smooth he didn't see where it went. With another jarringly incorrect curtsey, the girl trotted off to critique someone else's romantic interests.

Armed with a single dahlia, Aldon strode through the foyer of the Potions Guild and cleared his throat perfunctorily to gain the attention of the deskman.

"Need directions?"

"Indeed. I am looking for Harriett Potter, and I understand she uses the laboratories here from time to time. Would you be so kind as to tell me which—"

The man at the desk cut him off with a scowl. "Miss Potter is not an official member of the Potions Guild and I am to direct all journalistic inquiries to our public statement disavowing any knowledge of the Rigel Black Conspiracy and condemning the use of Dark Potions in acts of terror such as that witnessed at the Hogwarts tournament finale."

Aldon blinked at him. "I beg your pardon. I believe I have given the wrong impression—"

"I'm not at liberty to give any information as to the habits or whereabouts of any of the Guild-associated student interns, past or present, including Miss Harriett Potter—"

"I can see you reading from that little piece of paper," Aldon drawled. "If you'd be so kind as to allow me to explain—"

"What's all this, then?"

A man he recognized easily from the society pages was coming toward them with a slight frown. Aldon straightened to his full height before bowing to the proper degree.

"Aldermaster Hurst, my name is Aldon Rosier—"

"Got another tabloid scribbler after Miss Potter."

Aldon gave an affronted shake of his head. "I certainly am not—"

"—asking questions, he was—"

Aldermaster Hurst held up his hands peaceably. "Gentlemen, please." Turning to the deskman, he said, "Mr. Fawle, I thank you for your tireless work protecting those affiliated by the great science of Potions; however, I very much doubt the Heir of Rosier has picked up—what do the kids call it?—a 'side-hustle' writing gossip for sensationalist rags. In fact, I'm certain I'd have heard if Lord Rosier disowned his only son." Hurst chuckled as though the end of an Ancient House could be considered amusing. "Mr. Rosier, why don't we speak in my office?"

Aldermaster Hurst was moving briskly before Aldon had quite registered his suggestion, much less given his agreement. He followed the man down several corridors to a handsome set of doors that opened onto a study that would not have been out of place in any manor of old. Aldon readied himself for an offer of refreshment, already eyeing the decanter of beautifully-colored brandy by the bookshelf, but Aldermaster Hurst simply sat and folded his hands on the eighteenth-century mahogany desk.

"What do you want with Miss Potter?"

Aldon paused for a moment, surprised into silence by the lack of invitation to sit, but gathered himself. "I would like to speak to her."

Aldermaster Hurst gave him a wry smile. "Many people would like to speak to Harriett Potter. From the flower in your hand, I would like to suppose you mean the girl no harm, but, alas, I cannot make such an assumption without proof in these troubled times."

"I wouldn't hurt her," Aldon said, taken aback by the stern interrogation. "I'm a…well, friend might be overstating it," he admitted, rather more freely than he ought. "We have met several times at various functions, and I was concerned for her wellbeing in light of recent events. I hoped to…reassure her. And to be reassured."

The words were pulled out of him by some force he couldn't name. Guilt? Decency? No—magic. He stepped backward away from the desk, pinpointing it after a moment as the source of the pull. "Just what in Salazar's name are you about, sir? Did you think I'd not notice the infernal mind magic inset in that—"

"My apologies," Hurst said at once, standing. As his hands left the desk, the subversive presence of magic faded. "You don't know how many ill-wishers we've dealt with on Harry's behalf. All the public knows of her is her work here, after all."

Aldon was completely off-balance. Never in his life had he been subjected to such ungentlemanly treatment. "Dishonorable," he muttered, eyeing the desk with extreme prejudice. "I could have taken a wizard's oath, if you required it."

"Would you have? Then you would be quite different from the others—even lords, yes—who have come intending to do the girl harm," Hurst said flatly.

Aldon paled. "I'd no idea it was that bad. There hasn't been much backlash in the papers yet…"

"The papers are careful," Hurst said on a long sigh. "They can only print facts and fish for quotations, with the combined legal thunderstorm of the Potters and the Blacks rumbling overhead. That doesn't mean people can't read between them, you know. Any mixed-blood associated with the Hogwarts Halfblood is a natural target. Poor girl."

"I've all the more reason to speak with her, then," Aldon said. "Is she here?"

Hurst shook his head ruefully. "She hasn't been back."

Aldon's hope sank. "It's safer for her at home, I suppose." Hurst hesitated. Just a fraction of a second, but Aldon caught it. "Unless there's somewhere else I should be looking?"

Hurst's face was hard to read, but he eyed the flower in Aldon's hand once more before saying, "There's an apothecary she brews for, and as far as I know she's still brewing."

"Nearby?" An apothecary. He had heard something about that, hadn't he?

Hurst rubbed his jaw. "It's down Knockturn Alley. Still want to go?"

Aldon suppressed a shudder. He hated that alley. As a boy, his father had taken pains to show him exactly what kind of a life he could expect outside the family. Penniless. Filthy. His children clad in rags, selling flowers or worse—

He cleared his throat. Swallowed. "That one on the corner past Borgin and Burke's?"

Hurst inclined his head. "The venerable Mr. Krait runs it, and he doesn't part with information about Harry easily. Tell him I sent you."

Aldon grimaced at the idea of being sent like a house elf, but turned it into a smile. "Thank you. I'll take my leave, then."

"Harry needs all the friends she can get," Hurst said, opening the doors in the first show of courtesy thus far. "I hope you find the reassurance you're looking for."

Aldon made an awkward gesture, somewhere between tipping an imaginary hat and saluting, and hurried out of the Potions Guild feeling somewhat less than the recently come of age wizard he was. Something about Mastery in a subject gave a person a perpetual aura of professorship. It was enough to make anyone feel like a schoolboy.

He stopped at the entrance to Knockturn Alley. Instinct told him to cover his face, hide the fact that the Heir of Rosier was about to stroll blithely though a din of iniquity. He fought against it: he was seventeen, now. He could walk anywhere he chose.

By Merlin, the smell. Gutters that hadn't seen a cleaning in days, and something he could only assume was rot. Aldon breathed as little as possible until he reached a corner that looked vaguely familiar. The Serpent's Storeroom. There were worse names, he supposed.

The door creaked on the inward push and the abrupt transition from afternoon sun to musty shadow had him blinking. The proprietor eyed him suspiciously from the counter, and Aldon put on his most pleasant expression.

"Are you Mr. Krait?"

"Who's asking?"

"Aldon Rosier, at your service." He bent at the upper back and smiled, but it died when the man sniffed dismissively.

"Rosier, eh? Don't sell dark potions."

"I am not in the market, thankfully," Aldon said, looking over his shoulder automatically. What a thing to say in an open room. And just what was he implying about his pedigree? "I'm here looking for a brewer of yours, actually. Harry."

That got his attention. Krait stood with a swiftness Aldon would not have credited the older wizard. "Never heard of him. Get out."

Aldon stood his ground, lowering his voice in an attempt to smoothly deescalate the interchange. "Aldermaster Hurst sent me. I'm a friend of Harry's, and I know she brews for you."

"You don't know anything if you're showing up here bandying that name about like—"

The door creaked open and Krait snapped his mouth shut. His eyes flicked to the doorway and an unhappy scowl settled over his features. "Fine timing you have, lass."

"What's my timing matter?"

That voice. Different and yet familiar. Unable to believe his luck, he turned with his heart in his throat and faltered at the sight of someone—Harriett?—blowing black curls out of her face with a loose grin.

"Just be grateful I could get away today," she said, hauling the crate of potions in her arms toward the counter. "Got a double batch of—"

"Miss Potter?"

She froze, then very deliberately set the crate down and turned to face him. "Aldon Rosier…" she murmured the name to herself, almost disbelieving, then shook her head. "Mr. Rosier. What—are you here for potions?"

"He asked for you," Krait grumbled.

Her eyes—dear Salazar those eyes—landed on the dahlia he forgot he was holding. "How did you…find me? That sounded silly. I'm not hiding." She gave a self-deprecating laugh that died quickly. "What, ah—"

"I can see him out if you prefer, Harry," Krait growled.

Aldon took a step away from the counter and Harry shook her head quickly, coming to stand beside him—no, in front of him. Protectively.

"That's all right, Krait. Thanks for looking out, but I know him."

Krait give him a rather insulting one-over, eyes lingering on the gold chain of his pocket watch. "You know him. Really."

Without asking, Harry reached out and tucked the chain back into Aldon's robe pocket. "We've met, anyway," she muttered. Looking up at Aldon, she added, "What did you want?"

He pressed the flower into her hand and bent over it gallantly. "I had hoped to speak to you at some length. Are you at liberty this afternoon?"

She hesitated, staring at the flower. "I…am. Sort of. Is it about…?"

"I wanted to see how you were doing," Aldon said.

Harry didn't seem to believe him. She twirled the flower consideringly, and seemed to come to a decision. "Have you eaten?"

He shook his head. She took two steps toward the door, then looked back at him with a nervous smile. "Come on. I know a place."

Aldon was prepared to turn back toward Diagon, but Harry led him further away from the high street instead. He gave up trying to follow their progress after the first turn and instead tried to make sense of her absent rambling.

"—lucky my uncle was busy today and my dad still thinks he's accompanying me," she was saying. "I don't have to be home right away."

They stopped in front of a curtained food stall and Harry ducked in to rattle off two orders without asking his preference. She unstacked a pair of stools and nudged one toward him unselfconsciously.

"They do have you on lockdown, then," he guessed.

Harry nodded as she sat. "It's been better lately, but…we scared them."

"So, they didn't know," Aldon said. That confirmed one of his theories.

Her shoulders hunched and he regrated voicing the thought aloud. "No one knew. And now everyone does." She turned to look at him with haunting guilt. "Listen, I'm really sorry. About Rigel. It must have been a shock."

Aldon shrugged, ignoring the pit of churning worry and confusion that rioted in his stomach when he thought about Rigel. "In some ways it was," he said hoarsely. "In others…well, Rigel was special. We already knew that."

"He was." Harry said the words almost perfunctorily. "Even we didn't realize how special."

Aldon traced her features, ignoring how different they were now and focusing on the tension in her brow, the defensiveness in her eyes. He decided she was lying. Harry lacked the aura of shock Rigel's schoolmates now walked the world with. For all that she was clearly sorry, she wasn't surprised. She was too solidly planted. Too guilty.

Not that that was surprising. He'd come because he already suspected as much. Rigel spoke of her too often and too fondly. Rigel knew Harry, which meant Harry knew him. She had to lie to protect herself, but she definitely knew more than she implied.

Harry waved to someone across the street, and Aldon looked up to find the girl who'd sold him the dahlia perched on a slumping rooftop overlooking the alley. Harry tucked the dahlia behind her ear with a grin, obviously guessing its source, and Aldon marveled at how comfortable she looked. A far cry from the stiff girl in tight shoes at the Gala, or the done-up doll from the Yule Ball. Perched on a low stool with a rough-cut flower in her hair, she looked at home.

Someone inside the stall called Harry's name, and she jumped up to collect the food as the flower girl disappeared from the roof above them. Harry came back with two bowls of steaming curry and Aldon took his with a cautious sniff.

"It's not spicy," she assured him.

Not sure if he should be insulted or grateful, Aldon took a small bite. People walked by them in the alley and he moved his shoes further back, wondering if this was her idea of private.

"I put up a muffling charm," she said.

Aldon frowned, not having noticed her casting. "You didn't use a wand."

"I don't have one," she said plainly. The grin twisting her lips told him at least she knew how absurd it sounded. "Rigel took mine to school. I was too afraid to go to Ollivander's at first, so I learned everything wandlessly. It took a lot longer, but turned out to be more useful."

He wondered why she would tell him such a thing, but was distracted when his mind caught up with the implications. "That's why Snape took Rigel to get a new wand his first term. Your wand didn't work for him."

She nodded slowly. "He gave that one back to Ollivander. I wonder if I should buy it, now that Archie's is no longer registered in my name."

Aldon shook his head. "But I saw you use one that night at the Gala…or you had it switched with Rigel's…?"

"Rigel wasn't there that night," she said gently. "That was the real Archie. He had his own wand and I had Rigel's, just for safe keeping, mostly. Didn't think I'd have to pretend to use it." Harry snorted into her curry. "Of course, Malfoy noticed and we had to 'switch back.'"

Aldon clutched the bowl with both hands, processing everything as fast as he was able. "So, you can't actually use one another's wands." Even as he said it, he felt entirely stupid.

"Of course not," she said softly, stirring her curry slowly. "We aren't twins with sympathetic magic."

"Of course." And wasn't it frustrating? Wasn't it just a bit nauseating that Rigel did so many impossible things they couldn't tell which ones were real and which were bald-faced lies?

Harry pivoted slightly on her stool to face him better. "What did you really want to talk about, Rosier? Please understand, I don't know where Rigel is."

He shook his head. "I don't want to know anything that might compromise his safety. You may not believe it, but I still consider Rigel my friend." She caught her breath, but Aldon couldn't look at her. Staring into his curry, he kept seeing Rigel's face that night in the kitchens, his eyes tight with something he hadn't understood. "I feel terrible about the way it…went," he confessed. "At the end, you know, he said he was tired. That he felt like a fraud. And I didn't listen—"

A hand pressed into his elbow and he regained control of his faculties at once. Harry's verdant eyes were soft. "You couldn't have known."

"I never imagined. But that doesn't lift the regret." He moved his shoulders in an almost-shrug, but the weight of it resettled, unshaken. Sometimes he wondered if the feeling of failure would ever go away.

"He wouldn't want you to blame yourself at all," Harry said quietly.

Aldon swallowed all the words he had for Rigel and ruthlessly focused on the girl in front of him. Clearing his throat, he said, "I really didn't come here to talk about him. I want to talk about you."

Harry blinked at him. "Me?"

He nodded. "My offer from the Yule Ball—"

"Oh." Harry let out a short laugh. "Oh, no. Please don't worry about that." She waved a hand as though to clear a sudden smoke. "With the legislation failing and all, I don't have any expectations of you."

He tried not to be insulted that she dismissed the matter so easily. She was trying to be kind, he was sure. "I mean quite the opposite," he said carefully.

"What?"

"I came to let you know that…my offer still stands." He almost didn't finish the sentence. The confused frown on her face wasn't promising.

"But the Marriage Law is finished."

"But the advantages of being pureblood in our society go on." She flinched, but he thought she needed to hear it all. "I've been thinking about the entire mess with Rigel, and I think you were more involved in the cover-up than you've admitted. Don't admit it—don't say anything. Just listen." He set down his curry and took her hand, gently at first, but more firmly when she squeezed back with wordless anxiety. "If you were complicit in the blood identity theft, as a halfblood, you could be in a lot of trouble. If you were bound to a pureblood…you might be shielded from the blowback."

Harry's breath evened out, and suddenly she was perfectly calm, like a switch being flipped. She squeezed his hand one more time and let it go. "What do you think Archie's been doing all this time?" she said quietly.

Aldon pursed his lips. "If I'm right in thinking Archie was the 'Harry' I danced with at the Yule Ball, then I think he's very in love with his American classmate and might have taken the opportunity afforded by the legislation being struck down to break your engagement."

Harry grimaced. "That's a good guess. And he did, but I don't need protection. Nor do I deserve it."

He opened his mouth to object, but she put a repressive hand on his shoulder.

"Your loyalty to Rigel is admirable, to go so far even knowing I'm not really his cousin." She said the last teasingly, as though she could make light of the situation. "If I really am culpable, you shouldn't be trying to protect me anyway. Luckily for both of us, I wasn't as involved as you think. I'm in no danger, Rosier."

He didn't believe her for a minute.

"Thank you for checking in on me, though. No one else has. Not that I expect them to," she added with a little stab at her curry.

He wisely chose not to comment on the likelihood of Pansy Parkinson paying the girl a visit as soon as Draco could be trusted alone for more than an hour.

Aldon opened his mouth to ask whether she'd really been living on her own since she was eleven, but Harry jumped up to smile at a roughly-garbed stranger, bowl abandoned on the curb.

"Leo!" She smiled at the newcomer as though he was her best friend in the world. "I thought Margo might tip you off."

The older boy gave her a crushing hug before swinging her out for a once-over. "She said your new boots looked expensive."

Harry grinned and stuck out her foot to show them off. Aldon supposed they did look new. "They're the latest model. Non-slip, acid proof, and temperature controlled."

"The trifecta," Leo said, smiling at her fondly. "Who's this, then?"

Aldon stood from the low stool and bowed shortly. "Aldon Rosier, at your service."

Leo bowed back. "Lionel Hurst, at hers."

Harry nudged him with a roll of her eyes. "Leo is the Aldermaster's son," she said, as though the shape of his nose and the shared name didn't make it clear. "Leo, Aldon is one of Rigel's friends from school."

The understanding that lit in Leo Hurst's eyes was more suspicious than Harry's entire act had been. "Nice to meet you," the older boy said. He slipped a moneybag out of his pocket, and it took Aldon a long moment to recognize it. "I believe this is yours."

Aldon patted his robes and realized, yes, it must be. He reclaimed it with an incredulous stare, even as Harry grimaced at Leo reprovingly.

"They didn't know he was your friend," Leo said apologetically.

Harry sighed and nodded as though this was a perfectly intelligible turn of events. "Put it in an inside pocket," she suggested as Aldon made to tuck it away again. He did so with an embarrassed grunt.

"Do you have time to train this afternoon?" Leo asked her.

Harry's eyes lit up. "I do, actually." She turned to collect her bowl. "Sorry, Rosier. I've got to run, but—" She paused and gave him a long look. "It was good of you to come." Her eyes took on a wistful quality. "Rigel had a good friend in you."

"Has."

Harry's expression fell into something stern. "You'll never see him again." The words cut through him like a rapier. "Please understand that," she implored.

He buried the hurt and summoned a small smile. "Well, then. I've got an opening in my friend roster now, so…"

She bit her lip. "I…will keep that in mind."

He'd been sure she would refuse the offer, and the smile she pulled on said almost as much. Harry returned the bowls to the stand and restacked the stools. Before she left, Aldon beat back his pride enough to ask, "How, ah, do I get back to—?"

The flower urchin from earlier appeared at his elbow like a demon summoned to a dark ritual. "I'll show you the way."

"Thanks, Margo," Harry said, flipping the girl a coin. "Keep an eye on his watch."

"Won't let nobody nick it," the girl promised solemnly.

Aldon could hardly refuse. "Lead the way, Miss Margo."

The girl giggled and took his hand in her smaller, dirtier palm. "Aren't you glad you didn't go for carnations?"

He had no answer to that. He was leaving with far more questions than answers, come to think of it, but even so…he was glad he took the trouble to track Harry Potter back to her lair. If nothing else, she was still interesting.

"How many more of your posh friends are you going to lead down these alleys?"

"I didn't lead him," she protested. "I never imagined seeing Aldon Rosier here." The mental image of him squatting on that stool with a bowl of street curry would never leave her.

"You say that like he's royalty," Leo pointed out.

"If the Wizarding World had Kings and Queen, he probably would be," she admitted ruefully. "Only the Malfoys and Lestranges stand above the Rosiers." At Leo's unimpressed look, she smiled slyly. "Little did he know he was graced by the presence of true royalty."

Leo pretended to inspect his bare fingers. "Should I have offered him my ring?"

She laughed. Leo stopped walking and took her hand. "That, right there. I've missed your laugh, lass. You've been away too long."

Harry swallowed. It was so easy to fall back into place with Leo and forget the unsaid things between them. With her father working late that night, she had no effective curfew. There could be no avoiding the long-overdue conversation. It had to happen.

It didn't happen.

Leo launched into a story about Marek and a gang of out-of-towners, and she forgot about their impending Talk until they reached the Dancing Phoenix. She waved at familiar faces as they wove through to the courtyard, but Leo didn't let her stop.

Only when he began to take off his shoes did she realize he really did intend to train.

"You're off-balance," he said, sinking into a ready stance.

She wobbled a bit copying him and grimaced. "It's maddening, being short again."

"Short can be useful," Leo said, darting in with a jab she ducked beneath easily. "Use it, don't fight it."

Harry grumbled, but launched into the practice with a sense of relief. This was a familiar problem. She'd take any distraction from having to fully explain herself.

The session went longer than usual, and Harry was far from holding her own, but even dusty and sweaty she felt better by the end of it. She still lost her balance and overestimated her reach, but the feeling of despair about it had receded. Maybe re-learning was a better answer than a permanent Polyjuice solution. With her luck, she'd get to a size she liked and then go through the second half of puberty.

Leo's whole crew was there when they trudged back into the Phoenix. Solom had a glass of milk waiting on ice, and Harry had to pretend her glasses had fogged when Rispah pulled her close and told her how very brave she was. Aled gave her grief about staying away half the year when she was only down the street, and they all had a good laugh at Marek for not realizing the bloke in America wasn't even her.

"Now I know why you were so cross with me for sending him," Leo sighed.

"A woman doesn't need a reason to be cross with a man," Rispah sniffed.

Leo shook his head, leaning back in his chair precariously. "My Harry's never cross! It was dreadfully out of character and can only be explained by a great deception."

Harry nudged his chair further back with her foot and smiled sweetly as he grabbed for the bench to stay balanced. "If I've deprived you of regularly experiencing my ire, Leo, I do apologize. I'll see to correcting that now that I have no secrets to keep."

"A woman must have some secrets," Rispah told her seriously. "It's part of the mystique."

"Everyone's seen your mystique, Rispah—"

Marek was on his arse before anyone knew what happened. He pointed accusingly at Rispah, who lounged in exaggerated indolence on Harry's shoulder. "How—?"

"Secret."

They laughed Marek back into his seat with a fresh pint to nurse his pride. As the guitarist in the corner struck up a note and the men jumped up to sing, Rispah dipped her head toward Harry's ear and said, "You look fully yourself, my dear. It becomes you."

Harry gave the beautiful woman a watery smile. "I'm sorry for deceiving you all—"

"Don't." Rispah let a single finger hover over Harry's mouth. "We understand it. What wouldn't we do for our own?" She gestured at the carousing group and shook her head. "I would do anything for my cousin. I just hope yours appreciates all you did for him."

She let Rispah see the pride in her eyes. "He'll be one of the greats. Now that he doesn't have to hide himself anymore, the world will see what Archie can really do."

Harry was looking forward to seeing it. She didn't know how much of his magic and attention had been tied up in continuous morphing, but she could imagine.

"You too, Harry."

"Me?"

Rispah nudged her. "You can show the world what you can really do now, too."

She hitched her mouth. "I haven't exactly been holding back."

As the sun threatened to set, Harry stood with a groan of stiff muscles. The group protested but she shook her head with a smile. "Dad'll never let me leave again if I'm not home when he gets in."

"And we all want Harry to come back again soon," Rispah said. She bussed Harry's forehead and patted her cheek. "Mrs. Hurst's been worrying, too. Next time, drop by the clinic."

"If I had time, I'd go right now and have her heal the beating from my limbs."

"And cheat yourself of all the progress?" Leo tapped her bicep with a gentle fist. "I wouldn't let you."

"Better walk her home, Leo," Aled called.

"To save her from temptation," Marek added with a clink of his glass on the table.

Leo waved off their capricious comments and sent Harry through the door with a bow.

"A king would never bow so deep," Harry said lightly.

"He would to a queen," Leo shot back.

Stymied, she made a bee-line for the nearest public Floo. As the noise of the Dancing Phoenix faded behind them, Harry said, "You still haven't…asked me anything."

Leo took a deep breath and let it out slowly, looking up at the sky as he did so. "Way I see it, there's no need to rush through it. Is there anything you need help with right now?"

She shook her head.

He nodded. "Then I don't need to know anything right away."

Harry didn't know what to say to that. They walked in silence for a time, and she listened to the sound of his footsteps keeping pace beside her. Leo stopped at the Floo and put his hands in his pockets. "We have time, Harry. Just be for a bit." With a wry tilt of his head, he added, "You seem like you need a break from interrogations, anyway."

She smiled. It was exactly what she needed. "Somehow, you always know."

"If you're the only thing I know my whole life, Harry, I'll be a wise man," Leo said.

Harry shook her head, a grin fighting through her reproach. "And then you ruin it."

"You liked it."

"Goodnight, Leo."

"Sleep tight, Harry."

For once, maybe she would.

It was Sunday morning, and Harry was meditating. She was supposed to be practicing her Animagus transformation, but James didn't know she'd already cracked it. He did know she was working on it, thanks to something Archie had admitted during his 'Morning at the Ministry,' as the family continued to refer to his interrogation. She wasn't sure what exactly was said, only that James had insisted on overseeing the remainder of her training, so she was pretending to try.

No one could know she'd had the ability when Rigel escaped. It was too easy to imagine an animagus slipping the Auror's net, and it was probably only unwillingness to know that preventing anyone asking whether Rigel was an animagus himself.

She wasn't even sure she could replicate the transformation outside of such an extreme fight-or-flight situation. She wasn't going to find out with her father watching.

A tap at the window broke her façade and she watched with unabashed interest as James crossed the room to collect the post. The owl shook its leg impatiently as James ran several spells over it, but he wouldn't be rushed. Once satisfied, he flipped through the mail deftly and handed an envelope to Harry without commenting.

Harry raised her eyebrows. "Are we done triple-checking my mail for letter bombs?"

"Keep joking about the death threats, Harry. That's sure to make me rethink your restrictions." James looked at her over the top of his coffee and she made a face at him.

Neither of them was completely joking, but they weren't deadly serious, either. Remus was a wise man. She went to open the envelope, pausing as her father added, "Besides—if the Potions Guild is trying to kill you, even I can't save you."

Harry slid the newest edition of Potions Quarterly from its sleeve with a smile that froze when she turned it over and saw the cover.

"Lestrange," she muttered darkly. "Must be his thesis piece."

"You don't sound happy for him," James remarked.

Harry pressed her lips together, but flipped to the middle of the magazine against her better judgement. His pointy, inbred face stared out at her from a glossy centerfold. She recognized the view from the window behind him and scowled. "He made them go out to his castle for the shoot? Ew."

"This would be his first publication under his own auspices, yes?"

She lowered the periodical to stare incredulously at James. "Without Master Whitaker on the byline, yes. But how did you…?" She flipped back to the front and realized he was paraphrasing the subtitle of the cover blurb: 'Breakout Brewer Caelum Lestrange: First in Print with Fresh Ideas.'

Harry tore back to the article, skimming it angrily until the content caught up to her. She shook her head and started back at the beginning. "It's…about Shaped Imbuing." It wasn't even bad. He outlined the concept in a way that was persuasively interesting before jumping into his ideas for theoretical applications and practical demonstration. She read the third paragraph several times before believing it.

'Shaped Imbuing, a method pioneered by novice brewer Harriett Potter, is the most revolutionary advancement to Potions in three centuries.'

Shaped Imbuing, pioneered by Harriett Potter.

"He credits me…" Harry felt her mouth fall open as she read on. "He cited my internship paper and—and there are direct quotes from our tutoring sessions." Unable to take anymore, she balled the magazine and threw it into the fire with a growl of rage.

James summoned it from the fire and doused the flames with an incredulous smile. "Is that how we treat repositories of knowledge?"

Harry jumped to her feet and began to pace angrily, not sure she trusted herself to control her magic without some physical outlet. "What the hell is he playing at?"

James looked between her and the article, clearly amused. "Is this some kind of weird potions courtship thing?"

She clenched her fist and shook it in his general direction. "Can you just burn that, please? I need some visceral satisfaction, but I can Vanish something into Non-Being if you'd rather."

"Not the antiques, please," James said calmly. He was skimming the pages. "Now, I'm no expert, but he seems to treat the subject fairly."

"Fairly? He's downright respectful," she snarled. "Constructively critical of its limitations and practically admiring in describing the discovery process."

"You've lost me," James said frankly. "Because those sound like good things."

"But they're all a lie." Harry sent a fireball of magic into the fireplace and winced as the chimney shook. She ran static-charged fingers through her hair and buried her face in her hands. "They have to be. He's vile."

None of it made any sense. It would have been submitted months ago for review, but months ago he would have been brewing that potion. How could she reconcile the words with his actions? He could he treat her work, halfblood work, so professionally, yet hold such hate that he would work with Voldemort toward pureblood supremacy? Normal people couldn't compartmentalize their beliefs so completely. Could they?

"Maybe he didn't write it," she said, testing the words aloud. Only no one else could have quoted her like that.

James came to kneel beside her on the floor. "What's this really about, Fawn? I thought you enjoyed teaching this kid."

"He did something unforgivable," she muttered. "It made me realize he's just a bigot like all the others, and he'll never change."

James brought her into a strong hug until the fight went out of her. When she blew out a long breath, he said, "You know, it's very difficult to do what Sirius did."

She lifted her head to give him a look. "I know that."

"Do you? Maybe because you grew up with him, it seems normal to you that he turned his back on everything he knew for the sake of principles. For friendship." James leveled her with serious eye contact. "But it's really, really hard to do. Most people don't. That you've made any progress with the Lestrange boy is…impressive."

"I haven't," she bit out.

James bopped her over the head with the singed article. "This was not written by a bigot. Don't give up on him yet."

Harry glared at him. "You don't know what he's—"

"And you don't know what Sirius had done, before he turned his back on the Dark. Even while he was trying to." The grim truth in James' eyes gave her pause. She couldn't imagine Sirius doing anything unforgivable. Her father pressed the journal into her hand and said, "You don't have to forgive him for whatever he did or said. Just…be a hand, if he ever reaches out."

He stood and picked up his coffee. On his way out of the room, he added, "I'm not saying it'll work out. Some people never turn. But I know you're brave enough to try, Harry."

James left, and she sank her head into her hands again. Lestrange stared at her through the cracks in her fingers, looking so sure of himself it had to be an act. He didn't deserve it. Maybe that wasn't the point, though.

Maybe…she could try again.

"The so-called pureblooded elite will never buy into an equal society if it means willingly relinquishing their own undue power! The Rigel Black Child has shown us the only way! Revolution! Revolution from within and without!"

A general cheer went up about the alley. Harry slipped through the crowd, avoiding eye contact as the woman on a makeshift pedestal shot sparks into the air with her wand to accentuate her talking points.

"If we have to shove their high and mighty noses in it every day, we will—"

Harry turned the corner and was left to imagine how, exactly, the woman planned to bring the attention of the ruling class to her cause. It was the fourth protest she'd seen in the alleys that week. Rabble-rousers, James called them. Harry gathered it was a loosely-affiliated group of groups rather than a single, cohesive movement, and the Aurors didn't seem concerned. They were busy tracking down Voldemort and dodging political attempts to assign blame for the disastrous way Riddle's tournament ended.

One silver lining of said disaster was that Riddle had disappeared from the lime light completely. Brooding, no doubt, and nursing wounded pride. And furiously plotting Rigel's demise, she allowed after a moment's consideration. It would be a very good thing if she and Riddle never crossed paths again.

The sun had already set when she reached the Lamia Lodge. James didn't like her leaving the house so late, but he was the one who had officially lifted her restrictions. Trust had to begin somewhere.

She entered without knocking, as she usually did, and the door scarcely had time to creak before she was slammed up against the inside corridor with a cold fist around her collar.

"Human," the unfamiliar vampire growled.

"Guilty," she choked, pulling her magic tightly into her skin to keep it from lashing out. "Is there a new human policy I should know about?"

"More like a new menu—"

"Enough, Silo. The human is here to see me." Kasten appeared at the end of the hallway, dark eyes glinting in the dim light of the wall sconces.

The hand released her, and Silo, who upon second glance was quite a bit shorter than any vampire she'd ever seen, leered at Kasten as he passed. "Watch your tone, fledgling. And teach your pet the codes."

Kasten stared after the other vampire with reproval. Harry rolled her neck as she touched the bottle in her pocket to make sure it hadn't cracked. "Are there codes now?" she asked.

"Not really. The Rogue uses one, but Silo's rule of thumb puts humans up against the wall in any case."

"I'm sure it's effective security," Harry said, somewhat doubtfully.

"The coven is on edge," Kasten murmured.

Harry thought about the woman shouting in Diagon Alley and grimaced. "The whole world is on edge."

"Beings with sense are always tense in times of great anticipation." Kasten's face was hard to read, but he did not sound anticipatory so much as pained. "People feel a change coming. It terrifies some and galvanizes others. So it will always be."

"I don't mind if the world changes," Harry muttered. "I just wish it would leave me out of it."

Kasten shook his head and led her further into the lodge. In some places, she could see where the wallpaper had burned away, and the wood around the doorway into the foyer was noticeably charred. "In an upheaval, there is no safe place to stand."

She eyed the slumping front desk, which had somehow survived the spring's conflagration despite being the textbook definition of dry tinder. A pair of chairs in the corner of the room were new, and Kasten gestured to one of them, awkwardly hovering until she sat.

"Your lab?" she asked, glancing toward the soot-stained staircase.

"Still being refurbished," Kasten said. "It is fit for working, but not for human lungs."

Harry took the bottle from her pocket and passed it to Kasten for examination. "This should help with his disorientation. The mental scars of possession will heal with time, but Doggart's Dram will speed the recovery."

"You are certain it will work on our kind?"

"It works on Squibs and there are documented uses of it by centaurs and banshees." Kasten raised his eyebrows, and Harry shrugged. "I didn't look into the specific circumstances. Sentient minds are the key; it won't work on animals, but any being could benefit. Active magic is not required."

Kasten nodded. "I will test a small dose on myself if you don't mind. Just to ensure it is safe."

"I understand. If it works, I'll bring more."

"You do not understand," Kasten said slowly. "Not fully. Your assistance in this time is…it implies a certain relationship with our coven."

Harry frowned. "In this time but not in others?"

Kasten's eyes widened. "You do not know." At her blank look, his eyes grew distant and pained once more. "The coven goes to war, Harry. This night."

She startled. "Tonight? What, now?"

"The Carpathians have crossed a red line. They conspired with wizards to enslave a rival vampire." Kasten leaned forward as though to ensure she understood the gravity of his words. "It cannot be borne."

Harry took a deep breath. "I thought you were already at war with the Carpathians. They did all this." She gestured to the scars of fire and ash on the room around them.

"Covens attack one another from time to time. It is expected when tensions reach a breaking point," Kasten said slowly. "Now, however, we know that attack was orchestrated by a human. Now, we know this is no skirmish. After this night, there will be only one coven in the alleys."

Harry gripped the arm of her chair to keep from reaching out. Her touch would not be welcome, she suspected. "Will you fight?"

"Even I cannot remain aloof," Kasten said. "Though I am young, I am Grandfather's heir. I will—"

"You will remain here with Gavril."

They looked over to see Irvina coming in from the courtyard. She was bedecked in blood-red battle armor, the elegance of which Harry had never seen the like. Her beautiful hair was bound with black ribbon, and there was a flame in her eyes that gave her the air of an avenging goddess. Harry pitied anyone in her way.

Kasten stood, Harry a moment after. "I am of age," he began, but Irvina interrupted him.

"Gavril must survive. You will tend to him through the battle. If our coven falls, you will carry him to safety. You are the seed that must plant us anew, Kasten. Gavril will be your lieutenant. The Count has decreed it."

Kasten's face hardened. "Then it shall be done."

Irvina turned her deadly gaze on Harry. "And you, fleshling? Will you fight for us?"

Harry recalled trying and failing to fend off Voldemort in his vampire host. "I could never keep up," she admitted.

Irvina nodded once. "That is as well. War is for the wrathful. You will be more use to Kasten alive if we should fail." She tipped back her head and let out a deep-throated cry. Countless echoing cries answered from the courtyard. The vampiress curled her fingers into claws, and the fierce expectation in her smile was terrifying. "Blood has waited long enough," she crooned.

"Go home, Harry," Kasten advised her. "This night is not for humans."

Harry moved toward the door in a daze. She looked back at the door to see Kasten standing a silent sentry at the other end of the dark corridor. "Be careful," she whispered. "If it goes wrong—"

"I will write."

She nodded, and stumbled out of the Lodge—and into Leo.

He caught her on the step and shook his head exasperatedly. "Why am I not surprised to find you here?"

"Leo, what—is the Rogue involved in this?"

Leo pulled her to the other side of the alley. "The Court doesn't strictly speaking get involved in coven matters."

She gave his attire a once-over, noting the arm braces, extra sheaths, and the leather-backed steel collar that looked like it might turn a pair of fangs from the carotid. "But?" she prompted, armed crossed.

"But the code was broken," Leo said grimly. "The Carpathians sold out one of ours to an outsider, and even if they hadn't—these battles have a way of getting out of hand."

"How can you keep up in a vampire fight?" Harry asked, bewildered. Leo was fast, but he wasn't that fast.

He laughed, a short, hard sound. "We won't. My boys'll be setting a perimeter, trying to keep the fighting in and uninvolved humans out of the way. If we happen to catch any stragglers…well, that's as it is."

Harry worried, and it must have shown on her face. Leo clipped her chin with a finger. "We'll be all right, lass. Dealt with coven squabbles before, and I don't doubt we will again." He hesitated, then said casually, "That said, I wouldn't mind if the city fire-brigade got a little tip-off, if you take my meaning."

Harry stared at him. "You want me to…tell someone?"

Leo pursed his lips and tilted his head. "Strickly speaking, it's not illegal for two covens to work out their differences. Only thing is, vampire battles tend to involve a lot of fire. And last time, well, we ran our folk pretty ragged trying to contain it until the fire-dousers came round." He waggled his eyebrows at her. "Might be nice if they showed up sooner. Not too soon, mind you. But quick enough."

"Uh-huh. This seems a little outside the spirit of the Code," Harry said. "I don't want to see a tattle-tale tax on my next tithe."

"This is a somewhat gray area in the Code," Leo admitted. "Fact is, fire is dangerous, and there's enough folk in these parts without magic to make it worth erring on the side of preventative planning."

Harry nodded slowly. A fully grown wizard could escape a fire no problem, but children, Squibs, the myriad passive-magic beings…not to mention the entire population of muggles just one city sector over, who wouldn't even see the smoke until it spread beyond the alley wards. "I'll see what I can do, Leo."

"Get home quick, and watch your back, lass."

Leo slipped into the Lodge after a series of complicated knocks, and she hoped he was going to be as removed from the fighting as he implied. The nearest public Floo was just a couple of blocks, but she jogged the distance to settle the nerves in her stomach.

James was waiting for her in the Floo room when she stumbled through the wards. "Hey, Dad."

"Little late, don't you think?"

She stood and brushed the soot from her sleeves. "My friend had more to talk about than I thought."

James gestured to the sweat on her face. "And then you went for a run?"

Harry wiped her brow with her sleeve and nodded. "Well, things are a little…heated in the alleys."

"What does that mean?" he asked sharply.

"Who's the on-call team for dousing this week?" she asked casually.

James scowled down at her. "It's Kingsley's crew. Are the alleys on fire?"

Shacklebolt. Harry had heard how he'd pulled one over on Archie in interrogation and didn't feel too bad about saying, "Not yet. But you might want to Floo him and let him know to be on more of an…alert status tonight. Maybe he shouldn't even go to sleep."

"Harry…"

"No wizarding laws will be broken."

"I don't love the way you stressed 'wizarding.'" James rubbed his forehead. "You've been out of restriction one week and you've gone and set the alleys on fire. Do you see how this makes it hard to trust you?"

"I haven't done anything," she said primly. "I am a concerned citizen making an anonymous tip that at some point tonight an enormous fire might break out south of Diagon Alley and if someone wanted to put his fire brigade on alert it might be of benefit to the community that he protects and serves. Maybe."

James groaned. "Anonymous tips will be the death of me."

Harry pretended to yawn. "Gosh, I'm tired. I'm sure you have lots of paperwork to start, so I'll get out of your way."

"I should deputize you and make you do the paperwork."

"I'm afraid the Auror department doesn't accept interns of ill repute."

"I'm closing the Floo."

"Thanks, but I've finished my errands for the evening."

Harry pretended not to hear her father send a ball of fire magic into the Floo. She climbed the stairs and the worry settled back over her. For all that she'd told Kasten she wanted to stand to the side, it was difficult to sleep knowing people she cared about were fighting battles without her. When it came to a fight where she could keep up…how long would she really be able to stay a spectator?

Regulus strode into the study without knocking, but straightened to attention upon finding him within. "My lord, forgive me. I assumed you would be taking supper."

Riddle eyed the missive in the younger man's hand. "Your report?"

Regulus inclined his head and crossed to the fireside armchair. "There's been an attack on the coven that aligned itself with the impostor."

"The Order?"

"No, other vampires," Regulus said. His mouth twisted on the word, and Riddle knew it rankled the proud man to be reduced to a gutter alley spy. Regulus was not yet forgiven for falling prey to Rigel's deception. If anyone should have seen through the act, it was him.

That was the problem with these old-school elitists. When it came down to it, they couldn't actually tell the difference. Rigel's power blinded them, and it took a blood ritual gone wrong to expose his impurity. Without unfathomable back luck, the boy might have gone his whole life without being caught. Might have climbed the ranks. Might have been given the very keys to the kingdom. Might have been the forceful change their kind needed to survive.

Instead, he was vapor in the wind. One more ghost story in the pantheon of purity myths.

Riddle tossed the report into the fire and let it smolder. "Inter-species squabbling doesn't concern us. When the Order and the impostor come to a head, that is our moment."

"My lord, about what I told you…" Regulus quailed under Riddle's sharp look, but rallied manfully. "Why not use the…mark of magic to track the imposter down and deal with it."

"I could do so quietly and efficiently and save the world a lot of trouble," Riddle admitted with a dark smile. "But that would not earn us any favors, Regulus, and we are sorely in need of good publicity."

"I see."

He didn't. None of the fools ever did. It wasn't really his fault—poor, sheltered pureblood, soaring, eyes closed, toward a burning sun, knowing not his coming demise, only chasing the warmth of it on his skin. Without him to lead them, they'd be gnats on the windshield of the world already.

Regulus bowed out of the room, but the door swung open almost immediately and a far more impertinent thorn took his place.

"Are we skipping dinner again?" Owens all but threw himself into the opposite chair, crossing his legs and allowing his foot to tap with American manners. "Only I wish you'd warn a guy. I could've eaten more at lunch."

"If you're looking for something to prattle at, the mirror in the foyer pretends to listen better than I," Riddle drawled, turning back to his book.

"I wanted to talk about the summer champion's tour," Owens said flatly. "Are we still going to—"

"No."

The boy sniffed. "Why not, though?"

Riddle snapped his book together and regretted it when he recalled in which century it had been bound. Smothering his irritation until it was discernable only as a thread of steel beneath his words, he said, "What would be the point of that, Jacob? The legislation is dead. We must nurture another opportunity to advance our cause."

"But I could show my face," Owens whined. "Make connections. Aren't I more useful as your heir if everyone knows who I am?"

"You are not anyone's heir yet."

"I'm Slytherins'. You said so yourself." He spoke in Parseltongue as though Riddle needed reminding of his gift. At times he wondered if it had been a mistake to draw Isolt's line out of obscurity, but it was his nature to retain a fallback plan.

As annoying as that plan might be, it was preferable to having no alternative, particularly now that Rigel had gone and proven himself unsuitable in front of all and sundry.

"So, as heir presumptive you would give the media a spectacle? Should we leave an empty chair for our missing felon to remind everyone of the colossal, inexorable failure of the final task?"

Owens sunk into his chair and grumbled, "Maybe he'd come. Show-off likes attention."

"He'd be a fool to show his face, and Rigel is no fool. Never mind the Ministry. What I'll do to him when I have his lying neck within reach…" He allowed himself to picture it for one, satisfying moment. So many loose ends would be severed with the boy's death. The wildcard taken out of play, and all the vows laid to rest between them.

The Vow…there was a thought.

The wording had been…ambiguous, on the boy's end. Any and all tasks required of a champion. Did that proscription end when Rigel satisfied the condition of winning? Certainly, Riddle was still held to his part of it. He would not be so arrogant as to predict the exact boundaries of the Vow's interpretations; one never really knew until the blood began to heat in the veins.

Still, there was a chance. He risked appearing the fool if Rigel didn't show, but Rigel risked much more if the Vow considered the requirement valid.

It seemed he had one final wager to make with Rigel Black.

He was trying to get his head right and be an adult about it. Trying to put his feelings aside and see how much bigger than him it all was. Trying to listen to what Pansy needed him to hear.

Some days, it was harder than others.

The conservatory was tastefully bedecked, with silver cloth draping that made the greenery stand out all the more. His mother had cried, as she always did at sacred bondings, and she would cry again when the bride and groom exchanged first spells. The reception was in full swing and shaping up to be a who's who of Dark society.

Draco wove through people without really seeing them. The notes of a string quartet drew his gaze to the dance floor, and he wondered how two people could possible be so happy with so much chaos and confusion in the world. Watching Edmund and Alice sway, he thought people in love must exist in a separate reality from the rest of them.

He skirted the punch table and nabbed one of the undiluted fairy wines. His mother wouldn't approve of him drinking in his 'fragile emotional state,' but she would be too busy imagining Rookwood-Selwyn babies to notice.

"—can't believe how badly the Party misjudged that—"

"—wrong that I'm glad the law didn't go through? Wouldn't want to marry one of them…"

He took a long swig, wishing he could charm his ears shut with magic without being unforgivably uncouth. There was no avoiding politics at such events, but he was sick to death of the endless speculation about the legislation, the last task…Rigel.

"—and that thing—the amulet! It stopped the Killing Curse."

"Impossible."

"It did."

"That piece of refuse must not have cast it right."

"I think I know a perfect Killing Curse when I see one."

Draco turned to blink incredulously at the wizard who would say such a thing in mixed company. He had a beard that was either woefully neglected or a wild animal making a remarkably neat nest in the folds of his neck. The beard quivered as the wizard poked his friend in the chest and insisted, "That was a fully manifested curse and something stopped it."

A hand at his elbow made Draco start and slosh his wine onto his cuff. Blaise was there, apologetically siphoning the spilled wine off the fabric with practiced wand movements.

"Sorry, Draco. Didn't mean to startle you."

"Not your fault," Draco murmured. "I got distracted by—"

"The imbecile bragging about recognizing the most recognizable curse in existence?" Blaise shot the bearded wizard a droll look and shook his head. "Hard not to hear him."

"Sick of people talking about it," Draco complained.

"You're going to be sick for a while, then," Blaise said flatly. "In case you missed it, Rigel won the Triwizard Tournament, broke the Founders' wards, revealed himself a halfblood, and then escaped from under the noses of the entire DMLE."

"You forgot 'survived a killing curse' and 'betrayed all his friends,'" Draco grumbled.

Blaise raised an eyebrow. "I assume you're kidding about the second part, as Pansy indicated you had recently pulled your head out of your arse, but as to the first—that was Lady Potter's doing."

Draco stared at him. "What was?"

"The Killing Curse," Blaise said quietly. "Rigel let me examine the amulet he was wearing. It had some intense protective magic woven into it, and Lady Potter designed and crafted the whole thing."

"The Potters just can't stop inventing things, can they?"

Blaise and Draco turned guiltily, and Pansy shook her head with a rueful smile. "Didn't I say we were going to go through it together? Come along, boys. The others are waiting."

Something about the way her elegantly secured ponytail swished when she walked away made Draco wonder if Pansy had led armies into battle in a previous life.

The others were gathered in an out-of-the-way clearing, loosely shaded from prying eyes by a trailing vine that had escaped its winter pruning.

Pansy cleared her throat and met each of their eyes before starting. "To be exceedingly clear, we are here to discuss the potential whereabouts of our friend, Rigel. We do not intend to turn him in and we are not here to blame or question him. Only to find him and help him, if needed."

All eyes turned to Theo, who scowled back defiantly. "I wouldn't be here if I wasn't still his friend. Anyway, I came around before Draco did."

Draco narrowed his eyes, but Pansy said quickly, "Speaking of Draco, he is not to be questioned or tasked in regards to this matter. He is here as an interested observer only."

Theo smirked at him. "We know about the life debt. Everyone knows Lord Malfoy is in the dog house with Riddle because of it."

"All these years and no one's murdered you yet, Theo. Remarkable," Draco bit out.

"And we aren't here to argue," Millicent put in. "I have an update."

"Go ahead, Millie," Pansy agreed.

"There is no sign of him on the continent." At their frowns, Millicent gestured impatiently. "No, that's good, don't you see? We're narrowing it down."

"Or he's better at hiding than you are at looking," Blaise suggested.

"We traced every recently disgraced or penniless family," Millicent said defensively. "No lost heirs unaccounted for, and no one suddenly reappearing after a long time away. My father and uncles have been making inquiries, too. I know they haven't found anything."

"You're assuming he's associated with a prominent family," Theo argued. "That doesn't even line up with the account Arcturus Black gave the Aurors."

"I've chosen to treat Heir Black's account not as fact but as evidence of what Rigel wants us to think. We all know he's too smart not to have thought up a story ahead of time in case he got caught."

There was general consensus at this. "Does anyone else have news to share?" Pansy asked hopefully.

Aldon stepped forward with a smile so smug it was a wonder it didn't walk off his face and start its own line of leather shoes. "I found Harry Potter," he said.

"Was she missing?" Theo looked around to make sure he was not the only one confused by the non sequitur.

"She's been laying low," Pansy said, eyes narrowed. "My letters have been turned away unopened. Where did you run into her?"

"Knockturn Alley." The way he said it was deliberately provocative.

Theo whistled. "I knew she was cool."

"She works there, apparently," Aldon went on. At Pansy's sharp inhale, he smirked. "Not like that. As a potions brewer."

Pansy blew out a breath, color in her cheeks. "Obviously. I knew that."

"We knew she had a job, at least. Was it really in Knockturn Alley? I thought those rumors were nonsense," Millicent said.

"Which ones? I heard she was living in some old lady's attic. Then I heard she was living in a nest of vampires, acting as their blood bank. And some are saying she lived on the streets and stole to eat—only I guess she wouldn't need to steal if she had income." Theo scratched his head. "It's not easy parsing through all the mad stuff."

Draco could keep quiet no longer. "Harry brews for an apothecary in Knockturn, and for Horace Burke and a number of other distributers probably as well. I'm sure she doesn't need to steal anything." The others stared at him. "What? Rigel and Uncle Snape have both have mentioned it numerous times. Weren't you listening?"

Pansy gave him a soft smile, and he realized it was because he'd said Rigel's name aloud without growling it. "All right, so you found her at work," she prompted. The attention turned back to Aldon, who preened like an underfed puppy.

"We had a long talk. She's doing surprisingly well, all things considered."

"Is she?" Pansy and Millicent exchanged a look.

"Well enough to leave her family's protection to wander about London," Aldon said, shrugging. "More than that, she seems…relaxed. Like a different person—and not just her appearance."

"Her appearance has changed?" Blaise said sharply.

Aldon nodded. "Drastically. She used to look like Rigel, remember? And so did Arcturus. All three of them have apparently been switching places for years."

"All three of them? Are you sure?" Pansy pressed.

"She admitted it. I think it was difficult to switch Rigel in and out of place while they were at home. At some of the social events we thought Rigel attended, it wasn't him at all. It was one of the other two." Aldon nodded in the face of their collective disbelief. "Hard to fathom, isn't it? That's why they all had to look alike."

"And why he was so bloody androgenous," Theo muttered.

Draco's stomach clenched at the thought that Rigel's unique femininity had been so precisely designed—a mask even Harriett Potter could wear. Aldon was right; it was mental.

"But which times was it the real Rigel, and which times was it Arcturus? Or Harriett?" Millicent put a hand to her head. "I have to think about this."

"Maybe we never saw Rigel on holidays," Aldon speculated.

"No, we did." Pansy was thinking furiously. "At the summer garden parties—that was definitely Rigel."

"And at the Yule Ball," Blaise put it.

"But that was not Harry," Aldon confirmed. "Archie went as her that night."

"Wicked," Theo breathed.

"What about the New Year Galas?" Pansy asked.

Millicent shook her head. "Too hard to tell. Maybe when he saved Mr. Ogden—"

"No, that was Arcturus and Harriett," Aldon said confidently. "I asked her about the wand switching thing. It's…not a thing."

Pansy turned with wide eyes to Draco. "You noticed they switched that night! Rigel had Harriett's wand, and Harriett—"

"Never had a wand. She carried Rigel's on holidays, but even now she doesn't carry one at all. Doesn't need it," Aldon said. Draco wanted to shake him until he dropped all his secrets at once instead of dolling them out like an old lady in the park who didn't want the birds to go away.

Pansy deflated. "Oh. I suppose that explains why Rigel had to get a new wand in first year."

"Doesn't it?" Aldon shook his head. "It's amazing how many things considered 'Rigel's eccentricities' were actually part of the act."

"Amazing," Draco muttered sourly. How could they act like they were solving clues at a murder mystery party? Didn't it kill them to picture Rigel's face? Didn't it feel as though a knife was twisting deeper with every new lie revealed?

"When you think about it like that…" Theo ticked off his fingers blithely. "There's his weird aversion to touching people, the way he sleeps fully dressed, and how none of us ever saw him change clothes. How do you explain that?"

"It's called modesty, Theo," Millicent muttered.

Aldon blinked slowly, something sad overshadowing the pleasure of knowing things no one else did. "Merlin, no wonder he was so damn self-conscious. I thought it was some kind of inferiority complex, but…it was more than that, wasn't it? Every day was a reminder that he wasn't good enough. That without the lie, he wouldn't be there."

"That would give anyone a complex," Blaise said slowly.

"And every time someone talked about the inferiority of lesser bloods, they might as well have been talking about him," Aldon croaked.

Even Theo winced at that. "He was too good at fooling us."

"We weren't looking for that sort of deception," Millicent said, somewhat defensively.

"Now we know better. Always look for the deception," Draco drawled.

"Our parents will be hamming that home for the next decade, yes. Thanks, Draco." Pansy's smile was devastatingly insincere. She turned to Aldon. "This is too much to process verbally. I need you to write down everything you remember about your conversation with Miss Potter and—"

Aldon took a scroll out of his sleeve and handed it over with a smile.

Pansy snatched it with a moue that was not quite a pout. "Thank you. Millie and I will go through this and cross-reference it with other facts. We'll come up with new theories and try to meet again before the new term."

"It's going to be weird without him, isn't it?" Theo said.

"This is what normal looks like, now," Draco said. "We just have to get used to it."

Pansy gave him a proud smile.

"You lot are the worst sort of wallflowers."

Edmund had found them, Alice at his side.

"The anti-social sort?" Pansy came forward to press Alice in a hug, which the older girl tolerated magnanimously.

"The conspiratorial sort," Edmund corrected. "Trading information?"

"More like pooling it," Aldon admitted shamelessly.

"We were just finishing," Pansy said quickly. "Looking forward to the, er, cake-cutting, Edmund."

"And the gift-opening." Blaise had a meaningful note in his voice, and Draco followed his gaze to a small package Edmund was holding half-hidden in his dress robes.

Edmund revealed the present with a slow nod. "That's why we're here. Our elf pre-screened them to prevent any unpleasant surprises and…"

"We got a pleasant surprise instead." Alice lifted the tag so they could read it.

Pansy took two steps forward with a small gasp, her eyes welling up. "Oh, Rigel."

"He sent it?"

"He's alive, then!"

Alive. Rigel was alive.

"Alive and as predictable as ever," Alice said with a small smile.

"We didn't want to bandy it in front of prying eyes, but you all deserve to see it."

Without any fanfare, Edmund pulled on the ribbon and the wrapping fell away. It was a potion, and Draco wanted to cry because of course it was.

"A memory potion," Millicent breathed. "But those are so rare."

"And difficult," Blaise murmured. "How does he have the time or resources on the run…?"

"What does it do?" Theo asked tentatively.

Alice was staring at the bottle like it might disappear at any moment. "It captures important memories. Like a pensive, only you don't have to know any mind magic to use it."

"They retain memories crystal-clear, forever," Millicent said.

"Did he…send a memory?" Blaise asked.

Edmund shook his head. "It's empty. But there's a note." He pulled a small card from his pocket and read it aloud. Draco couldn't help it—he heard the words in Rigel's voice.

Edmund and Alice,

I almost didn't send this, but there's no sense letting a good potion go to waste. If the words of a cheat and a cad mean anything, please accept my good wishes and know that I'd be an even worse person if I'd never met you.

Life is unpredictable. Everything can change in an instant, so cherish what you have as long as you can, and don't take the everyday moments for granted. I put as much into this as I dared, and I'm confident it will hold a lifetime of memories, so don't wait for the big ones—save them all.

For myself, your friendship and guidance will be cherished always.

R

The words sank into Draco's soul and the fire there banked and eased just a little. Rigel's words said so much—except sorry. He was guilty and conflicted. He wasn't sorry.

Alice blinked hard against her mascara. "The little twerp is making it really difficult to stay angry."

Edmund pulled her close. "That isn't your angry face, love."

Millicent had her arm around Pansy, and Theo wrapped them both up with a loud sniff. Aldon pulled Blaise into the mix and the new bride and groom joined the embrace with quiet dignity. Then Pansy held her hand out for Draco, and waited.

He took it, and soaked in the presence of those who knew Rigel best. For a moment, he could see that they felt the loss as keenly as he, though they all expressed it differently.

"He's still our friend, too," Pansy whispered.

That much was clear. Rigel was still their friend and they would find him, no matter what it took. Maybe he couldn't actively look, but he could put himself in places and situations where he might hear something by accident. Pansy was right. Rigel needed them.

And they needed him.